<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Liberal Democrats on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/liberal-democrats/</link><description>Recent content in Liberal Democrats on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/liberal-democrats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>While I was out....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Floella Benjamin campaigns with Sarah Teather</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 13:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</guid><description>WBTimes report that &amp;ldquo;Floella Benjamin ditched the teddy bear props&amp;rdquo; when she joined Lib Dem candidate for Brent Central, Sarah Teather this week. Floella joined Sarah on Harlesden High Street to collect signatures in Harlesden, to sign up residents to a petition urging the government to reform air passenger duty.
Air Passenger Duty (APD) is an excise duty which is charged on the carriage of passengers flying from a United Kingdom airport.</description></item><item><title>NW2 Residents Association Thanks Lib Dem Councillors</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/nw2-residents-association-thanks-lib-dem-councillors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/nw2-residents-association-thanks-lib-dem-councillors/</guid><description>The North West Two Residents Association held its AGM on the 22nd April at the Windmill Pub on Cricklewood Broadway.
NW2 began in September 2007 as a group local residents who wanted to improve the sense of community in the Cricklewood area. As Carol Granger, Committee Chair, writes &amp;ldquo;The Association was founded first to try to improve the sense of community in the area and provide opportunities for people in the neighbourhood to get together, and to get to know each other and maybe help each other out; but also to improve the appearance of the area (litter, graffiti, etc); to try to improve relationships with Brent and the officers who look after services for the area; try to make sure Cricklewood didn&amp;rsquo;t stay the Cinderella of Brent / Barnet / Camden.</description></item><item><title>Labour pay legal costs to Brent Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</guid><description>Brent councillor James Powney laments the threat and use of legal writ to silence debate, tending towards an environment where &amp;lsquo;legitimate freedom of speech could be restricted by self censorship.&amp;rsquo;
Legal writ has its strength though. When Brent Labour distributed a leaflet with false claims about Sarah Teather, the Brent Leb Dems took appropriate legal measures. In the face of the legal action, Labour have now admitted their story was false and agreed to pay the Lib Dems legal costs.</description></item><item><title>WB Times "Butler told to apologise"</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</guid><description>Brent&amp;rsquo;s Labour Group formal apology for issuing leaflets with defamatory claims about Sarah Teather is on page 4 of the WB Times this week.
Willesden and Brent Times, 23 April, 2010</description></item><item><title>Butler issues full apology for Teather expenses smear</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</guid><description>LibDem Voice has some news on Brent Centrals dirty politics.
Labour Minister Dawn Butler has issued a legal apology to Sarah Teather for calling her a hypocrite over MPs’ expenses. Butler made the accusation while the running of Sarah Teather’s office was under investigation. The Parliamentary Standards Commissioner later dropped the investigation because there were no grounds to suspect any wrongdoing by Ms Teather.
This issue came up at the MapRA Hustings on Monday night.</description></item><item><title>MP Sarah Cleared</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A letter of complaint against Sarah Teather was sent to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner, supposedly from a man at an address in Brent. Then a second letter of complaint was sent, again from this man, but giving a new address. However, this new address does not exist. There is a real address with the same house number and postcode (but different rest of address), at which there is one person on the electoral register – a woman who has the name of someone listed on Labour MP Dawn Butler’s register of interests as being a member of her staff.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Labour Team smear tactics....?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</guid><description>In a recent letter to residents of the Mapesbury ward of Brent Central, Labours&amp;rsquo; candidate Angela Griggs slings a little mud on expenses. Apparently complains have been made to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner about Sarah Teathers&amp;rsquo; expenses in relation to her constituency office.
Now we know Sarah&amp;rsquo;s expenses are squeaky clean - check TWFY.com and compare the ACL to Dawn Butler and her £66,000&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Lib Dems choose open-source and free software</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/10/04/lib-dems-choose-open-source-and-free-software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/10/04/lib-dems-choose-open-source-and-free-software/</guid><description>According to Publictechnology.net, the Liberal Democrats have decided to go for Open Source software for organisational infrastructure. The LDs have selected an open-source consultancy and technical services business in Rugby, Credativ, to migrate and support crucial parts of the LibDems tech needs.
I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased to see this commitment to free and open-source software by a major political party!</description></item><item><title>FlockTogether</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/flocktogether/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/flocktogether/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the LibDem FlockTogether page on the Stonebridge local council by-election.</description></item><item><title>FUD review for July</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/08/fud-review-for-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2006 07:35:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/08/fud-review-for-july/</guid><description>FUD? Check wikipedia&amp;hellip;
Received the first campaign materials from Team YellowGold and Team Red since the elections for local government in May. Sorry for the blue tint on the scans, I think my scanner is broken.
The BELD are thanking people for voting for them in Mapesbury and give people the contact numbers of their new local councillors. I won&amp;rsquo;t reprint them here though - surely you can get them from Brent Council (after 6 or 7 clicks) or from the BELD website (well actually you can&amp;rsquo;t find any info about your local councillors or FOCUS TEAM on the BELD website).</description></item><item><title>is the veil intact?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/is-the-veil-intact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/is-the-veil-intact/</guid><description>Electoral law prevents a council from promoting candidates standing in local elections. Has the spirit of the &amp;lsquo;purdah&amp;rsquo; period been broken by Brent Council? The Brent Lib Dems seem to think so. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve not yet seen the article in question, my copy of the Brent Magazine has been sitting unread since it arrived and usually only gets a slight glance before being recycled. I&amp;rsquo;ll get a scan and post it.</description></item><item><title>Focus on...Queen's Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/focus-onqueens-park/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/focus-onqueens-park/</guid><description>A recent Focus On&amp;hellip;Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park from the Liberal Democrats with the candidates for Councillors showing their opposition to the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park tower development.
Lib Dems Focus on Queen&amp;#39;s Park Also highlighted are the traffic problems that are percieved will blight an already congested Salusbury Road. Well, the development is supposed to address this issue by changing the flow of traffic in the area - but with no tower to route traffic around&amp;hellip;?</description></item><item><title>Queen's Park Tower Plan</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</guid><description>The proposal for the tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park is a lead topic for each of the parties contesting the electoral ward of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. For Labour it is getting like the Monty Python topic not to be mentioned in front of our hosts for the World Cup. The Lib Dems have made great gains from this thread - well, a sitting (yet not restanding) Councillor defected to Team Yellow with the tower plan as a key issue.</description></item><item><title>QP Cllr Davies joins Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/qp-cllr-davies-joins-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 12:21:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/qp-cllr-davies-joins-lib-dems/</guid><description>After announcing his intention not to stand in the coming local election in a letter to residents of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park on the 6th, Cllr Jonathan Davies had now joined the Liberal Demcrats.</description></item><item><title>Brent Labour Councillor Jonathan Davies has joined the Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/12/brent-labour-councillor-jonathan-davies-has-joined-the-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 07:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/12/brent-labour-councillor-jonathan-davies-has-joined-the-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Brent Labour Councillor Jonathan Davies has joined the Liberal Democrats reports the BELD website.
&amp;ldquo;I have realised that the beliefs I stand for such as the safeguarding of our civil liberties, international justice and a free and fair society are best represented within the Liberal Democrats.&amp;rdquo;
Also connected to Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s feelings over the proposed development of a tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ? : &amp;ldquo;The issue of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Tower is a classic example of Brent Labour in action.</description></item><item><title>Brent News from the Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 17:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</guid><description>This local red top was delivered in late February. It leads with the news of the Liberal Democrats delivering a &amp;ldquo;hammer blow&amp;rdquo; to Labour&amp;rdquo; in Dunfermline by-election.
brent news lib dems feb 06
The national political story was the continued opposition to the ID card legislation by Sarah Teather and the Liberal Democrats. The newsletter also covered the story of the comments made by Labour Cllr Jonathan Davies on the &amp;lsquo;consultation&amp;rsquo; over the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Tower plans.</description></item><item><title>the lib dems stand up for us</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/the-lib-dems-stand-up-for-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/the-lib-dems-stand-up-for-us/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;the lib dems stand up for us&amp;rdquo; ? well it is a Brent Lib Dem flyer&amp;hellip; this flyer arrived in either late Feb or early March - the trail started early for the BELD team.
BELD stand up for us feb/mar 06
The update lacks focus - there are a lot of different things crammed ontoa doublesided sheet of A4. Quality of life/local environment make the agenda again - also mentioned is that the lib dems want to focus council tax receipts on public services, sports facilities and public toliets - with disabled access?</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>also in early march I received the Liberal Democrat Focus On&amp;hellip;Mapesbury newsletter. This newsletter was the first opportunity to meet the Lib Dem candidates for the Mapesbury wards. The candidates are Chris Leaman, Sami Hashmi and Hayley Matthews.
LD Focus On Mapesbury March 2006
The BELDs expect that a Labour council would again increase council taxes significantly after the local elections. The LDs (as we know) propose a &amp;lsquo;fairer system&amp;rsquo; of local income taxation.</description></item><item><title>calling it as you see it</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/calling-it-as-you-see-it/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 12:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/calling-it-as-you-see-it/</guid><description>Brent Lib Dems have been redistributing the comments made by Labour Cllr for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Jonathan Davies on the governance and effectiveness of Brents&amp;rsquo; Labour Council.
Outer of BELD &amp;lsquo;the verdict&amp;rsquo; flyer
I&amp;rsquo;m glad to see that Cllr Davies has the ability to speak his own mind and to make judgements based on his observations. His views on the consultation around the proposed development consisting of a tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park will chime with many in the local area.</description></item><item><title>You can take your time...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/17/you-can-take-your-time/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/17/you-can-take-your-time/</guid><description>&amp;hellip;picking a shadow cabinet when you don&amp;rsquo;t have all eyes watching, waiting for you to make clear exactly what your intentions are with regard to the party. If your leadership hasn&amp;rsquo;t been subjected to intense probing by spectators and participants alike you are not under the same pressures and scrutiny and can take stock, deliberate before revealing your hand.
Having worked as a constituency MP for the last 18 months and increased her majority in the face of a strong Labour campaign, Sarah is to join the Liberal Democrat &amp;lsquo;front bench&amp;rsquo; team.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 02:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Received a letter from Charles Kennedy this morning urging me to vote because &amp;lsquo;in certain places, the election is effectively a straight choice between having a Liberal Democrat or a Labour MP&amp;rsquo;.
The real alternative has been distilled to four key points:
end student tuition and top-up fees prevent older people having to selltheir homes to pay for long term personal care provide 10,000 more police and cut their paperwork scrap the unfair council tax A little something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-2/</guid><description>Received a letter from Charles Kennedy this morning urging me to vote because &amp;lsquo;in certain places, the election is effectively a straight choice between having a Liberal Democrat or a Labour MP&amp;rsquo;.
The real alternative has been distilled to four key points:
end student tuition and top-up fees prevent older people having to selltheir homes to pay for long term personal care provide 10,000 more police and cut their paperwork scrap the unfair council tax A little something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Charles Kennedy in Brent East</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/charles-kennedy-in-brent-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/charles-kennedy-in-brent-east/</guid><description>If you received a copy of Brent People from the Liberal Democrats over the weekend you&amp;rsquo;ll have seen this pic already.
More over at Brent East Campaigning</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-3/</guid><description>A departure from the tabloid red top of Brent News, the latest campaign freesheet from the Lib Dems, Brent News, leads with the headline of &amp;lsquo;Sarah Set To Win&amp;rsquo; - naturally&amp;hellip;
It features a photo of the Liberal Democrat leader Charles Kennedy with Sarah Teather on Kilburn High Road. Good to see that when top &amp;lsquo;names&amp;rsquo; (to borrow the description Yasmin gave to the &amp;lsquo;top labour&amp;rsquo; people who have given her support) from the Lib Dems come to support their candidate it is their Leader and prospective Prime Minister that visits.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Many postings to this blog today. It&amp;rsquo;s all I&amp;rsquo;ve done this morning!
I&amp;rsquo;ve received a letter from Sarah Teather for her campaign to be re-elected by the people of Brent East to serve a second term.
Her message: &amp;lsquo;I believe that people in Brent East deserve a local MP who will stand up to Tony Blair. I am proud to fight this election on my record of local action from fighting for fairer funding for our local schools to welcoming more police for Dudden Hill, Kilburn and Willesden Green.</description></item><item><title>Positive Alternatives from the Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/23/positive-alternatives-from-the-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2005 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/23/positive-alternatives-from-the-lib-dems/</guid><description>10 Good Reasons to vote Liberal Democrat from http://www.libdems.org.uk/.
Read about Sarah launching the Lib Dem poster campaign.
WE OPPOSE: Putting targets first
WE PROPOSE: Putting patients first
WE OPPOSE: Tuition fees &amp;amp; top up fees
WE PROPOSE: Scrapping student fees
WE OPPOSE: Compulsory I.D. Cards
WE PROPOSE: Spending the money on 10,000 more police
WE OPPOSE: Selling your home to pay for care
WE PROPOSE: Free personal care for the elderly</description></item><item><title>Feeling blue?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/feeling-blue/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/feeling-blue/</guid><description>I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure who the campaign material that recently popped through my front door belonged to. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t inclined to turn the flyer over really&amp;hellip; I read the Guardian &amp;amp; the Indy, I get enough conservative bashing on a daily basis to have toned it out. But who was it from&amp;hellip; Labour or Lib Dem? A closer inspection and I trained my eye on the graphic in the bottom corner which gave it away as anti-tory material published by Brent Lib Dems.</description></item><item><title>News from Number 1, High Road, Willesden Green</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/news-from-number-1-high-road-willesden-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 14:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/news-from-number-1-high-road-willesden-green/</guid><description>In last weeks Willesden &amp;amp; Brent Chronicle, Sarah wrote of the recent silly season for the UK&amp;rsquo;s political parties, hammered home the message that the Lib Dems are now the second party of British Politics (although, not yet Her Majesty&amp;rsquo;s Official Opposition) and invited us to make a cup of tea while waiting for the pre-manifesto to download.
&amp;ldquo;The Conference Feelgood Factor&amp;rdquo;
It is conference season. To those uninterested in politics the annual tradition of political gatherings with their set piece speeches and media razzmatazz in some seaside town must seem a little odd.</description></item><item><title>Liberal Democrat Pre-Manifesto</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/08/liberal-democrat-pre-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 21:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/08/liberal-democrat-pre-manifesto/</guid><description>Available for download from Sarah&amp;rsquo;s website is the LDs pre-manifesto &amp;ldquo;Freedom Fairness Trust&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;ll save you a £1 on buying it. Although as it is a 5.8MB PDF (with an estimated 17 minutes download at 56k) of 12 full colour pages, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t advise you print it&amp;hellip;not with the cost of inkjet printing.
But I would advise you read it; well, at least give the front page a glance and read the Ten Reason to vote Liberal Democrat.</description></item><item><title>Jody Dunn’s Campaign Diary</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/26/jody-dunns-campaign-diary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2004 15:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/26/jody-dunns-campaign-diary/</guid><description>Today I extend my congratualtions and a big welcome to the blogging community to Jody Dunn, Liberal Democrate candidate in the (maybe) Hartlepool by-election.
You can read her blog at http://www.jodydunn.org.uk/
Sarah visited Jody in Hartlepool last week. It was the highlight of Jody&amp;rsquo;s day.
I hope that Jody will share her blogging experiences with Sarah when they next meet. Maybe that will change Sarah&amp;rsquo;s perception of blogging.</description></item></channel></rss>