<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sarah Teather on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/sarah-teather/</link><description>Recent content in Sarah Teather on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 10:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/sarah-teather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sarah Teather no longer my MP?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2013/09/08/sarah-teather-no-longer-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 10:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2013/09/08/sarah-teather-no-longer-my-mp/</guid><description>As many of you know I used to have a blog here called &amp;lsquo;Sarah Teather is My MP&amp;rsquo;. But it looks like soon (2015) Sarah is to stand down from Parliament and will no longer be my MP. The former Children&amp;rsquo;s Minister told the Observer that she feels Nick Clegg&amp;rsquo;s party no longer campaigns sufficiently for social justice and liberal values on immigration. In a statement on her website, she said that her differences with the party &amp;ldquo;have been getting larger rather than smaller&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather appointed Minister of State for Children and Families</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/14/sarah-teather-appointed-minister-of-state-for-children-and-families/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/14/sarah-teather-appointed-minister-of-state-for-children-and-families/</guid><description>Brent&amp;rsquo;s LibDem MP ﻿﻿Sarah Teather has been appointed Minister of State for Children and Families at the Department of Education by David Cameron. Sarah will work under the new education secretary Michael Gove who had immediately renamed this department from the ﻿﻿﻿Department for Children, Schools and Families (DCSF). Top. Priority. A surprise appointment? Others had suggested housing&amp;hellip;. A quick search shows that Sarah has taken an interest in this area in the past - ﻿she has asked around 50 questions of (what was) the DCSF and taken an interest in education issues within other Departments.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather - Housing Minister?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/13/sarah-teather-housing-minister/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 13:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/13/sarah-teather-housing-minister/</guid><description>Public sector newswires with insufficient to talk about have been waiting for news on who the new Housing minister would be, with Grant Shapps and Sarah Teather the most likely candidates. Housing is an issue Sarah has spoken about often in the Commons.</description></item><item><title>Brent's General Election results.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</guid><description>The voters of Brent have returned Lib Dem Sarah Teather with a majority of 1,345, a swing of 11% from Labour, and Labour&amp;rsquo;s Barry Gardiner with a majority of 8,028, loosing 2.5% of the vote to the Conservatives (+2.2%) and other parties. I was at the count on Thursday night tally marking for the Lib Dems and in-between boxes of ballot papers talking with candidates and journalists about the political economy of Brent as a borough.</description></item><item><title>Floella Benjamin campaigns with Sarah Teather</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 13:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</guid><description>WBTimes report that &amp;ldquo;Floella Benjamin ditched the teddy bear props&amp;rdquo; when she joined Lib Dem candidate for Brent Central, Sarah Teather this week. Floella joined Sarah on Harlesden High Street to collect signatures in Harlesden, to sign up residents to a petition urging the government to reform air passenger duty.
Air Passenger Duty (APD) is an excise duty which is charged on the carriage of passengers flying from a United Kingdom airport.</description></item><item><title>Labour pay legal costs to Brent Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</guid><description>Brent councillor James Powney laments the threat and use of legal writ to silence debate, tending towards an environment where &amp;lsquo;legitimate freedom of speech could be restricted by self censorship.&amp;rsquo;
Legal writ has its strength though. When Brent Labour distributed a leaflet with false claims about Sarah Teather, the Brent Leb Dems took appropriate legal measures. In the face of the legal action, Labour have now admitted their story was false and agreed to pay the Lib Dems legal costs.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather commended by British Muslim Initiative and salaam.co.uk</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/24/sarah-teather-commended-by-british-muslim-initiative-and-salaam-co-uk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 00:11:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/24/sarah-teather-commended-by-british-muslim-initiative-and-salaam-co-uk/</guid><description>YouElect is a non-profit and independent British Muslim grassroots initiative aimed at promoting voter registration and political engagement. I&amp;rsquo;ve just looked up Brent Central where Sarah Teather is the Community Choice Candidate, commended by both the British Muslim Initiative and salaam.co.uk.
Dawn Butler and Sachin Rajput are also profiled on the YouElect site.</description></item><item><title>WB Times "Butler told to apologise"</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</guid><description>Brent&amp;rsquo;s Labour Group formal apology for issuing leaflets with defamatory claims about Sarah Teather is on page 4 of the WB Times this week.
Willesden and Brent Times, 23 April, 2010</description></item><item><title>Butler issues full apology for Teather expenses smear</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</guid><description>LibDem Voice has some news on Brent Centrals dirty politics.
Labour Minister Dawn Butler has issued a legal apology to Sarah Teather for calling her a hypocrite over MPs’ expenses. Butler made the accusation while the running of Sarah Teather’s office was under investigation. The Parliamentary Standards Commissioner later dropped the investigation because there were no grounds to suspect any wrongdoing by Ms Teather.
This issue came up at the MapRA Hustings on Monday night.</description></item><item><title>MP Sarah Cleared</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A letter of complaint against Sarah Teather was sent to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner, supposedly from a man at an address in Brent. Then a second letter of complaint was sent, again from this man, but giving a new address. However, this new address does not exist. There is a real address with the same house number and postcode (but different rest of address), at which there is one person on the electoral register – a woman who has the name of someone listed on Labour MP Dawn Butler’s register of interests as being a member of her staff.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Labour Team smear tactics....?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</guid><description>In a recent letter to residents of the Mapesbury ward of Brent Central, Labours&amp;rsquo; candidate Angela Griggs slings a little mud on expenses. Apparently complains have been made to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner about Sarah Teathers&amp;rsquo; expenses in relation to her constituency office.
Now we know Sarah&amp;rsquo;s expenses are squeaky clean - check TWFY.com and compare the ACL to Dawn Butler and her £66,000&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>MySociety's 'Free Our Bills' campaign</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/mysociety-free-our-bills-campaign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 15:02:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/mysociety-free-our-bills-campaign/</guid><description>Today I&amp;rsquo;ve accessed three different MySociety websites: TheyWorkForYou, WriteToThem and WhatDoTheyKnow. I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;d do without these powerful tools: MySociety are indespensible and we&amp;rsquo;d all miss them if they weren&amp;rsquo;t here.
I was using WriteToThem to contact Sarah Teather to urge her to support Early Day Motion (EDM) 2141 that her parliamentary colleague Jo Swinson has tabled.
 FREE OUR BILLS CAMPAIGN, 22.07.2008, Swinson, Jo
That this House believes it has a duty to publish Bills in such a fashion that they can be accessed as easily and as early as possible by the public; notes that the non-partisan Free Our Bills campaign is urging the House to publish bill texts in a new electronic format to improve accessibility and public scrutiny of legislation; further notes that the changes requested would have no impact on the content of Bills, nor upon the process by which they are currently made; considers that the new format could be delivered cheaply and quickly; acknowledges that the Leader of the House&amp;rsquo;s office did not accept a prior request for new formatting from mySociety, nor provide an explanation of why the changes could be made; and calls on the Leader of House to ask House of Commons Clerks to work with Free Our Bills campaign staff to commence publication of Bills in the new format.</description></item><item><title>Remarkable.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/09/05/293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2007 08:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/09/05/293/</guid><description>Daniel Finkelstein puts the boot into the Lib Dems and encourages leadership machinations ahead of the party conference season, goading Ming into a long walk along a short pier.
&amp;ldquo;Remarkably few people will shout through to the kitchen: &amp;lsquo;Hold dinner for a moment, love, Sarah Teather’s on.&amp;rsquo; &amp;quot; - I must be one of the remarkable few.</description></item><item><title>Poke Sarah!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/18/poke-sarah/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2007 09:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/18/poke-sarah/</guid><description>Sarah Teather and other Brent Liberal Democrates have joined facebook. I&amp;rsquo;ve poked her, have you?
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting to see our Sarah on Facebook&amp;hellip; A few years ago electronic networking wasn&amp;rsquo;t on her list methods for constituency communications. How things change over time: the ubiquity of the term &amp;ldquo;social networking&amp;rdquo;, meaning a twittering, bebobuzzing space for me to show my face on the internet, has overtaken &amp;ldquo;blogging&amp;rdquo; in terms of its penetration into the nations daily lexicon.</description></item><item><title>bosom buddy</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/07/19/bosom-buddy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/07/19/bosom-buddy/</guid><description>This story got me posting as I&amp;rsquo;m a new father and my daughter is breastfed. Sarah was campaigning earlier this week with the NCT in support of their call for legislation to enshrine a woman&amp;rsquo;s right to breastfeed in public in England. The Scots have such legislation (must have been a devolved competancy) but in England and Wales breastfeeding in public is not protected. Both myself and my partner are in support of this legisation and support the NCT&amp;rsquo;s campaign.</description></item><item><title>The Teather Factor</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/13/the-teather-factor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2006 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/13/the-teather-factor/</guid><description>Speaking on the &amp;lsquo;carnage&amp;rsquo; following the local elections in Brent, Labour Cllr Mary Arnold acknowledges that Team Yellow worked hard for the victories they knotched up:
&amp;ldquo;There is also the Teather factor - there&amp;rsquo;s a machinery that the Lib Dems have got for producing leaflets and campaigning, for bringing people in to canvass.&amp;rdquo;
The Lib Dems did manage to distribute a lot of paper in Mapesbury and Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park - significantly more than teams Red and Blue.</description></item><item><title>She speaks!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/24/she-speaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/24/she-speaks/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Perhaps I can drag the right hon. Gentleman away from the spat with the Conservative Front-Bench spokesman, fun though it is&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Well, those where her first words of the new parliament&amp;hellip;
Sarah returns to the House of Commons and continues her efforts at tackling the housing &amp;lsquo;crisis&amp;rsquo; in Brent. Those of you who are regular readers of the BELD website will recall her speech of Oct last year in Westminster Hall on this topic.</description></item><item><title>A news round-up</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/a-news-round-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/a-news-round-up/</guid><description>Not awake at 415am? Shame as you missed Sarah&amp;rsquo;s victory speech! If you want to watch it you can thanks to the BBC.
Paul Palmer of the Evening Standard, who was having terrible trouble with his laptop when trying to submit his story, writes about the Brent East result. He focuses on Yasmin loosing rather than Sarah winning.
More later, when google news advises me of it!</description></item><item><title>Brent East - the morning after...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/brent-east-the-morning-after/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/brent-east-the-morning-after/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve posted over at Brent East Campaigning about yesterday, the election count and the result - take a peek.
Looks like the BELDs need to get their website updated&amp;hellip; no mention yet of Sarahs HOLD of Brent East.
From the Lib Dem website election news ticker:
04.12 GAIN - Sarah Teather wins the Brent East seat she won at a by-election (technically a gain measured from 2001) with a swing of 30% and a majority of 2,700</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather Is STILL My MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/sarah-teather-is-still-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/sarah-teather-is-still-my-mp/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve woken up and eaten - needed to do that before posting anything. NK and I left the count after Sarah Teather had been returned as the MP for Brent East, but not before posting to sarah teather is my MP. I&amp;rsquo;ve still got the &amp;lsquo;wild eyes&amp;rsquo; I had yesterday, although that&amp;rsquo;s now from lack of sleep. This politics junkie had quite an Election Day.
As I posted yesterday, I&amp;rsquo;d been out and about in Mapesbury and Willesden with June Thomas from Slate Magazine.</description></item><item><title>Brent East by-election, 2003</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/brent-east-by-election-2003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/brent-east-by-election-2003/</guid><description>The by-election of 2003 was caused by the death of the member of Parliament for Brent East, Paul Daisley of the Labour Party. The by-election to fill his seat was held on September 13, and was won by the Liberal Democrat candidate Sarah Teather.
The turnout by electors at this election was 36.42%
More information on the 2003 Brent East by-election from wikipedia.</description></item><item><title>Positive Alternatives from the Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/23/positive-alternatives-from-the-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2005 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/23/positive-alternatives-from-the-lib-dems/</guid><description>10 Good Reasons to vote Liberal Democrat from http://www.libdems.org.uk/.
Read about Sarah launching the Lib Dem poster campaign.
WE OPPOSE: Putting targets first
WE PROPOSE: Putting patients first
WE OPPOSE: Tuition fees &amp;amp; top up fees
WE PROPOSE: Scrapping student fees
WE OPPOSE: Compulsory I.D. Cards
WE PROPOSE: Spending the money on 10,000 more police
WE OPPOSE: Selling your home to pay for care
WE PROPOSE: Free personal care for the elderly</description></item><item><title>Postage problems.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/22/postage-problems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2005 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/22/postage-problems/</guid><description>Sarah is being blighted by postage problems. It seems that whenever she writes to a member of the government they take months to respond or the letter is delayed.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example.
Letter sent - 14 Oct 2004
Parliamentary question asked to chase up - 4 March 2005
Reply sent - 22 February 2005
Another. Two on the 22nd of Feb, here and here. Another from the 21st Feb.
Extremely late replies, letters not received at each end - poor filing perhaps?</description></item><item><title>Busy day today.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/09/busy-day-today/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2005 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/09/busy-day-today/</guid><description>Sarah will be at Downing Street today to deliver a 1,000 name petition on behalf of Hindu&amp;rsquo;s opposing further restrictions by the Home Office on religious workers seeking leave to stay in the UK.
For the Home Office, the measures they wish to take (outlined here by The Scotsman) are part of building community cohesion.
&amp;ldquo;Multi-cultural communities are often multi- faith communities and this should be fully recognised in policies aimed at promoting diversity.</description></item><item><title>EDM for Parliament to approve military actions</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/03/edm-for-parliament-to-approve-military-actions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2005 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/03/edm-for-parliament-to-approve-military-actions/</guid><description>Some of you may remember that I wrote to Sarah asking her if she will be supporting the motion to impeach Tony Blair. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t minded to.
She wrote to me last week after going through some papers and finding my email. Papers? Email? I know, I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get it either. I digress. She wrote to me last week to bring an Early Day Motion she had recently signed to my attention.</description></item><item><title>Tution Fees Text Poll</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/21/tution-fees-text-poll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2005 23:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/21/tution-fees-text-poll/</guid><description>Sarah launched a text poll on tuition fees. Describing tuition fees as an unfair tax on students, Sarah said &amp;ldquo;Tuition fees will be one of the key issues to many at the forthcoming General Election. Many people are now suffering horrendous levels of debt because of Labour&amp;rsquo;s broken promise on this issue.&amp;rdquo;
The Liberal Democrats are committed to scrapping tuition fees. To pay for free higher education they will introduce a 50p tax rate on incomes over £100,000.</description></item><item><title>Congratulations Brent East.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/congratulations-brent-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/congratulations-brent-east/</guid><description>Sarah has been unanimously re-selected by Brent Liberal Democrats to fight the next General Election. You can read the news story on this over at the BELD website.
Sarah said she would be campaigning for a renewed mandate from the electorate of Brent East on local issues such as civic neglect, neighbourhood policing, housing problems and post office closures. Her efforts would continue in the House of Commons tackling ID cards, detention without trail and student tuition fees.</description></item><item><title>Opposition Day: Family Doctor Services</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/opposition-day-family-doctor-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/opposition-day-family-doctor-services/</guid><description>It was a busy Commons week for Sarah last week. Not content with appearing in Hoggart&amp;rsquo;s Sketch&amp;hellip;Sorry&amp;hellip;Questioning the Prime Minister over a serious funding shortfall caused by the actions of Government, Sarah was also speaking up for Family Doctor services in Brent East on Opposition Day.
Speaking of the impact of the Governments 48-hour first appointment target for GPs on the forward planning of appointments, Sarah said that despite repeated assurances from Brent PCT that there would be no impact, patients were experiencing problems.</description></item><item><title>How do you know you’ve made it as an MP?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/how-do-you-know-youve-made-it-as-an-mp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/how-do-you-know-youve-made-it-as-an-mp/</guid><description>How do you know you&amp;rsquo;ve made it as an MP? When Simon Hoggart features you in his Sketch. It had taken our Sarah a little over a year to gain such acceptance. It was after her performance in Prime Ministers Question Time last week Simon welcomed her into the fold.
&amp;ldquo;Prime minister&amp;rsquo;s questions, and the Liberal Democrat Sarah Teather rose to speak. She is very short and is the youngest of all MPs, but she is also pretty tough.</description></item><item><title>I’m not going to make a fortune this way...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/im-not-going-to-make-a-fortune-this-way/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/15/im-not-going-to-make-a-fortune-this-way/</guid><description>Dividends from Polidex for week ending Sunday 14, November 2004
MP: Sarah Teather
Full shares: 268
Additional shares: 1
Increase: 0%
Profit: euro0.00
Total profit this week: euro0.00
New total value: euro1,395.66</description></item><item><title>The problem with being a keen recycler...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/01/the-problem-with-being-a-keen-recycler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2004 13:10:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/11/01/the-problem-with-being-a-keen-recycler/</guid><description>&amp;hellip;is sometimes you recycle things too quickly. And I that is what happened to last weeks Kilburn Times. So, I can&amp;rsquo;t give you a copy of the data published by the them right now. I&amp;rsquo;m going to mail the paper and see if I can get a copy from them.</description></item><item><title>also from the Kilburn Times...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/30/also-from-the-kilburn-times/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2004 17:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/30/also-from-the-kilburn-times/</guid><description>In the Kilburn Times this week, Sarah features three times on the letters page.
She is pictured with staff from the New Deal Communities group announcing further measures to curb anti-social behavior in South Kilburn. Residents of estates in South Kilburn are being urged to report drug-dealing to Crimestoppers and Crime Concern to reduce the high drug crime rate of the area.
There are two letters relating to an award presented by Sarah reported in the October 20th edition of the paper.</description></item><item><title>Compare and contrast</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/29/compare-and-contrast/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2004 01:41:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/29/compare-and-contrast/</guid><description>Last week, in a show of openness prior to the commencement of the &amp;lsquo;Freedom of Information Act&amp;rsquo; next year, MPs released the details of their expenses for public review. In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Kilburn Times, part of the Archant London Group of newspapers, Kristina Pedersen reports on the disclosure.
The paper has published tables comparing the MPs that serve the constituencies that their paper is published in: - Tony McNulty (Harrow East), Paul Boateng (Brent South), Barry Gardiner (Brent North), Gareth Thomas (Harrow West), Mark Field (Cities of London &amp;amp; Westminster), Karen Buck (Regent&amp;rsquo;s Park &amp;amp; Kensington North), Clive Soley (Ealing, Acton &amp;amp; Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Bush), Glenda Jackson (Hampstead &amp;amp; Highgate), Iain Coleman (Putney), Sarah Teather (Brent East) and Michael Portillo (Kensington &amp;amp; Chelsea).</description></item><item><title>MP’s expenses</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/29/mps-expenses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2004 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/29/mps-expenses/</guid><description>I wrote the post below last weekend - but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to post it until today. Sorry.
I was sure I was going to have something to say on this topic after I saw the manner which the placater of the commuting masses &amp;lsquo;Metro&amp;rsquo; covered the story: &amp;ldquo;UK pay is dwarfed by MP&amp;rsquo;s expenses&amp;rdquo; (Frontpage, Fri 22 Oct). Here we have an example of the media creating a frenzy.</description></item><item><title>And relax....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2004 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</guid><description>And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)
Been busy. Enrolled on BA Politics Economic and Public Policy at Goldsmiths University. Getting my teeth stuck in. Substantial stuff. Satisfying.
And then there is [And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title>Privacy and SPAM</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/20/privacy-and-spam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2004 15:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/20/privacy-and-spam/</guid><description>I wrote to Sarah last week after reporting on her questioning of the Secretary of State for Trade and Industry on the subject of unsolicited telecommunications. I asked her what steps would the Liberal Democrats take to combat SPAM? Would the LD&amp;rsquo;s advocate OPT-IN or OPT-OUT measures? Would LD&amp;rsquo;s toughen up privacy laws to protect my contact details or will they be relaxed?
Sarah was prompt in her response. I wrote using her direct @parliament.</description></item><item><title>Happy anniversary Sarah!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/14/happy-anniversary-sarah/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/14/happy-anniversary-sarah/</guid><description>Today Sarah celebrates the first anniversary of being elected to serve Brent East. 365 Days in office. Happy anniversary Sarah.
In today&amp;rsquo;s Guardian Sarah is interviewed by Matt Barnard where she talks about the highlights of the last 12 months.
Top thing you probably didn&amp;rsquo;t know about Sarah that you&amp;rsquo;ll discover from the interview - she&amp;rsquo;s learning Gujarati.</description></item><item><title>Stopping Spam!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/stopping-spam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 14:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/stopping-spam/</guid><description>Sarah has been asking questions of the Secretary of State for Trade and Industry relating to unsolicited bulk communications (be they by mail, telephone or fax calls or email.
You can follow the question thread here.
Sarah wanted to know how many residential and commercial address have registered for the Address Preference Service - But because the Post Office is no longer a state concern, the address preference service is not managed by the government but by Royal Mail Group.</description></item><item><title>News from Number 1, High Road, Willesden Green</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/news-from-number-1-high-road-willesden-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 14:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/13/news-from-number-1-high-road-willesden-green/</guid><description>In last weeks Willesden &amp;amp; Brent Chronicle, Sarah wrote of the recent silly season for the UK&amp;rsquo;s political parties, hammered home the message that the Lib Dems are now the second party of British Politics (although, not yet Her Majesty&amp;rsquo;s Official Opposition) and invited us to make a cup of tea while waiting for the pre-manifesto to download.
&amp;ldquo;The Conference Feelgood Factor&amp;rdquo;
It is conference season. To those uninterested in politics the annual tradition of political gatherings with their set piece speeches and media razzmatazz in some seaside town must seem a little odd.</description></item><item><title>My Douglas Adams Fridge</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/24/my-douglas-adams-fridge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2004 14:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/24/my-douglas-adams-fridge/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ll remember Sarah&amp;rsquo;s campaign - it is highly memorable after all! Without a hit of sarcasam: when I am walking about Brent and I see the spoil that is illegal fly-tipping I think &amp;lsquo;thats a grot spot that is&amp;rsquo;.
Well. I recently disposed the aging 1980s 75/25 Fridge/Ice Box monster that lurked in the corner of my kitchen and took delivery of two purring sleek shinning white replacements. So now I have the need for a &amp;lsquo;Special Collection&amp;rsquo; from Brent&amp;rsquo;s Street Care Team.</description></item><item><title>Liberty or Equality?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/21/liberty-or-equality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/21/liberty-or-equality/</guid><description>At one of the Guardian sponsored fringe events surrounding the Liberal Democrat conference in Bournemouth yesterday, Sarah shared the stage with Nick Clegg, Mark Oaten and Sir Menzies Campbell debating Liberty or Equality?
Anyone blogging from the LD conference attend?
&amp;ldquo;Ms Teather, the party&amp;rsquo;s victor in last year&amp;rsquo;s Brent East byelection, suggested a compromise of &amp;ldquo;licensed smoking bars&amp;rdquo; if a public ban on smoking comes into force, while Sir Menzies, fresh from his barnstorming conference speech on foreign policy, suggested introducing a &amp;ldquo;civil liberties audit&amp;rdquo; against which all future incursions on citizens&amp;rsquo; rights be measured.</description></item><item><title>Party Conference Outing</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/19/party-conference-outing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 17:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/19/party-conference-outing/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Sex, gaffes and silly stunts - it&amp;rsquo;s party (conference) time again and Westminster&amp;rsquo;s circus is heading off to the coast.&amp;rdquo;
Participating in the Guardian fringe debate at the Lib Dem conference on Mon 20th will be Sarah Teather. &amp;ldquo;Liberty v equality: which do the Liberal Democrats want?&amp;rdquo;
Simon Hoggart chairs a panel of Sir Menzies Campbell, Nick Clegg, Sarah Teather MP and Mark Oaten MP.
You can read the Guardian Special Report on the Lib Dem Conference here.</description></item><item><title>Update: Impeaching Tony Blair</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/19/update-impeaching-tony-blair/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/19/update-impeaching-tony-blair/</guid><description>Last month, I faxed Sarah to get her views on the move to impeach Tony Blair.
Awaiting me on my return from holiday was a soft creamy envelope from the House of Commons. It&amp;rsquo;s dated 7th September so, if you allow for fax being sent on FRI 27th and the Bank Holiday Monday that followed, I make that a response within 5 working days. Tick in box - Faxyourmp.com informed.</description></item><item><title>Who is my MP?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/16/who-is-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2004 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/16/who-is-my-mp/</guid><description>Search the All Seeing Eye (You know who I mean&amp;hellip;.) for &amp;ldquo;Who Is My MP&amp;rdquo;?
And&amp;hellip;..</description></item><item><title>News Round-up</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/15/news-round-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2004 13:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/15/news-round-up/</guid><description>Ok, I know I said that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to comment on that story, but in the end I did. I had some time while sitting waiting for my outbound flight. And yes, my holiday was very refreshing, thanks.
Teather Opens Erin Court
Sarah cut the ribbon (I assume; no photo of this) on Erin Court on Friday 3rd. Developed by Sutherland Housing Association, Erin Court provides housing for key workers from Brent specifically education and NHS workers.</description></item><item><title>Crude and attention grabbing?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/02/crude-and-attention-grabbing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2004 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/02/crude-and-attention-grabbing/</guid><description>Well, why else would someone call it Operation Gobstoppers? Althought after &amp;lsquo;Grot Spots', what did I expect?
When you read Sarah&amp;rsquo;s comments made on the launch of the initiative you&amp;rsquo;ll notice that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t use the verb &amp;lsquo;to gob&amp;rsquo; once! She uses &amp;lsquo;to spit&amp;rsquo;! Perhaps it should have been called Operation SpitStopper.
&amp;ldquo;Being spat at is a horrible thing not only is it totally anti-social it also carries health risks particularly in a place like Brent, which has such a high rate of TB.</description></item><item><title>A few notes by way of an update.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/02/a-few-notes-by-way-of-an-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2004 03:31:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/02/a-few-notes-by-way-of-an-update/</guid><description>No response from my fax to Sarah last week. I&amp;rsquo;m sure she&amp;rsquo;ll respond within the target timescale - maybe even bettering her average response time! (she currently responds to 42% of messages sent via FaxYourMP.com within 14 days).
There are some dates for your diary on the BELD website. Sarah Teather holds six advice surgeries a month you can find the times and venues here.
I&amp;rsquo;m just not going to pass comment on this.</description></item><item><title>Will Sarah vote to impeach Blair?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/will-sarah-vote-to-impeach-blair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2004 14:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/will-sarah-vote-to-impeach-blair/</guid><description>Yesterday moves were made to begin impeachment proceedings on Tony Blair. I want to know where Sarah stands on this issue.
Sent via FaxYourMP.com
Dear Sarah Teather,
Yesterday afternoon a group of MPs launched a campaign to impeach Tony Blair for &amp;ldquo;high crimes and misdemeanours&amp;rdquo; in the run up to the war against Iraq.
As I&amp;rsquo;m sure you will agree, the prime minister still has a case to answer regarding his role in persuading parliament to support the war in Iraq.</description></item><item><title>PRAI, FOCI, BELD, ST, BLOG!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/prai-foci-beld-st-blog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2004 01:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/prai-foci-beld-st-blog/</guid><description>PRAI, FOCI, BELD, ST, BLOG? read on.
I received a mail this afternoon from Tim at Prater Raines Partners. PRAI are the people who developed FOCI, the web content management system used by Sarah and the Brent Lib Dems.
Hi Tim. As CMS go, FOCI is pretty good. There are lots of functions: election graphs, opinion polls, online petitions. Although as I&amp;rsquo;ve not seen the user interface I can&amp;rsquo;t comment on it&amp;rsquo;s easy of use as a tool.</description></item><item><title>Information Request</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/25/information-request/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 14:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/25/information-request/</guid><description>To: info@brentlibdems.org.uk
Date: Wed, 25 Aug 2004 10:06:01 +0100
Subject: Information request
Hello,
I was hoping that your office could forward me the results of the 2003 Brent
Residents survey. On your website you state that you will be reporting back to
local residents, however I do not find this report on the website.
Many thanks,
Rob</description></item><item><title>Stock photography</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/25/stock-photography/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 14:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/25/stock-photography/</guid><description>Or, how to give out the desired impression by using images.
In 2003, Sarah undertook a Residents Survey. The people of Brent were asked 50 questions on key-issues in a door to door survey. You can have a look at the PDF of the survey here.
Take a look at the photograph of Sarah and Cllr Havard Hughes with bulging post bag of responses that accompanies the news post in June 2003.</description></item><item><title>She’s right....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/19/shes-right/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2004 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/19/shes-right/</guid><description>it is &amp;ldquo;bureaucratic nonsense&amp;rdquo;.
Under rules introduced by the Home Office last month, Australians, Canadians, New Zealanders, South Africans and Americans must prove they have a good grasp of English to become UK citizens. Yet the Home Office has to decide who will judge this.
Meanwhile, applications for naturalisation are being rejected. Sarah wrote to David Blunket highlighting the &amp;ldquo;bureaucratic nonsense&amp;rdquo; of the rules after one of her constituents was rejected.</description></item><item><title>Meeting with Sarah Teather</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/18/meeting-with-sarah-teather/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2004 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/18/meeting-with-sarah-teather/</guid><description>On Monday afternoon I met with Sarah Teather in her constituency office on Willesden Lane. We spoke about a number of things: blogging (needless to say), engaging with constituents, getting voice for unreported activities, technology as a barrier (for BELD!) and as an enabler (for local people) and also a little project I’ve been working on.
How Sarah engages with her constituents
The BELDs maintain an office on the Willesden High Road.</description></item><item><title>1000th unique page loads</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/12/1000th-unique-page-loads/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2004 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/12/1000th-unique-page-loads/</guid><description>At 01:26 this morning, sarah teather is my mp received its 1000th unique page load.
from the statcounter logs&amp;hellip;
Users of the Parliament network can&amp;rsquo;t type. They keep on ending up at the blog after searching for a miss-spelling of &amp;lsquo;sarah teather is my mp&amp;rsquo; Users who arrive at the site from search engine results have only used Google to search Those working late on the Brent Council Network had fun with the &amp;ldquo;Google &amp;lsquo;sarah teather&amp;rsquo; find the blog game&amp;rdquo; on Tuesday</description></item><item><title>Sarah wants to know your views</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/11/sarah-wants-to-know-your-views/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2004 16:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/11/sarah-wants-to-know-your-views/</guid><description>On Friday 6th August, Sarah announced that she was to conduct her own &amp;lsquo;Big Conversation&amp;rsquo; consultation with the residents of Brent East.
&amp;ldquo;Too many politicians think they know what&amp;rsquo;s best, without taking the time to listen to local people. I hope that Brent residents take the time to fill in the survey so that I can take up their issues both with the local Council as well as taking them up in Parliament.</description></item><item><title>Busy busy busy!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/busy-busy-busy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 16:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/busy-busy-busy/</guid><description>Yesterday was a busy day for this blog - 108 page loads for 81 unique vistors (of which, 15 were returning visitors). And no, those stats don&amp;rsquo;t include me. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite beat the 109 page loads for 66 unique vistors on the 16th of July.
Worth mentioning that several of the unique visitors originate from gsi.gov.uk &amp;amp; parliament.uk - From MPs?
A flurry of posts early this morning. I received an email notification of updates to the Brent East LD website.</description></item><item><title>Fair Trade is still a long way off</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/fair-trade-is-still-a-long-way-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 12:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/fair-trade-is-still-a-long-way-off/</guid><description>In an article published in Asian Voice on Tuesday 3rd, Sarah comments on the recent WTO trade talks and the floods in Bangladesh.
You can read it here.</description></item><item><title>Cleaning Up Brent</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/cleaning-up-brent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 12:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/cleaning-up-brent/</guid><description>I am pleased to see Sarah continuing to take action on the street furniture left behind following the privatisation and deregulation the telecoms industry.
Announcing her actions, Sarah said:
&amp;ldquo;Derelict phone boxes are an eyesore in Brent. Local residents are sick and tired of seeing them being used as rubbish bins, fly-poster sites and public toilets. I hope that local people show their frustration at these monstrosities by signing my petition.</description></item><item><title>Safer Neighbourhoods</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/safer-neighbourhoods/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 11:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/05/safer-neighbourhoods/</guid><description>On Monday, Sarah attended the launch of the Metropolitian Police Safer Neighbourhoods initiative in Kilburn.
First launched for the Stonebridge Estate in April this year, the program aims to provide new teams of uniformed officers working within communities to tackle quality-of-life issues and anti-social behaviour crimes.
Sarah commented that it was community policing that local people wanted. &amp;ldquo;Not only do they want more police on the streets, they want police officers who they know and trust.</description></item><item><title>What to do with ‘grot spots’ in Brent</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/04/what-to-do-with-grot-spots-in-brent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2004 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/04/what-to-do-with-grot-spots-in-brent/</guid><description>From what I can gather, there are two different options for reporting &amp;lsquo;grot spots&amp;rsquo; for action by the local authority.
You can report them to Sarah.
Or
You can report them direct to Brent Council&amp;rsquo;s Street Care Team.
For street sweeping, you can visit them online to report poor standards of cleanliness. The Street Care team promise they will be rectified within 24 hours. They will ensure that streets and roads are kept tidy, litter bins are emptied on a regular basis and to remove any dead animal from the highway within one hour of it being reported.</description></item><item><title>Moi?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/03/moi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2004 16:48:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/03/moi/</guid><description>Moi?
Well, JC thinks so.
I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can redeem myself over the next few days. Updates to follow&amp;hellip; .. .</description></item><item><title>HOWTO: blog for your MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/howto-blog-for-your-mp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2004 22:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/howto-blog-for-your-mp/</guid><description>Blog for your MP
Make your blog part of the solution, not part of the problem. This bit is important. Your already poking enough fun by running a blog on their behalf, riding google rankings and racking up page views when their site should be getting the traffic. And if you have some real deep-seated hatred for your MP, perhaps you ought to reconsider your motives for doing this. Part of the solution.</description></item><item><title>Ask...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/ask/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2004 17:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/ask/</guid><description>&amp;hellip; and you shall receive.
Tim, keep on keeping on.
To: yeot@parliament.uk, timyeomp@parliament.uk
Subject: Webloging by MPs
Good morning Mr Yeo,
You&amp;rsquo;re probably going to be reading a few of these messages today, so I thank you in advance for reading mine.
Can I just say that, for what it&amp;rsquo;s worth, I don&amp;rsquo;t think Mr Tim Ireland has been a very helpful chap with regards to the e-government agenda he has been pushing.</description></item><item><title>Blogging by/for MPs</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/blogging-byfor-mps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2004 16:19:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/29/blogging-byfor-mps/</guid><description>Following on from the Hansard Society report into UK Political Weblogs (PDF report here), the Guardian keeps the spotlight on this area with this story, basically encouraging MPs to get blogging.
There has been much said on this topic in blogsphere of late. And with good reason. So I&amp;rsquo;m not going to repeat it here.
But I would like to highlight a few bits of the Guardian article.
&amp;ldquo;Although the public might think otherwise, a lot of MPs do not have a great deal of money,&amp;rdquo; explains Ferguson.</description></item><item><title>Blogging MPs</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/27/blogging-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2004 23:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/27/blogging-mps/</guid><description>Some background
Some comment
Get a blog Sarah</description></item><item><title>Give me your grot spots!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/26/give-me-your-grot-spots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2004 00:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/26/give-me-your-grot-spots/</guid><description>38 days later&amp;hellip;.and the Brent LD website has been updated!
On Thursday it was announced that Sarah was urging her constituants to adviser her of &amp;ldquo;grot spots&amp;rdquo; in the locality. She promises &amp;ldquo;real action to tackle these problems&amp;rdquo;.
If Sarah was a blogger, she may have discovered the The Willesden Herald blog (delivering all the news that&amp;rsquo;s unfit to print). Over recent weeks, they have had photos of fly-tipping blocking roads around the area.</description></item><item><title>Spotted!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/16/spotted/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/16/spotted/</guid><description>Just not in Brent&amp;hellip;in Leicester.</description></item><item><title>Where is my MP?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/15/where-is-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 12:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/15/where-is-my-mp/</guid><description>Last update to Brent &amp;amp; Brent East Lib Dem website? June 14th
Last update to Sarah Teather&amp;rsquo;s website (which is, incidently, exactly the same static content as the B&amp;amp;BE LD website)? June 14th
So, it&amp;rsquo;s been over a month since Sarah or the Brent East Lib Dem&amp;rsquo;s updated their site. Is that because there is nothing to announce? And if so, just what has my MP been up to and where?</description></item><item><title>Question Time Last Night</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/09/question-time-last-night/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2004 16:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/09/question-time-last-night/</guid><description>Wow! What an informed and articulate audience! If there was ever an argument for extending suffrage to the 16-18 year old age group then last night&amp;rsquo;s broadcast proves it.
I would have blogged this live, but since the untimely demise of my iBook and the now elongated repair time from Apple I had to make notes old-school style with lead and tree fibre. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to capture Sarah&amp;rsquo;s point of view on the subjects raised and capture a few quotes.</description></item><item><title>BBC Question Time 8 July 2004</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/08/bbc-question-time-8-july-2004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2004 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/08/bbc-question-time-8-july-2004/</guid><description>BBC Question Time tonight features Sarah Teather MP, David Lammy MP; Minister for Constitutional Affairs, Boris Johnson; Shadow Arts Minister, Jimmy Carr; Comedian and Kat Fletcher; NUS President.
And I&amp;rsquo;ve not been offered tickets for the audience! Downer!</description></item><item><title>Campaign ‘Diary’ from Sarah Teather</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/05/campaign-diary-from-sarah-teather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2004 20:56:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/05/campaign-diary-from-sarah-teather/</guid><description>While this isn&amp;rsquo;t news in the current affairs sense, it&amp;rsquo;s relevent to the &amp;lsquo;online activism&amp;rsquo; of blogging for your MP. I found this on the Guardian website from the time of the Brent East By-election last year which took Sarah into Parliament.
While this isn&amp;rsquo;t news in the current affairs sense, it&amp;rsquo;s relevent to the &amp;lsquo;online activism&amp;rsquo; of blogging for your MP. I found this on the Guardian website from the time of the Brent East By-election last year which took Sarah into Parliament.</description></item><item><title>Response from Sarah Teather’s Office</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/05/response-from-sarah-teathers-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2004 17:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/05/response-from-sarah-teathers-office/</guid><description>Following up on those missing speeches&amp;hellip;
Dear Mr Dyke,
Thank you very much for your e-mail about the two debates that Sarah took part in the week before last.
You mentioned that you had looked on Hansard and Theyworkforyou.com for the debates but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find them. Both debates took place on Tuesday 22nd June in Westminster Hall, which is separate from the main chamber of the House of Commons. Speeches made in Westminster Hall are still recorded in Hansard but are in a different section, which might account for why you could not locate them in the online Hansard.</description></item><item><title>The missing speeches...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/the-missing-speeches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2004 16:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/the-missing-speeches/</guid><description>OK. After some further searching I found the speeches. Firstly, the reason I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the searches is that they were not made on the 1st of July as the news posts on the Brent &amp;amp; Brent East Lib Dem web site states and secondly, the speeches were made in adjournment debates in Westminster Hall, not in the House of Commons as the photographs would suggest.
So, updated with correct, relevent and contextual information, here is the Brent &amp;amp; Brent East Liberal Democrats &amp;lsquo;Content In Brief&amp;rsquo; for 2nd July 2004.</description></item><item><title>making the spoken word more informing...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/making-the-spoken-word-more-informing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2004 15:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/making-the-spoken-word-more-informing/</guid><description>OK. It&amp;rsquo;s great to have the Brent Liberal Democrat auto mailer tell me that a speech made by Sarah has been posted to their website. But this is the crazy-super-inter-highway-web-thingy! Here we can make things more informing, have greater detail and relevence. Online, you can hyperlink! So. In order to make OK. It&amp;rsquo;s great to have the Brent Liberal Democrat auto mailer tell me that a speech made by Sarah has been posted to their website.</description></item><item><title>when news isn’t news</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/when-news-isnt-news/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2004 14:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/03/when-news-isnt-news/</guid><description>Yesterday, the &amp;lsquo;Brent &amp;amp; Brent East Liberal Democrats team&amp;rsquo; automailer sent me a content update for their website.
Today&amp;rsquo;s content in brief from the Brent &amp;amp; Brent East Liberal Democrats web site: Articles posted to the site today:
Fighting Discrimination against Muslims by Sarah Teather in Hansard, speech by Sarah Teather MP in Houses of Parliament http://www.brentlibdems.org.uk/article.php?id=16 Teather Calls for Fairer Funding for Brent Schools by Sarah Teather MP in Hansard, speech by Sarah Teather in the House of Commons http://www.</description></item><item><title>Question Time on Thursday 8th July</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/02/question-time-on-thursday-8th-july/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 15:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/07/02/question-time-on-thursday-8th-july/</guid><description>Is a special edition of the program. It will be produced by the winners of the BBC Schools Question Time Challenge.
&amp;ldquo;Schools Question Time Challenge is a UK-wide scheme, supported by BT in association with the Institute for Citizenship and by the BBC, to help pupils develop their citizenship and communication skills by producing local School Question Time events.&amp;rdquo;
Along with the head of the National Union of Students, the panel will include Sarah Teather!</description></item><item><title>googling “sarah teather” this evening...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/23/googling-sarah-teather-this-evening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2004 02:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/23/googling-sarah-teather-this-evening/</guid><description>and within 6 days of starting, sarah teather is my mp is the second listing.</description></item><item><title>tom watson MP stopped by...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/23/tom-watson-mp-stopped-by/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2004 00:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/23/tom-watson-mp-stopped-by/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Bloggerheads is creating mayhem. Sarah Teather is my MP. She isn&amp;rsquo;t but you know what I mean&amp;rdquo;
Bloggerheads a.k.a. Tim Ireland began the &amp;lsquo;blog for your MP&amp;rsquo; crusade with his blog for Tim Yeo. I found out about Bloggerheads and TheyWorkForYou through a long chain of email lists, conventions, links and sites, that all started as a dinner meeting email follow-up from the loverly DH.
Is Bloggerheads &amp;ldquo;creating mayhem&amp;rdquo;?</description></item><item><title>i’m glad to see she’s consistant</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/17/im-glad-to-see-shes-consistant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 22:58:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/17/im-glad-to-see-shes-consistant/</guid><description>I checked out how sarah has voted on some recent key issues. She voted against the Higher Education Funding Bill and the Lords Amendment on Foundation Hospitals.
She also voted for votes for 16-year-olds, inline with her view that they should have sufferage extended to them.
Her views on post office closures are confirmed by her voting record and by her questioning of other MP&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>things sarah feels strongly about</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/17/things-sarah-feels-strongly-about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 21:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/17/things-sarah-feels-strongly-about/</guid><description>Read &amp;lsquo;Sarah&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rsquo; campaigns
Sarah thinks that the Council Tax is an unfair tax introduced by the Conservatives and made worse under Labour. Sarah wants to see the Council Tax scrapped and replaced with a fairer alternative based on a persons ability to pay.
Sarah wants the Government to scrap Tuition fees and abandon its plans for top-up fees. Sarah belives that university fees are an &amp;lsquo;unfair tax&amp;rsquo; on students.</description></item><item><title>googling “sarah teather” this afternoon</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/16/googling-sarah-teather-this-afternoon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 19:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/16/googling-sarah-teather-this-afternoon/</guid><description>and I found this priceless story! Sarah Teather MP, youngest in Parliment, caught and rebuked by the Speaker for making comic gestures!
More from LibDemWatch and Recess Monkey</description></item><item><title>blogging for my MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/16/blogging-for-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 15:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/16/blogging-for-my-mp/</guid><description>This is NOT the official weblog for Sarah Teather. This weblog is inspired by the grassroots activism and democratic advocacy of They Work For You Dot Com.
Read these articles by Tim Ireland for further information.
Why Politicians Need Weblogs
How To Run a Weblog on Behalf of Your MP</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather is my MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/15/sarah-teather-is-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/06/15/sarah-teather-is-my-mp/</guid><description>I live in the constituency of Brent East and I have the pleasure of being served in the House of Commons by Sarah Teather MP; the youngest member of parliment.</description></item></channel></rss>