<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Expenses on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/expenses/</link><description>Recent content in Expenses on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 18:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/expenses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More news from up Brent North</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/more-news-from-up-brent-north/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 18:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/more-news-from-up-brent-north/</guid><description>I met this chap while out on the Unlock Democracy / Hang-em rally this afternoon.
Barry Gardiner&amp;rsquo;s £198,500 dwarfs Dawn Butler&amp;rsquo;s £66,000 expenses claims.</description></item><item><title>Labour pay legal costs to Brent Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</guid><description>Brent councillor James Powney laments the threat and use of legal writ to silence debate, tending towards an environment where &amp;lsquo;legitimate freedom of speech could be restricted by self censorship.&amp;rsquo;
Legal writ has its strength though. When Brent Labour distributed a leaflet with false claims about Sarah Teather, the Brent Leb Dems took appropriate legal measures. In the face of the legal action, Labour have now admitted their story was false and agreed to pay the Lib Dems legal costs.</description></item><item><title>WB Times "Butler told to apologise"</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</guid><description>Brent&amp;rsquo;s Labour Group formal apology for issuing leaflets with defamatory claims about Sarah Teather is on page 4 of the WB Times this week.
Willesden and Brent Times, 23 April, 2010</description></item><item><title>Butler issues full apology for Teather expenses smear</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</guid><description>LibDem Voice has some news on Brent Centrals dirty politics.
Labour Minister Dawn Butler has issued a legal apology to Sarah Teather for calling her a hypocrite over MPs’ expenses. Butler made the accusation while the running of Sarah Teather’s office was under investigation. The Parliamentary Standards Commissioner later dropped the investigation because there were no grounds to suspect any wrongdoing by Ms Teather.
This issue came up at the MapRA Hustings on Monday night.</description></item><item><title>MP Sarah Cleared</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A letter of complaint against Sarah Teather was sent to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner, supposedly from a man at an address in Brent. Then a second letter of complaint was sent, again from this man, but giving a new address. However, this new address does not exist. There is a real address with the same house number and postcode (but different rest of address), at which there is one person on the electoral register – a woman who has the name of someone listed on Labour MP Dawn Butler’s register of interests as being a member of her staff.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Labour Team smear tactics....?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 18:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/03/25/mapesbury-labour-team-smear-tactics/</guid><description>In a recent letter to residents of the Mapesbury ward of Brent Central, Labours' candidate Angela Griggs slings a little mud on expenses. Apparently complains have been made to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner about Sarah Teathers' expenses in relation to her constituency office.
Now we know Sarah&amp;rsquo;s expenses are squeaky clean - check TWFY.com and compare the ACL to Dawn Butler and her £66,000&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Election Expenses</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/10/election-expenses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/10/election-expenses/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been digging around into the rules around election expenses. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to calculate the maximum permitted expenses a candidate or agent may incur in Brent East. Thankfully the Electoral Commission website is a wealth of information on electoral law and regulations.
Election expenses are those ‘expenses incurred whether before, during or after the election, on account of or in respect of the conduct or management of the election’. They may only be incurred by the candidate, his election agent or persons authorised in writing by that agent.</description></item></channel></rss>