<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Third Year on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/third-year/</link><description>Recent content in Third Year on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/third-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hacking the Networked Society.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/dissertation/essay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/dissertation/essay/</guid><description>Introduction. The dynamic between free-software and open-source is often misunderstood by social and political theorists. As a consequence it is also under-theorised within socio-political theory. In this paper, I show how philosophies of free/libre, open-source and commons regimes have engendered new forms of sociopolitical consumption and new political economies of meaning. My emphasis on the interplay between the local and the global/structure and agency, shows new ways of ‘thinking’ the cosmopolitan, sedimented in the interconnected networks of the technical age.</description></item><item><title>Critically discuss Appadurai’s theory of globalisation with reference to his idea of scapes.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/culture-globalisation-power/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/culture-globalisation-power/essay/</guid><description>Appadurai’s theory of globalisation stands out from the myriad of theories in a number of ways. First and foremost his theory of globalisation emphasises identity and perspective over institutions and nation-states, the spatial and temporal over the economic and political; in this sense Appardurai’s theory of globalisation is post-modern. Secondly, his approach is post-structural: Appadurai is challenging other models of social theory that are based on models of structure. Appadurai’s theory of globalisation goes beyond the usual dualisms of global/local relations with an account of the effect of deterritorialisation and global cultural flows on the construction of identity by individuals, ‘communities’ and that of the nation-state.</description></item><item><title>Do you agree with Hardt and Negri’s contention that we now live in the age of Empire?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/discourse-power-politics/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/discourse-power-politics/essay/</guid><description>My reading of Hardt and Negri’s Empire1 has taken me on a personal political journey. The text has provoked a critical examination of my own politics, bringing about a new consciousness of subject and sovereignty, of agency in a hyperglobalised world and of resistance to global capital. To a greater or lesser degree I do support Hardt and Negri’s contention that we now live in the age of Empire.
To justify my position of qualified agreement with these authors I will explore the following four broad themes that emerge from the work: global informational networked capitalism, of subject, sovereignty and supra-nationality, of biopolitical (re)production and of political agency for the authors’ subject of liberation, the multitude.</description></item><item><title>Evaluate the contemporary relevance of Schmitt’s conception of ‘the political’.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/beyond-all-reason/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/beyond-all-reason/essay/</guid><description>Schmitt’s stark conception of ‘the political’ serves to remind us of two significant yet often neglected aspects of political philosophy. Firstly, Schmitt’s conception of the political draws our attention to the establishment and membership of a political community; who is outside our group, why, and what the relationship to outsiders is. Secondly, and most crucially, Schmitt reminds us that the methods of politics are contestable, that ‘the political’ is not bound within any manifestation of ideologies, institutions and mechanisms.</description></item><item><title>To what extent do social, p2p or participatory financial models democratise capital?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/new-radical-politicial-economy/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/new-radical-politicial-economy/essay/</guid><description>“What matters in the world is money, machines and people, in that order. Our political task is to reverse the order.” Keith Hart1
The long established savings and loan institutions are criticised at every point, from the financial models that they operate down to their de-personalised, off-shore call-centres. My argument in this paper is that banking services are anti-social, hierarchical and intensely private. These traditional banking services are, I contend, inherently undemocratic, even anti-democratic at the extremes.</description></item><item><title>“There is no such thing as a ‘communitarian’ critique of liberalism for such ‘critiques’ are in reality only expressions of liberal dissatisfaction with the excesses of liberal individualism”</title><link>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/liberalism-critics/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/ba-politics/liberalism-critics/essay/</guid><description>After an eleven year absence, the manifestation of all that was 1990s Girl Power, the Spice Girls, reformed recently for a world tour. Once again the emancipatory message of ‘girl power’ and the undefinable yet absolutely essential ‘zig-a-zig-ah’ was heard blasting out of stadiums. Although this time to much smaller, and now older audiences. The tour was cut short due to ‘personal reasons.’ In the course of this paper it will become clearer why the Spice Girls, ‘girl power’ and ‘zig-a-zig-ah’ are apt cultural references to begin a paper on political theory.</description></item></channel></rss>