<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Third Year on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/third-year/</link><description>Recent content in Third Year on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/third-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hacking the Networked Society.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/dissertation/essay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/dissertation/essay/</guid><description>This is my dissertation from my BA Politics back in 2008.
Introduction. The dynamic between free-software and open-source is often misunderstood by social and political theorists. As a consequence it is also under-theorised within socio-political theory. In this paper, I show how philosophies of free/libre, open-source and commons regimes have engendered new forms of sociopolitical consumption and new political economies of meaning. My emphasis on the interplay between the local and the global/structure and agency, shows new ways of ‘thinking’ the cosmopolitan, sedimented in the interconnected networks of the technical age.</description></item><item><title>Critically discuss Appadurai’s theory of globalisation with reference to his idea of scapes.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/culture-globalisation-power/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/culture-globalisation-power/essay/</guid><description>I wrote this essay in my third-year of my BA Politics, back in 2008. The module was Culture, Globalisation and Power, taught by Adrian Sledmere
Appadurai’s theory of globalisation stands out from the myriad of theories in a number of ways. First and foremost his theory of globalisation emphasises identity and perspective over institutions and nation-states, the spatial and temporal over the economic and political; in this sense Appardurai’s theory of globalisation is post-modern.</description></item><item><title>Do you agree with Hardt and Negri’s contention that we now live in the age of Empire?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/discourse-power-politics/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/discourse-power-politics/essay/</guid><description>I wrote this essay in my third-year of my BA Politics, back in 2008. The module was Discourse, Power, Politics, taught by Dr Saul Newman
My reading of Hardt and Negri’s Empire1 has taken me on a personal political journey. The text has provoked a critical examination of my own politics, bringing about a new consciousness of subject and sovereignty, of agency in a hyperglobalised world and of resistance to global capital.</description></item><item><title>Evaluate the contemporary relevance of Schmitt’s conception of ‘the political’.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/beyond-all-reason/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/beyond-all-reason/essay/</guid><description>I wrote this essay in my third-year of my BA Politics, back in 2008. The module was Beyond All Reason, taught by Dr James Martin
Schmitt’s stark conception of ‘the political’ serves to remind us of two significant yet often neglected aspects of political philosophy. Firstly, Schmitt’s conception of the political draws our attention to the establishment and membership of a political community; who is outside our group, why, and what the relationship to outsiders is.</description></item><item><title>To what extent do social, p2p or participatory financial models democratise capital?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/new-radical-politicial-economy/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/new-radical-politicial-economy/essay/</guid><description>I wrote this essay in my third-year of my BA Politics, back in 2008. The module was New Radical Political Economy, taught by Dr Derek Wall.
“What matters in the world is money, machines and people, in that order. Our political task is to reverse the order.” Keith Hart1
The long established savings and loan institutions are criticised at every point, from the financial models that they operate down to their de-personalised, off-shore call-centres.</description></item><item><title>“There is no such thing as a ‘communitarian’ critique of liberalism for such ‘critiques’ are in reality only expressions of liberal dissatisfaction with the excesses of liberal individualism”</title><link>https://robdyke.com/posts/liberalism-critics/essay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/posts/liberalism-critics/essay/</guid><description>I wrote this essay in my third-year of my BA Politics, back in 2008. The module was Liberalism and its Critics, taught by Prof Sanjay Seth
After an eleven year absence, the manifestation of all that was 1990s Girl Power, the Spice Girls, reformed recently for a world tour. Once again the emancipatory message of ‘girl power’ and the undefinable yet absolutely essential ‘zig-a-zig-ah’ was heard blasting out of stadiums.</description></item></channel></rss>