<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Goldsmiths on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/goldsmiths/</link><description>Recent content in Goldsmiths on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 22:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/goldsmiths/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>dissertation project - submitted and now online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/21/dissertation-project-submitted-and-now-online/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 22:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/21/dissertation-project-submitted-and-now-online/</guid><description>Hacking the Networked Society.
Abstract: The dynamic between free-software and open-source is often misunderstood by social and political theorists. As a consequence it is also under-theorised within socio-political theory. In this paper, I show how philosophies of free/libre, open-source and commons regimes have engendered new forms of socio-political consumption and new political economies of meaning. My emphasis on the interplay between the local and the global/structure and agency, shows new ways of &amp;lsquo;thinking&amp;rsquo; the cosmopolitan, sedimented in the interconnected networks of the technical age.</description></item><item><title>self-publishing of recent essays</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/20/self-publishing-of-recent-essays/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/20/self-publishing-of-recent-essays/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve converted some of my recent papers into web pages for easy reading online. I hope that others find them of some use, if only for the bibliographies!
Here is my New Radical Political Economy paper on social, peer-to-peer, participatory financial models. In the paper I contrast traditional banks and interest bearing capital transactions to these emergent models. Here is the web HTML version, and this is the PDF version for download.</description></item><item><title>new radical political economy</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/04/13/new-radical-political-economy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/04/13/new-radical-political-economy/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished a paper on social, peer-to-peer, participatory financial models. In the paper I contrast traditional banks and interest bearing capital transactions to these emergent models. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at three different examples of these new business models, Zopa, Kiva and Open Capital, considering to what extent these organisations are challenging established practices.
The full paper is available as a PDF. As soon as I&amp;rsquo;ve got my LaTeX/HTML conversion working I&amp;rsquo;ll post that too.</description></item><item><title>dissertation book print project</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-book-print-project/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 15:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-book-print-project/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been investigating the feasibility of collecting and publishing final year dissertation projects in book form. I think that this will make a great reminder of our time of study, our political alliances and the friendships that have grown over the years at Goldsmiths. Also it&amp;rsquo;s such an indulgent, gratuitous act: So Fucking Goldsmiths. My plan is to gather together our dissertations and publish a book (ISBN record and everything) of our works to have it printed and ready for graduation in September.</description></item><item><title>dissertation project - reviewed and replanned</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-project-reviewed-and-replanned/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 15:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-project-reviewed-and-replanned/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy reviewing and replanning my dissertation project - only five weeks to go until hand-in! I&amp;rsquo;ve cut a lot out since my proposal last year, tightening my focus and shortening my reading lists. My four papers now look something like this&amp;hellip;
Who Governs in a Networked Society (final draft complete) - My first chapter is concerned with the depoliticisation of government and the politicisation of the social world in a global networked society.</description></item><item><title>ULU Elects!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/27/ulu-elects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 11:25:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/27/ulu-elects/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to suffer election fatigue what with GCSU, America, shortly London and ULU as well. Well damm representative governance, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say.
ULU do get several points awarded for a sensible and secure electronic voting mechanism. You can vote from this page, online and confidentialy, assuming that you have got a username and password that have been emailed to your ULU College Email account.
How did they do such a thing you may ask&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Some colleges in the UoL will provide ULU with a database of the students who are eligible to vote in the elections from that college.</description></item><item><title>How I would have rigged the Goldsmiths College Student Elections...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/26/how-i-would-have-rigged-the-goldsmiths-college-student-elections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 10:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/26/how-i-would-have-rigged-the-goldsmiths-college-student-elections/</guid><description>&lt;p>How I would have rigged the Goldsmiths College Student Elections and some recommendations for the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are many ways of rigging an election and, with increased abstraction and dispersal of the act of voting, influencing the outcome of ballots gets easier and easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s just think for a moment what takes place when a student votes. First of all, the student needs to be co-present with the ballot! This is a given and the only part of the process that can not be virtualised. The student presents some ID before being given a ballot paper. The ballot is privately completed and cast into the ballot box.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Goldsmiths College Students Election e-Voting was extremely vulnerable to exploitation by someone with malicious intent. The e-voting mechanism virtualised the ballot paper instead of virtualising the whole process. Anyone visiting the goldsmithsstudents.com website was able to download a Microsoft Word file. This file used a macro to capture the input of the user; in this case the ranking of the preference of candidates. A student was expected to complete the form, save it, then send the file as an attachment from their college email account to &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;a href="mailto:su@gold.ac.uk">su@gold.ac.uk&lt;/a>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The most vulnerable part of the whole process is that &lt;strong>single file&lt;/strong> made available for public download.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>On puting the effort in...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/25/on-puting-the-effort-in/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 12:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/25/on-puting-the-effort-in/</guid><description>By the Gods! There are but weeks remaining for the third year politics students. Next significant deadline is the 13th March, the hand-in for New Radical Political Economy (NRPE) and Liberalism and Its Critics. I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished my NRPE paper, &amp;lsquo;To what extent do social, peer-to-peer and participatory models democratise capital&amp;rsquo;, so this week I&amp;rsquo;ll be devoting to my Dissertation project which has received somewhere between little and no attention since I wrote my proposal back in October&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>goldsmiths in conflict over twinning campaigns</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/goldsmiths-in-conflict-over-twinning-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 21:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/goldsmiths-in-conflict-over-twinning-campaigns/</guid><description>&lt;p>How many twins can one university have? If Goldsmiths SU passes all of the resolutions before it on conjoining in solidarity with another university it&amp;rsquo;ll have a hard time buying trousers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some would have Goldsmiths twin with a university in Palestine and have campaigned tirelessly for 18 months. Others would see Goldsmiths twin with an Israeli institution and have brought out the votes to defeat motions in the past. Both condemn the other for their solidarity, their morality (or lack of it), their inequity&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Both sides seek absolute right and the destruction of the other&amp;hellip; A grotesque caricature of only the most extreme elements of the conflict on which they hope to have some bearing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>current efforts</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/current-efforts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/current-efforts/</guid><description>Plenty of keyboard time coming up over the next few weeks&amp;hellip;
The dissertation project continues: are radical openness of f/los communities embodying resistance to Empire? My proposal was graded at 8/10 &amp;hellip; must be doing something right. Now to maintain that effort!
Also researching a paper on social. p2p and participatory financial models with specific reference to banking systems. Zopa, Kiva and Open Capital are my case studies. Meeting with the CFO of Zopa tomorrow!</description></item><item><title>Beyond All Reason</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/14/beyond-all-reason/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 00:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/14/beyond-all-reason/</guid><description>&lt;p>Well&amp;hellip; today was last day of term for two @smiths courses: Beyond All Reason and Culture, Globalisation and Power.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished &lt;a href="http://www.robdyke.com/wikwikwah/index.php/Beyond_All_Reason" title="Rob Dyke Wiki">uploading all my Beyond All Reason&lt;/a> mindmaps&amp;hellip; use with caution&amp;hellip;. Click on for some links&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Prime Minister's Lunch</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/the-prime-ministers-lunch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 12:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/the-prime-ministers-lunch/</guid><description>Live on Wired! The PML!</description></item><item><title>goldsmiths wiki</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/goldsmiths-wiki/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/goldsmiths-wiki/</guid><description>@smiths now has wiki space at a cost of around £2000 for the software licenses (1).
Wiki&amp;rsquo;s, along with blogs, are a prominent feature of the contemporary easy to read, easy to edit web. The term wiki is derived from the Hawaiian word for quick. Wiki&amp;rsquo;s are websites that are quick and easy to contribute to and to edit. The software purchased, Confluence, is merely an implementation of the wiki idea, corporatised, privatised and packaged up as an &amp;lsquo;enterprise level collaboration tool&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>@smiths... the student staff forum.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/smiths-the-student-staff-forum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 00:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/12/05/smiths-the-student-staff-forum/</guid><description>&lt;p>I should be I should be writing about Appadurai&amp;rsquo;s theory of globalisation, but I wanted to write about the student staff forum meeting I attended today more&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;p>The program monitoring program at goldsmiths has recently changed to a new model. This arrangement uses online tools to compliment the traditional Course Rep role to set an agenda for a number of meetings over the course of the college year between the academic staff and the students. As a Program Monitoring Rep I was at the first of the meetings today.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There was an agenda. These are my reflections on that meeting. Disclaimer. I would probably say all of the following again. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make it anything more than my opinion. The official minutes may more accurately reflect actual events. Mileage may vary. Terms and Conditions Apply. Offers not available to those outside the EU.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>extending `smiths library services</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/10/23/extending-smiths-library-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2007 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/10/23/extending-smiths-library-services/</guid><description>&lt;p>Goldsmiths SU has successfully campaigned for changes in the opening hours of the colleges library and ICT facilities. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in exploring what other ways the information that is stored in the library building can opened up to the benefit of students and staff alike. I&amp;rsquo;m not so much speaking about new things that the library can do, rather I am interested in ways in which existing services and resources could be linked up, extending their use.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Currently recommendations for reading / viewing / listening are distributed to students as files to download from &lt;a href="http://learn.gold.ac.uk" title="Goldsmiths Virtual Learnign Environment website">learn.gold.ac.uk&lt;/a> (which we usually print) or in hard copy (which we then annotate). Students then navigate to the library website to find out whether a given publication is &lt;em>even available&lt;/em>, and what its shelfmark is.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, there is the potential to make the process of recommending, finding, borrowing and even commenting on the value and relevance of a particular library resource more seamless by linking-up the library website and learn.gold site.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>study tools</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/10/23/study-tools/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2007 22:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/10/23/study-tools/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve invested a lot of time in researching and testing tools to support my studies. i wanted to to break away from so-called &amp;lsquo;productivity tools&amp;rsquo;, as in all my years of using software like Visio, Word, Outlook, I&amp;rsquo;ve never really been productive: too much of my time and effort has been wasted in taming the application, or repeated manually generating my desired formatting - perhaps counter-productivity tools would be more accurate.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m in my third year of studying for a BA. I&amp;rsquo;m researching my subjects and my ideas, reading lots, annotating my reading, working on assignments, editing and revising my work. I work in different locations and at different times and I want access to my work where and whenever I am. As such, a piece of hardware, a laptop or a pda is not the whole answer to these needs, I need software to support my study too.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>bring on the tools.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>E-Benchmarking for Goldsmiths CELT</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/e-benchmarking-for-goldsmiths-celt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/e-benchmarking-for-goldsmiths-celt/</guid><description>Towards the end of term at Goldsmiths I participated in a huge number of half-baked surveys and poorly designed questionnaires. Still, that&amp;rsquo;s my own fault for saying &amp;lsquo;Yes&amp;rsquo; to all the last minute BA Sociology / Psychology students, desperate to get some data to evaluate for their assignments. The E-benchmarking survey for CELT, on the other hand, was a focused piece of qualitative research using interviews with students to benchmark e-learning activity at Goldsmiths.</description></item><item><title>Goldsmiths Debating Society</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/01/30/goldsmiths-debating-society/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2007 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/01/30/goldsmiths-debating-society/</guid><description>There is talk about resurecting the &amp;lsquo;Smiths Debating Society&amp;hellip; check out the wiki and add yourself if you are interested in this.</description></item><item><title>political firsts...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/01/30/political-firsts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2007 12:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/01/30/political-firsts/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m interested in starting an e-journal of politics essays written by Goldsmiths students - want to help make it happen? The only requirement for publishing being that the essay received a First when marked. Publishing would be under the Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike License. Drop me an email at my goldsmiths account (ss601rd@&amp;hellip;) or leave comments here.</description></item><item><title>And relax....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2004 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</guid><description>And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)
Been busy. Enrolled on BA Politics Economic and Public Policy at Goldsmiths University. Getting my teeth stuck in. Substantial stuff. Satisfying.
And then there is [And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)</description></item></channel></rss>