<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>open data on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/open-data/</link><description>Recent content in open data on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 15:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/open-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>recently reading "The Liberty of the Networked" at oD</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/18/recently-reading-the-liberty-of-the-networked-at-od/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 15:59:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/18/recently-reading-the-liberty-of-the-networked-at-od/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been following Tony Curzon-Price&amp;rsquo;s essay The Liberty of the Networked (and part 2 and part 3) published over at the excellent openDemocracy.net to coincide in with The Convention on Modern Liberty to be held in London and across the UK on February 28th. Tony&amp;rsquo;s paper considers the social role of technology with regards to political thought and activity, comparing the liberty of the Ancients with the liberty of the Moderns to discover the liberty of the Networked.</description></item><item><title>Show Us a Better Way and Free Our Bills</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/13/show-us-a-better-way-and-free-our-bills/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/13/show-us-a-better-way-and-free-our-bills/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy fortnight for open-information projects and campaigns. Widely announced and re-announced were the winners of the Show Us A Better Way (SUABW) competition, sponsored by the Government, which sought new solutions to perhaps unknown problems. SUABW asked people what web-based tools they would build from public data-sources that would improve the way public information is shared and presented.
The winners are:
Can I Recycle It? UK Cycling Catchment Areas Location of Postboxes Loofinder The BBC PM report referred to a court case being thrown out because a piece of law that the case was built on had been taken off the statute book.</description></item><item><title>MySociety's 'Free Our Bills' campaign</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/mysocietys-free-our-bills-campaign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 15:02:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/mysocietys-free-our-bills-campaign/</guid><description>Today I&amp;rsquo;ve accessed three different MySociety websites: TheyWorkForYou, WriteToThem and WhatDoTheyKnow. I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;d do without these powerful tools: MySociety are indespensible and we&amp;rsquo;d all miss them if they weren&amp;rsquo;t here.
I was using WriteToThem to contact Sarah Teather to urge her to support Early Day Motion (EDM) 2141 that her parliamentary colleague Jo Swinson has tabled.
 FREE OUR BILLS CAMPAIGN, 22.07.2008, Swinson, Jo
That this House believes it has a duty to publish Bills in such a fashion that they can be accessed as easily and as early as possible by the public; notes that the non-partisan Free Our Bills campaign is urging the House to publish bill texts in a new electronic format to improve accessibility and public scrutiny of legislation; further notes that the changes requested would have no impact on the content of Bills, nor upon the process by which they are currently made; considers that the new format could be delivered cheaply and quickly; acknowledges that the Leader of the House&amp;rsquo;s office did not accept a prior request for new formatting from mySociety, nor provide an explanation of why the changes could be made; and calls on the Leader of House to ask House of Commons Clerks to work with Free Our Bills campaign staff to commence publication of Bills in the new format.</description></item></channel></rss>