<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stop the War on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/stop-the-war/</link><description>Recent content in Stop the War on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 21:07:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/stop-the-war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>goldsmiths in conflict over twinning campaigns</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/goldsmiths-in-conflict-over-twinning-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 21:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/goldsmiths-in-conflict-over-twinning-campaigns/</guid><description>&lt;p>How many twins can one university have? If Goldsmiths SU passes all of the resolutions before it on conjoining in solidarity with another university it&amp;rsquo;ll have a hard time buying trousers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some would have Goldsmiths twin with a university in Palestine and have campaigned tirelessly for 18 months. Others would see Goldsmiths twin with an Israeli institution and have brought out the votes to defeat motions in the past. Both condemn the other for their solidarity, their morality (or lack of it), their inequity&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Both sides seek absolute right and the destruction of the other&amp;hellip; A grotesque caricature of only the most extreme elements of the conflict on which they hope to have some bearing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Catch your MP...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/13/catch-your-mp.../</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/13/catch-your-mp.../</guid><description>The film of the Brent East STW hustings is one of a number of films documenting the views of Prospective Parliamentary Candidates on the aggressive action taken against Iraq. The Catch Your MP project aims to hold to account the 412 Members of the 2001-2005 Parliament that voted in support of military action.
Candidates for Brent East: Shahrar, Sarah, Yasmin, Kwasi and George along with Rocky (Wasn&amp;rsquo;t that a Rainbow cast?</description></item><item><title>I wish I'd seen this earlier...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/12/i-wish-id-seen-this-earlier.../</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/12/i-wish-id-seen-this-earlier.../</guid><description>Trawling through the list of refering links to this site I came across a search engine, A9.com, that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard of. I followed the link to discover where this blog was ranked on the list that refered the reader to the blog. Just below the link to this blog was a link to Film Makers Against War.
I wish I&amp;rsquo;d seen the film made of the Brent East Stop The War Hustings earlier.</description></item></channel></rss>