<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gladstone Park on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/gladstone-park/</link><description>Recent content in Gladstone Park on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 17:43:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/gladstone-park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GPCC 'Wordles'</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/12/06/gpcc-wordles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 17:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/12/06/gpcc-wordles/</guid><description>Here are two wordles created from the feedback on the GPCC launch event speaker feedback forms and the group activities from the afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Gladstone Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/07/25/gladstone-park/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2010 16:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/07/25/gladstone-park/</guid><description>A new website for the Gladstone Park Consultative Committee at http://www.gladstonepark.org.uk. Update your bookmarks.</description></item><item><title>Alice in Wonderland</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/06/20/alice-in-wonderland/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 13:41:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/06/20/alice-in-wonderland/</guid><description>The Madhatters Theatre Club present Alice in Wonderland.
See www.modproductions.org.uk</description></item><item><title>Dollis Hill House renewal project in jeopardy</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/10/dollis-hill-house-renewal-project-in-jeopardy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 09:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/10/dollis-hill-house-renewal-project-in-jeopardy/</guid><description>News earlier this year was that the Heritage Lottery Fund announced stage 1 funding towards a grant of £1.2 million to help restore Dollis Hill House. This would have enabled Dollis Hill House Trust (DHHT) to work with Training For Life and Brent Council to annex a section of a public park for pseudo-social-enterprise, or, in the words of the DHH, to bring about the &amp;ldquo;commercial exploitation of the house’s prime and dramatic location, balanced with a positive vision of the house’s future as a cohesive focus for the growing and increasingly diverse population of the surrounding area.</description></item><item><title>Dollis Hill House</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/dollis-hill-house/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 20:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/19/dollis-hill-house/</guid><description>I spend a lot of time in Gladstone Park and I&amp;rsquo;ve recently taken an interest in the state of Dollis Hill House. I think that the kindest word to describe the building is &amp;lsquo;wreak&amp;rsquo;. There are plans (there are always plans) to restore the house from the Dollis Hill House Trust in partnership with Training For Life. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what they are in detail&amp;hellip; but the appear to involve getting a whole bunch of money together to renovate the building into a venue of some kind - better than flats&amp;hellip; no worse than demolition.</description></item></channel></rss>