<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conservatives on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/conservatives/</link><description>Recent content in Conservatives on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/conservatives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>While I was out....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out..../</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out..../</guid><description/></item><item><title>Local Torys ready for an election.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/local-torys-ready-for-an-election./</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 14:29:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/local-torys-ready-for-an-election./</guid><description>Torys care for mapesbury! Is the exclamation mark is necessary? Well, I&amp;rsquo;m as surprised as they are, so I guess so!
On the back, Brent Conservatives ask Mapesbury residents how they would vote IF there was a general election in the next few months&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; Someone ought to let Sachin Rajput know that he&amp;rsquo;s on the list for Thursday.
Picked up on Mora Road on Monday. Uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Hampstead and Kilburn</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/hampstead-and-kilburn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 21:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/hampstead-and-kilburn/</guid><description>Liberal Democrat candidate Ed Fordham needs just 474 votes to win the seat from Glenda Jackson. Driving through QP this afternoon I saw lots of Labour posters and flags with only a few Lib Dem orange diamonds. Looks like there is mroe work for the Lib Dem team to do there. The Torys had just a single board - just like the solitary piece of literature I found from them today.</description></item><item><title>Brent Conservatives leave the office - SHOCK!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/brent-conservatives-leave-the-office-shock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 16:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/brent-conservatives-leave-the-office-shock/</guid><description>I was emailed a copy of the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Conservative Action Team campaign materials yesterday. Arwh, they are so smiley! not meanleanbusinessy-looking like some of the candidates in their campaign materials. So friendly looking I almost misstook them for the Greens!
Anyway&amp;hellip; The photos, I noticed, were all taken in the Brent Conservatives office on Walm Lane. No ward walking for this lot! Where others have posed mid-reporting-a-local-grot-spot (sorry Sarah), the QPCAT (!</description></item><item><title>find the Torys online (update)</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/find-the-torys-online-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/find-the-torys-online-update/</guid><description>After bumping into one of the Dudden Hill Tory candidates last friday I now have the correct website for the Brent Conservatives. The link has been added to the sidebar. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep the old link up as it is the link that the official Conservative Party website links to - when they update, so will I.
An update to this post.</description></item><item><title>meeting Jack Sayers</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/meeting-jack-sayers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/meeting-jack-sayers/</guid><description>I was sitting out my step, enjoying a smoke in the evening air, when Jack Sayers walks up the drive out on the campaign trail delivering leafets. Jack has been a Councillor since 1990 so he is looking to be returned for the fourth time by this ward. The leaflet introduces us to the other two Conservative candidates, Khalid dar and Jennifer Brown.
Speaking of police&amp;hellip; The Conservatives leafet compares the size of the Safer Neighbourhood teams in Conservative run Barnet Council to Labour run Brent.</description></item><item><title>Queen's Park Tower Plan</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</guid><description>The proposal for the tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park is a lead topic for each of the parties contesting the electoral ward of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. For Labour it is getting like the Monty Python topic not to be mentioned in front of our hosts for the World Cup. The Lib Dems have made great gains from this thread - well, a sitting (yet not restanding) Councillor defected to Team Yellow with the tower plan as a key issue.</description></item><item><title>Brent Conservatives Unavailable?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/brent-conservatives-unavailable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 07:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/brent-conservatives-unavailable/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to contact the websites of the Brent East Conservatives and Kwasi Kwarteng. I know they were available during the General Election last year but now they are uncontactable&amp;hellip;
kwasi kwarteng www com
and
Brent East Conservatives unavailable dot com</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Conservatives</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-conservatives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-conservatives/</guid><description>When I met Kwasi on Thursday at the MapRA AGM I mentioned to him that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen any campaign materials from him over the last couple of weeks. Yesterday an Election Communiation from Brent East Conservatives was delivered by Royal Mail.
His message: &amp;lsquo;The Conservatives are the alternative. I promise to give you, the electorate, my boss, more for your money. This isn&amp;rsquo;t some form of magic. Our policies are based on common sense.</description></item></channel></rss>