<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wifi on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/wifi/</link><description>Recent content in wifi on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2004 09:29:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New nodes increasing coverage... technology solutions for members... problems with banking...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/12/13/new-nodes-increasing-coverage-technology-solutions-for-members-problems-with-banking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2004 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/12/13/new-nodes-increasing-coverage-technology-solutions-for-members-problems-with-banking/</guid><description>The occasional blogging of the growth of a wireless community.
New nodes increasing coverage&amp;hellip; technology solutions for members&amp;hellip; problems with banking&amp;hellip;
New nodes.
We&amp;rsquo;ve installed two further nodes in the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park area; Donaldson Road and Hopefield Avenue. Coverage in these locals will be strong and we&amp;rsquo;ll be getting in touch with all those in the area who have sent us expressions of interest to advise them that the service is available.</description></item><item><title>So it’s December already...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/12/08/so-its-december-already/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2004 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/12/08/so-its-december-already/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s the point of blogging if I don&amp;rsquo;t blog? How occasionally can I blog and still be a blogger? I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy. Very busy. My two full time jobs have been demanding of late - Comwifinet needed a liberal application of the hands in order to site two further antenna in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. Coverage extends and the network continues to grow - albeit slowly.
At each encounter with &amp;lsquo;the system&amp;rsquo;, Comwifinet are being delayed.</description></item><item><title>Progressing, developing, growing</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/progressing-developing-growing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2004 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/progressing-developing-growing/</guid><description>The QPWC is live.
We are currently working on the final few elements of the club formation and then all you prospective members can start signing up.
The equipment used to connect home desktop PC&amp;rsquo;s will be arriving with Comwifinet early next week, along with the hardware for more network nodes to increase coverage and quality of service in area.
Also, a colaborative self-assistance forum will go live early next week.</description></item><item><title>And relax....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2004 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/22/and-relax/</guid><description>And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)
Been busy. Enrolled on BA Politics Economic and Public Policy at Goldsmiths University. Getting my teeth stuck in. Substantial stuff. Satisfying.
And then there is [And breath in&amp;hellip;
So. I last had something to &amp;lsquo;show and tell&amp;rsquo; over a month ago (and that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly big or clever&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title>News from the launch</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/16/news-from-the-launch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2004 09:43:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/16/news-from-the-launch/</guid><description>Feeed Pro, our technology partners, posted a news article on the launch of the QPWC. You can read it here</description></item><item><title>Launched!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/14/launched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 10:28:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/14/launched/</guid><description>The Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Wireless Club launched on Sunday at the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Day.
http://www.queenspark.me.uk
And now comwifinet is live too&amp;hellip;
http://www.comwifinet.com
Updates to Sarah Teather Is My MP coming this week - she&amp;rsquo;s been busy; I&amp;rsquo;ve gotta catch up.</description></item><item><title>Getting yourself online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/14/getting-yourself-online/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 10:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/14/getting-yourself-online/</guid><description>Order a beer from the Salusbury, maybe a slice of pizza from the deli, or take a seat with an eat from Baker and Spice&amp;hellip;
Open your laptop. Power up your PDA.
Set up your WiFi connection. The name (SSID) of the QPWC network is &amp;lsquo;COMWIFINET&amp;rsquo; (there are a few additional characters, but you&amp;rsquo;ll see it).
Open your web browser and got to a website. You&amp;rsquo;ll get redirected to a splash screen showing a login.</description></item><item><title>And now you’re live!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/13/and-now-youre-live/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2004 16:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/09/13/and-now-youre-live/</guid><description>The Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Wireless Club (QPWC - to not tire my fingers) went LIVE this weekend, lanuching the community wireless broadband network at Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Day.
And what a day! A great response from people at the event. We&amp;rsquo;re now working to follow-up with all those that we spoke to, to provide answers to FAQ&amp;rsquo;s on the website and to increase the coverage of the network to provide access to more people.</description></item><item><title>Something to show and tell.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/something-to-show-and-tell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2004 08:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/27/something-to-show-and-tell/</guid><description>Blogging has been light this last week or so. I&amp;rsquo;ve been very occupied with my current projects.
Holiday next week, returning on the 9th. Project launch on 12th. Hope to get near a keyboard afterwards.</description></item><item><title>A sneek preview</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/26/a-sneek-preview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2004 10:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/26/a-sneek-preview/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s not being promoted yet, but those of you who read this blog can get a sneek preview of the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Wireless Club website.</description></item><item><title>Queen’s Park Wireless Club</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/22/queens-park-wireless-club/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 12:55:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/22/queens-park-wireless-club/</guid><description>Queen’s Park Wireless Club
Exists to further the development of a wireless network in the area of Queen’s Park, London NW6. The community owned Queen’s Park Wireless Club is simply intended to facilitate non-profit-making digital media and sharing of common services by subscribing members at very high (broadband) speeds (to mean in excess of 10,000 Kbits/sec). The network exists for the purposes of connecting the community and sharing resources together for the benefit of all in the locality.</description></item><item><title>Queens Park Open Day</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/17/queens-park-open-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2004 09:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/17/queens-park-open-day/</guid><description>On September 12th, comwifinet will be demonstrating Wireless Broadband Internet access at the Queens Park Open Day.
Come and experience wirefree!</description></item><item><title>What’s Happening?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/16/whats-happening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2004 17:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/08/16/whats-happening/</guid><description>A Wireless Broadband Network for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park.
A local community group are forming a club to create a wireless broadband network in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. The Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Wireless Club aims to facilitate non-profit-making digital media and sharing of common services by subscribing members at very high (broadband) speeds to a wireless network.
We need your input! If you are a local individual, business, school, centre, group, or charity, [A Wireless Broadband Network for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park.</description></item></channel></rss>