<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>healthcare.gov on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/healthcare.gov/</link><description>Recent content in healthcare.gov on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 17:49:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/healthcare.gov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>dissecting a major Govt IT project to deliver a political objective</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2013/11/05/dissecting-a-major-govt-it-project-to-deliver-a-political-objective/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 17:49:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2013/11/05/dissecting-a-major-govt-it-project-to-deliver-a-political-objective/</guid><description>&lt;p>Some notes taken on observing people the other side of the pond dissecting a major Govt IT project to deliver a political objective.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Would this project have benefited from &lt;a href="http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-10-16/open-source-everything-the-moral-of-the-healthcare-dot-gov-debacle">Opensorcery&lt;/a>? If PPACA wasn&amp;rsquo;t communist enough! Writing in Bloomberg Businessweek, Paul Ford explains that the debacle known as &lt;a href="https://www.healthcare.gov/">healthcare.gov&lt;/a> makes clear that it is time for government to change the way it delivers IT: embrace the open source approach to software development that has revolutionized the technology industry. Well, openness worked before for Obama e.g. with the &lt;a href="https://www.itdashboard.gov/">IT spending dashboard&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://sourceforge.net/projects/it-dashboard/">code here&lt;/a>) but that was in the first years of the first term. You can do &lt;strong>anything&lt;/strong> in that period of a presidency.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Looking at the Congressional hearing (which makes our &lt;a href="http://www.publications.parliament.uk/pa/cm201314/cmselect/cmpubacc/294/29402.htm">PAC look rather tame on NPfIT&lt;/a>) as &lt;a href="http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/oct/24/obamacare-website-testify-congress-live">reported by Grauniad&lt;/a> two lessons stand out for me. One technical, the other political.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From a technical perspective the importance of proving an end-to-end test FIRST and n&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SuzyKhimm/statuses/393392886965747712">ot two weeks prior to a go-live&lt;/a> is crucial. This is the approach we are taking with Wardware and the other projects we are working on. Can we pass a simple message through the components of the stack? No. Fix it. And now? Yes. Great! Build on and test for regressions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>