<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dissertation on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/dissertation/</link><description>Recent content in Dissertation on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/dissertation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hacking the Networked Society.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2020/03/30/hacking-the-networked-society./</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2020/03/30/hacking-the-networked-society./</guid><description>Introduction. The dynamic between free-software and open-source is often misunderstood by social and political theorists. As a consequence it is also under-theorised within socio-political theory. In this paper, I show how philosophies of free/libre, open-source and commons regimes have engendered new forms of sociopolitical consumption and new political economies of meaning. My emphasis on the interplay between the local and the global/structure and agency, shows new ways of ‘thinking’ the cosmopolitan, sedimented in the interconnected networks of the technical age.</description></item><item><title>dissertation project - submitted and now online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/21/dissertation-project-submitted-and-now-online/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 22:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/05/21/dissertation-project-submitted-and-now-online/</guid><description>Hacking the Networked Society.
Abstract: The dynamic between free-software and open-source is often misunderstood by social and political theorists. As a consequence it is also under-theorised within socio-political theory. In this paper, I show how philosophies of free/libre, open-source and commons regimes have engendered new forms of socio-political consumption and new political economies of meaning. My emphasis on the interplay between the local and the global/structure and agency, shows new ways of &amp;lsquo;thinking&amp;rsquo; the cosmopolitan, sedimented in the interconnected networks of the technical age.</description></item><item><title>dissertation book print project</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-book-print-project/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 15:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-book-print-project/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been investigating the feasibility of collecting and publishing final year dissertation projects in book form. I think that this will make a great reminder of our time of study, our political alliances and the friendships that have grown over the years at Goldsmiths. Also it&amp;rsquo;s such an indulgent, gratuitous act: So Fucking Goldsmiths. My plan is to gather together our dissertations and publish a book (ISBN record and everything) of our works to have it printed and ready for graduation in September.</description></item><item><title>dissertation project - reviewed and replanned</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-project-reviewed-and-replanned/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 15:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/22/dissertation-project-reviewed-and-replanned/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy reviewing and replanning my dissertation project - only five weeks to go until hand-in! I&amp;rsquo;ve cut a lot out since my proposal last year, tightening my focus and shortening my reading lists. My four papers now look something like this&amp;hellip;
Who Governs in a Networked Society (final draft complete) - My first chapter is concerned with the depoliticisation of government and the politicisation of the social world in a global networked society.</description></item><item><title>On puting the effort in...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/25/on-puting-the-effort-in.../</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 12:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/25/on-puting-the-effort-in.../</guid><description>By the Gods! There are but weeks remaining for the third year politics students. Next significant deadline is the 13th March, the hand-in for New Radical Political Economy (NRPE) and Liberalism and Its Critics. I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished my NRPE paper, &amp;lsquo;To what extent do social, peer-to-peer and participatory models democratise capital&amp;rsquo;, so this week I&amp;rsquo;ll be devoting to my Dissertation project which has received somewhere between little and no attention since I wrote my proposal back in October&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>current efforts</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/current-efforts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/current-efforts/</guid><description>Plenty of keyboard time coming up over the next few weeks&amp;hellip;
The dissertation project continues: are radical openness of f/los communities embodying resistance to Empire? My proposal was graded at 8/10 &amp;hellip; must be doing something right. Now to maintain that effort!
Also researching a paper on social. p2p and participatory financial models with specific reference to banking systems. Zopa, Kiva and Open Capital are my case studies. Meeting with the CFO of Zopa tomorrow!</description></item><item><title>dissertation research proposal submitted today</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/11/13/dissertation-research-proposal-submitted-today/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 18:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/11/13/dissertation-research-proposal-submitted-today/</guid><description>Phew! Completed the text, committed to my repository, created a PDF, printed the output.
Attached&amp;hellip; Dissertation Research Proposal{#p304} (for those with too much time on their hands.)
I should get 5 spare minutes now to make public my repository and publish other essays and notes from previous study years.</description></item><item><title>research proposal for my politics degree</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/11/02/research-proposal-for-my-politics-degree/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2007 14:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/11/02/research-proposal-for-my-politics-degree/</guid><description>&lt;p>This year I get to write a dissertation for my degree course. I&amp;rsquo;m going to blog the development of my focus of study and my argument here and use my wiki and other tools to share resources I&amp;rsquo;ve found useful. I can&amp;rsquo;t wiki my work though - it needs to be all my own effort! But I will be publishing here it after its been submitted - another 10,000 words to add to the global text pool that is the internet.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>