<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hansard on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/hansard/</link><description>Recent content in Hansard on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 10:20:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/hansard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MPs Online - Hansard Society publication</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/mps-online-hansard-society-publication-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 10:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/mps-online-hansard-society-publication-2/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s published.
A new Hansard Society report, sponsored by Microsoft, MPs Online: Connecting with Constituents, reveals that MPs are using the internet primarily to inform their constituents rather than engage with them. The most widely used digital media are those which are mainly passive in nature, such as website. Interactive forms of media which could be used by MPs to develop a two-way dialogue with their constituents, such as blogs and social networking, are used less commonly.</description></item><item><title>The online campaign; an event by Hansard</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/the-online-campaign-an-event-by-hansard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 09:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/the-online-campaign-an-event-by-hansard/</guid><description>Just digging around the Hansard Society website for a copy of the report on MPs online, published by the e-democracy unit and I found the blurb for this event, The Online Campaign, in late March.
The use of online strategies is becoming increasingly important, encouraging grass-roots activism and enabling mass mobilisation. But there is no guarantee that the cooption of online strategies will guarantee electoral success or promote healthy dialogue between politicians and citizens.</description></item><item><title>MPs Online - Hansard Society publication</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/mps-online-hansard-society-publication/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 09:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2009/02/24/mps-online-hansard-society-publication/</guid><description>Just been listening to the Toady programme on R4 and heard in the news report at 8am that the Hansard Society had published a report on MPs online. According to the Societies' website, this &amp;ldquo;research attempts to understand how MPs themselves feel the internet affects the way that they work and communicate with their constituents. The research includes a survey of MPs and a focus group of MPs and their office staff.</description></item></channel></rss>