<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MAPRA on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/mapra/</link><description>Recent content in MAPRA on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 10:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/mapra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MapRA AGM</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/mapra-agm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 10:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/mapra-agm/</guid><description>Here are some of the photos I took of the Meet the Candiates session at the Mapesbury AGM last month.
[imagebrowser id=3]</description></item><item><title>NW2 Residents Association Thanks Lib Dem Councillors</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/nw2-residents-association-thanks-lib-dem-councillors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/nw2-residents-association-thanks-lib-dem-councillors/</guid><description>The North West Two Residents Association held its AGM on the 22nd April at the Windmill Pub on Cricklewood Broadway.
The NW2 Committee NW2 began in September 2007 as a group local residents who wanted to improve the sense of community in the Cricklewood area. As Carol Granger, Committee Chair, writes &amp;ldquo;The Association was founded first to try to improve the sense of community in the area and provide opportunities for people in the neighbourhood to get together, and to get to know each other and maybe help each other out; but also to improve the appearance of the area (litter, graffiti, etc); to try to improve relationships with Brent and the officers who look after services for the area; try to make sure Cricklewood didn&amp;rsquo;t stay the Cinderella of Brent / Barnet / Camden.</description></item><item><title>photos from the MapRA hustings last night.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/20/photos-from-the-mapra-hustings-last-night./</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/20/photos-from-the-mapra-hustings-last-night./</guid><description>&lt;p>Bums on seats&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/WVYtyE2hs7VMSikZow09Ng?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OKmG7VBI/AAAAAAAAAgc/vLPOHoCM7WU/s144/P1000341.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/rfnU_kDKvm-X_CLYPjX_Nw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OLXXfwTI/AAAAAAAAAgg/D8kSXXB80Rw/s144/P1000342.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/-0ksbEeqrrAPICkF95umGg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OM4xHosI/AAAAAAAAAgk/0Z0BTetcHj4/s144/P1000343.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And more&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MapRA AGM and hustings tonight.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/mapra-agm-and-hustings-tonight./</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/mapra-agm-and-hustings-tonight./</guid><description>&lt;p>Election hustings and MapRA AGM at St. Gabriel&amp;rsquo;s Church, Walm Lane, tonight.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Click on for a map.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Residents Associations AGM - 19th APR</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/12/mapesbury-residents-associations-agm-19th-apr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 08:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/12/mapesbury-residents-associations-agm-19th-apr/</guid><description>The Mapesbury Residents Association are holding the groups' Annual General Meeting on the 19th April. After the formal meeting there will be an Election Hustings. All the political parties have been invited and it will give you the opportunity to meet the candidates for election - councillors as well as MPs.
The MapRA AGM is a lively and informative event. With the usual high-quality nibbles, there are also stalls and information stands from the police, Brent Council and other local groups and organisations.</description></item><item><title>MapRA Network - Local Open Gardens</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/06/11/mapra-network-local-open-gardens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 16:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/06/11/mapra-network-local-open-gardens/</guid><description>I received an email from the MapRA Network advising me of some local Open Gardens in the National Garden Scheme. In this scheme, private gardens of national interest are opened to the public, in aid of charity. Here is a map of the local open gardens.
View Larger Map
For more information on the NGS visit www.ngs.org.uk The main charities supported are: Macmillan Cancer Support; Marie Curie Cancer Care; Help the Hospices.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>At the Mapesbury Residents Association Annnual General Meeting on Thursday night I was hoping to speak to the assembled residents about the Community Wireless Network I am involved in running in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. Having been very impressed by the collective action that MapRA have motived in their community around the Mapesbury Dell project and the purchase of old-fashioned, sorry, &amp;lsquo;heritage&amp;rsquo; street lights for some of the streets, I thought that a Community Wireless Broadband Network would have been something that the residents of Mapesbury may have been interested in working to acheive.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Residents Association AGM</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/mapesbury-residents-association-agm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/mapesbury-residents-association-agm/</guid><description>Those active in local civil society and engaged in their neighbourhood were out at St. Gabriel&amp;rsquo;s Church on Walm Lane on Thursday night for the Mapesbury Residents Association Annual General Meeting. MapRA is a large and active group of neighbours all commited to woking for the benefit of the Mapesbury community. Attendance from the membership of MapRA is good and the nave of church was full.
I had expected to see Sarah Teather there: She was there last year, speaking on some of the activities that she, as the local MP, had beeen working on with MapRA and other people from the neighbouorhood.</description></item></channel></rss>