<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Election 2010 on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/election-2010/</link><description>Recent content in Election 2010 on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:59:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/election-2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Take Back Parliament - Fair Votes Now</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/take-back-parliament-fair-votes-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:59:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/take-back-parliament-fair-votes-now/</guid><description>Flashmob for fair votes 5pm outside Lib Dem talks, 21 Palmer Street, SW1H 0AD.
http://twitter.com/takeback2010</description></item><item><title>Electoral Reform.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/electoral-reform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/electoral-reform/</guid><description>New figures from the Electoral Reform Society examine exactly how well each party would have done under two systems of PR: Alternative Vote (AV) and Single Transferable Vote (STV).
While they show that under AV the Lib Dems would only increase their seats to 79, the most interesting think for me is that the Conservatives still poll the most seats but insufficient for a majority in all examples.
A Lib/Lab coalition under AV would have a 60 seat majority, with a Lib/Con group a majority of 98.</description></item><item><title>Would Brent Central Lib Dems punish Sarah Teather for Lib/Con pact?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/would-brent-central-lib-dems-punish-sarah-teather-for-libcon-pact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/would-brent-central-lib-dems-punish-sarah-teather-for-libcon-pact/</guid><description>Brent Central is close. Just 1,345 votes separated Labour and the Lib Dems, around 3% or about 1.5 voters in every 50.
Would Brent Central Lib Dem voters punish Sarah Teather for a Lib/Con pact? In a briefing paper published today by the Fabian society, Brent Central is listed as a constituency likely to swing back to Labour at a second general election in 2010.
&amp;ldquo;﻿As this table shows, there are 15 Lib Dem seats that would fall to Labour if just one-in-five of their voters switched to Labour.</description></item><item><title>Take Back Parliament</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/take-back-parliament/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 11:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/take-back-parliament/</guid><description>Here is my video taken at the TakeBackParliament protest on Saturday.
Dressed in purple and holding signs such as &amp;ldquo;fair votes now&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;votes not moats&amp;rdquo; around a thousand campaigners gathered in order to &amp;ldquo;Take back Parliament&amp;rdquo; for the voters.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be doing it all again tonight, so I hear&amp;hellip;..</description></item><item><title>Brent's General Election results.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</guid><description>The voters of Brent have returned Lib Dem Sarah Teather with a majority of 1,345, a swing of 11% from Labour, and Labour&amp;rsquo;s Barry Gardiner with a majority of 8,028, loosing 2.5% of the vote to the Conservatives (+2.2%) and other parties. I was at the count on Thursday night tally marking for the Lib Dems and in-between boxes of ballot papers talking with candidates and journalists about the political economy of Brent as a borough.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather Is Our MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/07/sarah-teather-is-our-mp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 21:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/07/sarah-teather-is-our-mp/</guid><description>Sarah Teather was returned to parliament by the voters of Brent Central.
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Party &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Votes &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; % &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Liberal Democrats &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 20026 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 44% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Labour &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 18681 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 41% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Conservative &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 5067 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 11% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Green Party &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 668 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Christian Party &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 488 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Respect &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 230 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Independent &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 163 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 0% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>While I was out....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Gone in 60 seconds.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/gone-in-60-seconds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/gone-in-60-seconds/</guid><description>Here is Ross Kemp&amp;rsquo;s party piece.</description></item><item><title>Brent Central - Willesden Green</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/brent-central-willesden-green/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 10:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/brent-central-willesden-green/</guid><description>Mark Pack reports that in Willesden Green polling didn&amp;rsquo;t start until after 9am becuase ballot papers for the wrong Parliamentary constituency had been supplied to all three polling stations Willesden Green ward.
Bonkers.</description></item><item><title>The peoples election</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/the-peoples-election/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 10:37:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/the-peoples-election/</guid><description>Mr Brown was asked for his reaction to the news that celebrity TV supremo Simon Cowell was backing the Conservatives and thought the prime ministers was tired. ﻿﻿&amp;rdquo;This election isn&amp;rsquo;t about celebrities, it&amp;rsquo;s about people&amp;quot;, he said. Yet we have had a lot of celebrity involvement in the national and local campaigns:
Labour celebrities: Ross Kemp, Jo Brand, Eddie Izzard, David Tennant.
Conservative celebrities: Michael Caine, erm&amp;hellip;.. (help me out here, I don&amp;rsquo;t watch the telly!</description></item><item><title>Kilburn Station, 6:45pm</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/kilburn-station-645pm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 23:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/kilburn-station-645pm/</guid><description>Busy outside Kilburn Station this evening. Picked up a whole host of goodies and the Evening Standard.
Team Glenda gave me a DVD with ROSS KEMP on it! &amp;lsquo;Gone in 60 seconds&amp;rsquo; explains &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s at stake on Thursday&amp;quot;. Hopefully. He. Makes. It. Easy. For. Me. To. Understand.
Some more celebrity messages for Team Labour attacking the Tories from Jo Brand and Eddie Izzard. And David Tennant shares with us that he thinks David Cameron is &amp;ldquo;a terrifying prospect&amp;rdquo; in a viewspaper &amp;lsquo;Britian&amp;rsquo;s recovery at risk from Tories'.</description></item><item><title>Labour voter goodie bags</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/labour-voter-goodie-bags/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/labour-voter-goodie-bags/</guid><description>As seen in Mapesbury, junction of Olive and Snyed Roads.</description></item><item><title>Photos from Stonebridge - Hillside &amp; Fawood Children's Centre</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/photos-from-stonebridge-hillside-fawood-childrens-centre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/photos-from-stonebridge-hillside-fawood-childrens-centre/</guid><description>From wikipedia: Stonebridge is the largest electoral ward in Brent and includes Stonebridge Estate, and parts of Park Royal and Brent Park, St. Raphael&amp;rsquo;s Estate, Mitchellbrook and the Hillside district. The area has strong links with the Afro-Caribbean community which forms the ward&amp;rsquo;s ethnic majority.
Here are a few photos of the last remaining block on the Stonebridge Estate off Hillside, Brent. You can see the cleared land from recent demolition work in the foreground.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Butler's hoarding at Unisys, Brentfield</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/dawn-butlers-hoarding-at-unisys-brentfield/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 13:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/dawn-butlers-hoarding-at-unisys-brentfield/</guid><description>Is back on its legs.
Whatever you do, don&amp;rsquo;t visit the web address stencilled on the windows of the building, unless you want to book an escort&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Does Dawn know (or care) where Stonebridge is?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/does-dawn-know-or-care-where-stonebridge-is/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/does-dawn-know-or-care-where-stonebridge-is/</guid><description>On this mornings electoral communication from the Labour Party, Dawn Butler highlights housing, in particular the investment in Stonebridge and St. Raphael&amp;rsquo;s Estate where monstrous concrete high rises are being destroyed, replaced with low-density and low-rise housing.
Regeneration of Trellick Tower? Only that is not Stonebridge. It&amp;rsquo;s Trellick Tower, 3miles down the road in Ladbroke Grove&amp;hellip;..
trellick tower The stock photo comes from PhotoEverywhere.</description></item><item><title>Local Torys ready for an election.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/local-torys-ready-for-an-election/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 14:29:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/local-torys-ready-for-an-election/</guid><description>Torys care for mapesbury! Is the exclamation mark is necessary? Well, I&amp;rsquo;m as surprised as they are, so I guess so!
On the back, Brent Conservatives ask Mapesbury residents how they would vote IF there was a general election in the next few months&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; Someone ought to let Sachin Rajput know that he&amp;rsquo;s on the list for Thursday.
Picked up on Mora Road on Monday. Uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Butler hording advertising at Unisys, Brentfield.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/butler-advertising-at-unisys-brentfield/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/butler-advertising-at-unisys-brentfield/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Consider a building with a few broken windows. If the windows are not repaired, the tendency is for vandals to break a few more windows. Eventually, they may even break into the building, and if it&amp;rsquo;s unoccupied, perhaps become squatters or light fires inside.&amp;rdquo; Wilson and Kelling, 1982.
A building like this?
The ex-Unisys building on Brentfield has been empty for well over a decade. In 1997 the owners were granted planning consent to convert the office blocks to a 330-bedroom hotel, add a new penthouse storey on front block facing North Circular Road, a new single-deck car park and new boundary wall.</description></item><item><title>MapRA AGM</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/mapra-agm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 10:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/mapra-agm/</guid><description>Here are some of the photos I took of the Meet the Candiates session at the Mapesbury AGM last month.
[imagebrowser id=3]</description></item><item><title>Beam me up scottie.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/beam-me-up-scottie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:05:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/beam-me-up-scottie/</guid><description>Operation Lucid - Ubuntu in London
BBC to beam general election results on to Big Ben</description></item><item><title>A message from Ken Livingstone</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/a-message-from-ken-livingstone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 14:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/a-message-from-ken-livingstone/</guid><description>Shoring up the core vote, Ken Livingstone writes to Labour party voters/members in Brent Central. &amp;ldquo;We can&amp;rsquo;t afford to have the country run like Brent Council.&amp;rdquo; Letter received in Mapesbury, 2nd May.
Uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Hampstead and Kilburn</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/hampstead-and-kilburn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 21:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/hampstead-and-kilburn/</guid><description>Liberal Democrat candidate Ed Fordham needs just 474 votes to win the seat from Glenda Jackson. Driving through QP this afternoon I saw lots of Labour posters and flags with only a few Lib Dem orange diamonds. Looks like there is mroe work for the Lib Dem team to do there. The Torys had just a single board - just like the solitary piece of literature I found from them today.</description></item><item><title>Floella Benjamin campaigns with Sarah Teather</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 13:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/floella-benjamin-campaigns-with-sarah-teather/</guid><description>WBTimes report that &amp;ldquo;Floella Benjamin ditched the teddy bear props&amp;rdquo; when she joined Lib Dem candidate for Brent Central, Sarah Teather this week. Floella joined Sarah on Harlesden High Street to collect signatures in Harlesden, to sign up residents to a petition urging the government to reform air passenger duty.
Air Passenger Duty (APD) is an excise duty which is charged on the carriage of passengers flying from a United Kingdom airport.</description></item><item><title>Labour pay legal costs to Brent Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/labour-pay-legal-costs-to-brent-lib-dems/</guid><description>Brent councillor James Powney laments the threat and use of legal writ to silence debate, tending towards an environment where &amp;lsquo;legitimate freedom of speech could be restricted by self censorship.&amp;rsquo;
Legal writ has its strength though. When Brent Labour distributed a leaflet with false claims about Sarah Teather, the Brent Leb Dems took appropriate legal measures. In the face of the legal action, Labour have now admitted their story was false and agreed to pay the Lib Dems legal costs.</description></item><item><title>Atiq Malik standards board inquiry</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/atiq-malik-standards-board-inquiry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:27:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/atiq-malik-standards-board-inquiry/</guid><description>More on Atiq Malik, independent candidate in Brent Central, on this weeks WBTimes front page. They don&amp;rsquo;t disclose the nature of the allegations against him for &amp;lsquo;legal reasons&amp;rsquo; and the internet isn&amp;rsquo;t throwing up rumours for me to link to, not even on Labour Cllr James Powney&amp;rsquo;s blog - although there is a great archive of items on Atiq Malik&amp;rsquo;s views on women and optioning aspects of Sharia Law for UK Muslims.</description></item><item><title>from the local press</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/27/apr-local-press/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 11:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/27/apr-local-press/</guid><description>The Willesden and Brent Times spoke to local candidates standing as independents or for the smaller parties, including Shahrar Ali for the Green Party and Atiq Malik.
Atiq Malik is Brents&amp;rsquo; own &amp;lsquo;controversial&amp;rsquo; candidate. An ex-conservative councillor in Queensbury ward, jumped/pushed from the party in 2008, he has previously been referred to the Standards Board for England, the standards watchdog for Councillors and other officials. He was subsequently cleared of misconduct.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather commended by British Muslim Initiative and salaam.co.uk</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/24/sarah-teather-commended-by-british-muslim-initiative-and-salaam-co-uk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 00:11:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/24/sarah-teather-commended-by-british-muslim-initiative-and-salaam-co-uk/</guid><description>YouElect is a non-profit and independent British Muslim grassroots initiative aimed at promoting voter registration and political engagement. I&amp;rsquo;ve just looked up Brent Central where Sarah Teather is the Community Choice Candidate, commended by both the British Muslim Initiative and salaam.co.uk.
Dawn Butler and Sachin Rajput are also profiled on the YouElect site.</description></item><item><title>WB Times "Butler told to apologise"</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/wb-times-butler-told-to-apologise/</guid><description>Brent&amp;rsquo;s Labour Group formal apology for issuing leaflets with defamatory claims about Sarah Teather is on page 4 of the WB Times this week.
Willesden and Brent Times, 23 April, 2010</description></item><item><title>Local election leaflets online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</guid><description>The Straight Choice election leaflet project is an archive of election leaflets distributed throughout the campaign. This is a helpful thing to be doing as &amp;hellip;..
Promises that candidates make in their leaflets can be compared to what they promise to do elsewhere. In the future we can also compare the voting record of MPs with what they promised on the campaign trail.
It helps catch parties or candidates who are breaking electoral law - 2 parties have been reported to the authorities based on leaflets uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Brent Central - track the candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/brent-central-track-the-candidates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/brent-central-track-the-candidates/</guid><description>Democracy Club website helps us to hold candidates to account, and stimulate public engagement in the campaigns for local and national elections. Big job&amp;hellip; lots of small tasks. The website helps residents to track and contact candidates, create local issue lists and track the responses from candidates.
Check out Brent Central, Brent North and Hampstead and Kilburn at the DemocracyClub website and join in.</description></item><item><title>Butler issues full apology for Teather expenses smear</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/21/butler-issues-full-apology-for-teather-expenses-smear/</guid><description>LibDem Voice has some news on Brent Centrals dirty politics.
Labour Minister Dawn Butler has issued a legal apology to Sarah Teather for calling her a hypocrite over MPs’ expenses. Butler made the accusation while the running of Sarah Teather’s office was under investigation. The Parliamentary Standards Commissioner later dropped the investigation because there were no grounds to suspect any wrongdoing by Ms Teather.
This issue came up at the MapRA Hustings on Monday night.</description></item><item><title>photos from the MapRA hustings last night.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/20/photos-from-the-mapra-hustings-last-night/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/20/photos-from-the-mapra-hustings-last-night/</guid><description>&lt;p>Bums on seats&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/WVYtyE2hs7VMSikZow09Ng?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OKmG7VBI/AAAAAAAAAgc/vLPOHoCM7WU/s144/P1000341.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/rfnU_kDKvm-X_CLYPjX_Nw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OLXXfwTI/AAAAAAAAAgg/D8kSXXB80Rw/s144/P1000342.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.co.uk/lh/photo/-0ksbEeqrrAPICkF95umGg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.ggpht.com/_PY28G6lkrNU/S8-OM4xHosI/AAAAAAAAAgk/0Z0BTetcHj4/s144/P1000343.JPG" alt="">&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And more&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MapRA AGM and hustings tonight.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/mapra-agm-and-hustings-tonight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/mapra-agm-and-hustings-tonight/</guid><description>&lt;p>Election hustings and MapRA AGM at St. Gabriel&amp;rsquo;s Church, Walm Lane, tonight.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Click on for a map.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Last day to submit your nomination.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/last-day-to-submit-your-nomination/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 05:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/19/last-day-to-submit-your-nomination/</guid><description>Completed nomination papers accompanied by the deposit of £500 must be delivered to the Acting Returning Officer at the offices of the London Borough of Brent not later than 4pm on Tuesday, 20th April 2010.
You can view / download the election notices at Brent Council&amp;rsquo;s website.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Residents Associations AGM - 19th APR</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/12/mapesbury-residents-associations-agm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 08:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/12/mapesbury-residents-associations-agm/</guid><description>The Mapesbury Residents Association are holding the groups&amp;rsquo; Annual General Meeting on the 19th April. After the formal meeting there will be an Election Hustings. All the political parties have been invited and it will give you the opportunity to meet the candidates for election - councillors as well as MPs.
The MapRA AGM is a lively and informative event. With the usual high-quality nibbles, there are also stalls and information stands from the police, Brent Council and other local groups and organisations.</description></item><item><title>List of candidates for Brent Council wards.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/09/list-of-candidates-for-brent-council-wards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 06:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/09/list-of-candidates-for-brent-council-wards/</guid><description>The deadline for nominations closed at midday on 8 April 2010 and details of the candidates for the local elections are available in this PDF, published on 9 April. A PDF? Have Brent Council learned nothing about publishing information online? I&amp;rsquo;ll rework the list and make it nice and human-readable without having to download a PDF!</description></item><item><title>No Brent East, Just Campaigning</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/06/no-brent-east-just-campaigning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 12:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/06/no-brent-east-just-campaigning/</guid><description>There is to be a General Election on May 6th, along with the local elections. You would think it had been called back in December given the fluster and bumph in the media. The snow wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough to distract us from the political machinations at Westmonster. That snow will probably become an election issue this year, if anyone remembers it - perhaps there will be some more before the election.</description></item><item><title>Brent Labour - Mapesbury News</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/04/brent-labour-mapesbury-news/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/04/brent-labour-mapesbury-news/</guid><description>From your local Labour Action Team.
The theme of this newsletter is rubbish. Brent Labour argue that the charge made by the council for bulky refuse collection has lead to an increase in fly-tipping in Brent and pledge to &amp;lsquo;dump&amp;rsquo; the £25 charge if elected. If that isn&amp;rsquo;t inducement enough for you, they claim that cuts, CUTS!, will reduce the frequency of rubbish collection.
The main flytipping problem in Brent is caused by unscrupulous builder, dumping domestic building waste.</description></item><item><title>MP Sarah Cleared</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/01/mp-sarah-cleared/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A letter of complaint against Sarah Teather was sent to the Parliamentary Standards Commissioner, supposedly from a man at an address in Brent. Then a second letter of complaint was sent, again from this man, but giving a new address. However, this new address does not exist. There is a real address with the same house number and postcode (but different rest of address), at which there is one person on the electoral register – a woman who has the name of someone listed on Labour MP Dawn Butler’s register of interests as being a member of her staff.</description></item></channel></rss>