<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dotgovlabs on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/dotgovlabs/</link><description>Recent content in dotgovlabs on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 12:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/dotgovlabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discussing open source on DotGovLabs</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/04/discussing-open-source-on-dotgovlabs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 12:04:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/04/discussing-open-source-on-dotgovlabs/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m a member of the Cabinet Office &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Skunk_Works">Skunkworks&lt;/a> project &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href="https://dotgovlabs.direct.gov.uk">dotgovlabs&lt;/a>', where &amp;lsquo;innovators&amp;rsquo; post &amp;lsquo;solutions&amp;rsquo; in different &amp;lsquo;challenge&amp;rsquo; areas. Rather than write anything more (that you won&amp;rsquo;t read) about dotgotlabs, here is a &lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/21720640">video produced to explain the project&lt;/a> &amp;hellip; including me and others with great faces for radio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With interests in open source, open standards and interoperability and with experience in and around the NHS, I&amp;rsquo;ve contributed to many solutions posted in the Healthcare challenge.  I&amp;rsquo;ve commented on the &lt;a href="http://www.connectingforhealth.nhs.uk/systemsandservices/interop/making">interoperability&lt;/a> challenges facing &amp;lsquo;Solutions&amp;rsquo; such as &amp;lsquo;Give Patients Access to Data&amp;rsquo; (a challenge involving &lt;a href="http://www.patientopinion.org.uk/">Patient Opinion&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="http://www.mydex.org">MyDex&lt;/a>, see previous post on &lt;a href="http://www.robdyke.com/noc/2011/03/24/brent-council-to-allow-residents-to-manage-their-personal-data/">Brent Council opening up resident data access&lt;/a>) and on the use of social media in healthcare solutions &amp;hellip; and the &lt;a href="http://mmt.me.uk/blog/2010/11/21/nhs-and-tracking/">privacy implications&lt;/a> there in&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been contributing heavily to a solution posted by &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/timknight">Tim Knight&lt;/a> which proposed greater use of open source practices in the NHS - provisionally titled &lt;a href="https://dotgovlabs.direct.gov.uk/Page/ViewIdea?ideaid=1293">Open Me Project&lt;/a> (login req; email me for invitation).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The goal of the solution is to provide a framework and supporting tools for the collaborative development of open source solutions for NHS organisations and commercial healthcare providers. The solution has been voted up to progress from &amp;lsquo;Buzz&amp;rsquo; stage to &amp;lsquo;Teaming&amp;rsquo; stage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As part of the incubation process for solutions, DotGovLabs have engaged the support of Experts from Departments of state and the Private Sector to give feedback and pose challenging questions to teams. This weekend &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=18009701">David Ostler&lt;/a>, Chairman of unitedHealth posted feedback on our solution and several others.  I thought I would repost the exchange here.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>