<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brent Central on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-central/</link><description>Recent content in Brent Central on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Would Brent Central Lib Dems punish Sarah Teather for Lib/Con pact?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/would-brent-central-lib-dems-punish-sarah-teather-for-libcon-pact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 12:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/would-brent-central-lib-dems-punish-sarah-teather-for-libcon-pact/</guid><description>Brent Central is close. Just 1,345 votes separated Labour and the Lib Dems, around 3% or about 1.5 voters in every 50.
Would Brent Central Lib Dem voters punish Sarah Teather for a Lib/Con pact? In a briefing paper published today by the Fabian society, Brent Central is listed as a constituency likely to swing back to Labour at a second general election in 2010.
&amp;ldquo;﻿As this table shows, there are 15 Lib Dem seats that would fall to Labour if just one-in-five of their voters switched to Labour.</description></item><item><title>Brent's General Election results.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/08/brents-general-election-results/</guid><description>The voters of Brent have returned Lib Dem Sarah Teather with a majority of 1,345, a swing of 11% from Labour, and Labour&amp;rsquo;s Barry Gardiner with a majority of 8,028, loosing 2.5% of the vote to the Conservatives (+2.2%) and other parties. I was at the count on Thursday night tally marking for the Lib Dems and in-between boxes of ballot papers talking with candidates and journalists about the political economy of Brent as a borough.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather Is Our MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/07/sarah-teather-is-our-mp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 21:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/07/sarah-teather-is-our-mp/</guid><description>Sarah Teather was returned to parliament by the voters of Brent Central.
&amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Party &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Votes &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; % &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;th scope=&amp;quot;col&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Liberal Democrats &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 20026 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 44% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Labour &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 18681 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 41% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Conservative &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 5067 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 11% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Green Party &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 668 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Christian Party &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 488 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Respect &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 230 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 1% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Independent &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 163 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; 0% &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td&amp;gt; Not elected &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>While I was out....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/while-i-was-out/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Team Teather in Mapesbury</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/team-teather-in-mapesbury/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/team-teather-in-mapesbury/</guid><description>**[imagebrowser id=4]**﻿</description></item><item><title>Brent Central - Willesden Green</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/brent-central-willesden-green/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 10:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/06/brent-central-willesden-green/</guid><description>Mark Pack reports that in Willesden Green polling didn&amp;rsquo;t start until after 9am becuase ballot papers for the wrong Parliamentary constituency had been supplied to all three polling stations Willesden Green ward.
Bonkers.</description></item><item><title>Kilburn Station, 6:45pm</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/kilburn-station-645pm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 23:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/kilburn-station-645pm/</guid><description>Busy outside Kilburn Station this evening. Picked up a whole host of goodies and the Evening Standard.
Team Glenda gave me a DVD with ROSS KEMP on it! &amp;lsquo;Gone in 60 seconds&amp;rsquo; explains &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s at stake on Thursday&amp;rdquo;. Hopefully. He. Makes. It. Easy. For. Me. To. Understand.
Some more celebrity messages for Team Labour attacking the Tories from Jo Brand and Eddie Izzard. And David Tennant shares with us that he thinks David Cameron is &amp;ldquo;a terrifying prospect&amp;rdquo; in a viewspaper &amp;lsquo;Britian&amp;rsquo;s recovery at risk from Tories&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Does Dawn know (or care) where Stonebridge is?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/does-dawn-know-or-care-where-stonebridge-is/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/does-dawn-know-or-care-where-stonebridge-is/</guid><description>On this mornings electoral communication from the Labour Party, Dawn Butler highlights housing, in particular the investment in Stonebridge and St. Raphael&amp;rsquo;s Estate where monstrous concrete high rises are being destroyed, replaced with low-density and low-rise housing.
Regeneration of Trellick Tower? Only that is not Stonebridge. It&amp;rsquo;s Trellick Tower, 3miles down the road in Ladbroke Grove&amp;hellip;..
trellick tower The stock photo comes from PhotoEverywhere.</description></item><item><title>Bridge Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/bridge-park/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 10:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/bridge-park/</guid><description>I popped down to Bridge Park yesterday morning, for reasons which will become clear&amp;hellip;. Bumped into Errol Williams, preparing for a busy day out in Brent Proclaiming Christ&amp;rsquo;s Lordship. His first pledge is to bring all legislation is brought into conformity with the word of God. I uploaded his materials to TheStraightChoice for reference and they are included in the slideshow.
Bridge Park is just of Brentfield as you come down from Harlesden.</description></item><item><title>A message from Ken Livingstone</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/a-message-from-ken-livingstone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 14:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/02/a-message-from-ken-livingstone/</guid><description>Shoring up the core vote, Ken Livingstone writes to Labour party voters/members in Brent Central. &amp;ldquo;We can&amp;rsquo;t afford to have the country run like Brent Council.&amp;rdquo; Letter received in Mapesbury, 2nd May.
Uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Atiq Malik standards board inquiry</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/atiq-malik-standards-board-inquiry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 11:27:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/01/atiq-malik-standards-board-inquiry/</guid><description>More on Atiq Malik, independent candidate in Brent Central, on this weeks WBTimes front page. They don&amp;rsquo;t disclose the nature of the allegations against him for &amp;lsquo;legal reasons&amp;rsquo; and the internet isn&amp;rsquo;t throwing up rumours for me to link to, not even on Labour Cllr James Powney&amp;rsquo;s blog - although there is a great archive of items on Atiq Malik&amp;rsquo;s views on women and optioning aspects of Sharia Law for UK Muslims.</description></item><item><title>from the local press</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/27/apr-local-press/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 11:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/27/apr-local-press/</guid><description>The Willesden and Brent Times spoke to local candidates standing as independents or for the smaller parties, including Shahrar Ali for the Green Party and Atiq Malik.
Atiq Malik is Brents' own &amp;lsquo;controversial&amp;rsquo; candidate. An ex-conservative councillor in Queensbury ward, jumped/pushed from the party in 2008, he has previously been referred to the Standards Board for England, the standards watchdog for Councillors and other officials. He was subsequently cleared of misconduct.</description></item><item><title>Local election leaflets online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</guid><description>The Straight Choice election leaflet project is an archive of election leaflets distributed throughout the campaign. This is a helpful thing to be doing as &amp;hellip;..
Promises that candidates make in their leaflets can be compared to what they promise to do elsewhere. In the future we can also compare the voting record of MPs with what they promised on the campaign trail.
It helps catch parties or candidates who are breaking electoral law - 2 parties have been reported to the authorities based on leaflets uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Brent Central - track the candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/brent-central-track-the-candidates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/brent-central-track-the-candidates/</guid><description>Democracy Club website helps us to hold candidates to account, and stimulate public engagement in the campaigns for local and national elections. Big job&amp;hellip; lots of small tasks. The website helps residents to track and contact candidates, create local issue lists and track the responses from candidates.
Check out Brent Central, Brent North and Hampstead and Kilburn at the DemocracyClub website and join in.</description></item></channel></rss>