<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Election 2005 on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/election-2005/</link><description>Recent content in Election 2005 on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 10:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/election-2005/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Catch your MP...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/13/catch-your-mp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/13/catch-your-mp/</guid><description>The film of the Brent East STW hustings is one of a number of films documenting the views of Prospective Parliamentary Candidates on the aggressive action taken against Iraq. The Catch Your MP project aims to hold to account the 412 Members of the 2001-2005 Parliament that voted in support of military action.
Candidates for Brent East: Shahrar, Sarah, Yasmin, Kwasi and George along with Rocky (Wasn&amp;rsquo;t that a Rainbow cast?</description></item><item><title>I wish I'd seen this earlier...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/12/i-wish-id-seen-this-earlier/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/12/i-wish-id-seen-this-earlier/</guid><description>Trawling through the list of refering links to this site I came across a search engine, A9.com, that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard of. I followed the link to discover where this blog was ranked on the list that refered the reader to the blog. Just below the link to this blog was a link to Film Makers Against War.
I wish I&amp;rsquo;d seen the film made of the Brent East Stop The War Hustings earlier.</description></item><item><title>Election Expenses</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/10/election-expenses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/10/election-expenses/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been digging around into the rules around election expenses. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to calculate the maximum permitted expenses a candidate or agent may incur in Brent East. Thankfully the Electoral Commission website is a wealth of information on electoral law and regulations.
Election expenses are those ‘expenses incurred whether before, during or after the election, on account of or in respect of the conduct or management of the election’. They may only be incurred by the candidate, his election agent or persons authorised in writing by that agent.</description></item><item><title>See what happens when you win an election...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/09/see-what-happens-when-you-win-an-election/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2005 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/09/see-what-happens-when-you-win-an-election/</guid><description>This graphic was generated from the hit data to this blog between the 3rd and the 9th of May 2005.</description></item><item><title>Brent East Campaigning - A review</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/09/brent-east-campaigning-a-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2005 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/09/brent-east-campaigning-a-review/</guid><description>Over 6 weeks &amp;amp; 53 postings the Brent East Campaign has been blogged. My keyboard is wornout and revision for my exams in backlog. This has been a prolonged high - which explains my recent apearance. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d review my efforts and share my experiences of the last six of weeks.
Brent East Campaigning: The campaign
In the tense 10 minutes that the candidates stood with the returning officer and inspected the doubtful ballot papers I was sharing my impressions of the campaign with Paul Keilthy from Archant Media Group.</description></item><item><title>Any Answers?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/08/any-answers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2005 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/08/any-answers/</guid><description>Germaine Greer has some advice for newly elected politicians - don&amp;rsquo;t wear little red suits. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to listen to the Radio 4 Any Answers stream of the show to hear it&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>A news round-up</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/a-news-round-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/a-news-round-up/</guid><description>Not awake at 415am? Shame as you missed Sarah&amp;rsquo;s victory speech! If you want to watch it you can thanks to the BBC.
Paul Palmer of the Evening Standard, who was having terrible trouble with his laptop when trying to submit his story, writes about the Brent East result. He focuses on Yasmin loosing rather than Sarah winning.
More later, when google news advises me of it!</description></item><item><title>Brent East - the morning after...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/brent-east-the-morning-after/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/brent-east-the-morning-after/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve posted over at Brent East Campaigning about yesterday, the election count and the result - take a peek.
Looks like the BELDs need to get their website updated&amp;hellip; no mention yet of Sarahs HOLD of Brent East.
From the Lib Dem website election news ticker:
04.12 GAIN - Sarah Teather wins the Brent East seat she won at a by-election (technically a gain measured from 2001) with a swing of 30% and a majority of 2,700</description></item><item><title>Sarah Teather Is STILL My MP</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/sarah-teather-is-still-my-mp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/sarah-teather-is-still-my-mp/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve woken up and eaten - needed to do that before posting anything. NK and I left the count after Sarah Teather had been returned as the MP for Brent East, but not before posting to sarah teather is my MP. I&amp;rsquo;ve still got the &amp;lsquo;wild eyes&amp;rsquo; I had yesterday, although that&amp;rsquo;s now from lack of sleep. This politics junkie had quite an Election Day.
As I posted yesterday, I&amp;rsquo;d been out and about in Mapesbury and Willesden with June Thomas from Slate Magazine.</description></item><item><title>Tally marks... .. .</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/tally-marks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/06/tally-marks/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m reminded of the Banksy piece in Barcelona Zoo. Tally mark after tally mark after tally mark. From what I&amp;rsquo;m seeing as I tally out the ballots as they come out of the box for the collate before the count, it really is neck and neck.
For every one vote the Greens receive, the Conservatives are getting seven, the Liberal Democrats 45 and Labour 47 = 100 votes.
Thats my personal tally count taken from a few different wards and averaged.</description></item><item><title>From the count....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/from-the-count/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 22:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/from-the-count/</guid><description>Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that I&amp;rsquo;d be at the count for the Brent constituencies General Election ballot. But strange things happen in blogsphere&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m joined by NK a friend from Goldsmiths. We&amp;rsquo;re surounded by more rosets than a horse show. It is a three legged&amp;hellip;sorry&amp;hellip;horse race (sorry Kwasi) after all!
Some of the ballot boxes have arrived already but the count isn&amp;rsquo;t fully underway.
Results as and when I get them!</description></item><item><title>Brent East 05/05/05</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/brent-east-050505/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/brent-east-050505/</guid><description>Out and about in Brent East this morning and all is quiet at Brent East Conservative HQ.
My first stop was Sarah Teather HQ at 1 High Road to give my support before going off to meet Sarah at her polling station.
Team:Yasmin are at Willesden Green tube, handing out leaflets that look like an inducement to shop at a furniture store (to be scanned later) before going off to vote.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Michele Weininger</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-michele-weininger/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-michele-weininger/</guid><description>The independent candidate for Brent East fighting for Justice for Motorists from the &amp;lsquo;totalitarian power machine&amp;rsquo;.
Here as a JPG</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Conservative</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-conservative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-conservative/</guid><description>The Blue team managed to get a photocopied A5 flyer delivered yesterday&amp;hellip;they must have had a few quid spare after buying all those billboards.
It&amp;rsquo;s a three legged race - Front / Back as JPGs</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/05/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>Recevied a letter from Ken Livingstone yesterday.
&amp;ldquo;If you thought I was right as the local MP to take an independent-minded approach then you will find that Yasmin stands firmly in that tradition&amp;rdquo;
Front page JPG - Back page JPG</description></item><item><title>Voting intentions</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/voting-intentions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/voting-intentions/</guid><description>I thought that the time had come to talk about my personal voting intentions for tomorrow, in case you havn&amp;rsquo;t guessed them already.
I was talking to E over supper this evening about voting for what you believe in. This reminded me of C of the Olive Tree on Willesden Lane and his view that the only vote that matters is vote of principle. And I agree with him, although if I lived in Lewisham Deptford, the constituency where my university is located, I&amp;rsquo;d be voting Green - tatical voting combining with principles.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Many!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-many/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-many/</guid><description>More from Kwasi Kwarteng!
More from Sarah Teather!
More from Team:Yasmin!
First piece of campaign materials from Michele Weininger!
And Archant Media Group, publishers of the Times series of local papers, lead with the headline &amp;lsquo;Appeal to Vote&amp;rsquo;. Although WTF Archant are doing partnering with Beacon Bingo and Paddy Power Bookmakers I do not know&amp;hellip;
All coming tomorrow&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Indecision in Queen's Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/indecision-in-queens-park/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/indecision-in-queens-park/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 02:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Received a letter from Charles Kennedy this morning urging me to vote because &amp;lsquo;in certain places, the election is effectively a straight choice between having a Liberal Democrat or a Labour MP&amp;rsquo;.
The real alternative has been distilled to four key points:
end student tuition and top-up fees prevent older people having to selltheir homes to pay for long term personal care provide 10,000 more police and cut their paperwork scrap the unfair council tax A little something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/04/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>Yasmin used her what will probably be the final electoral communication delivered by Royal Mail before the election to remind us that &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the economy, stupid!&amp;rsquo; Short of saying &amp;ldquo;if you value it, vote for it&amp;rdquo;, Yasmin talked about the low mortgage rates under Gorden Brown and the fall in unemployment from New Labour&amp;rsquo;s New Deal. The National Minimum Wage and other &amp;lsquo;redistributive&amp;rsquo; policies are mentioned. A few figures&amp;hellip; A dig at the Lib Dems&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-2/</guid><description>Received a letter from Charles Kennedy this morning urging me to vote because &amp;lsquo;in certain places, the election is effectively a straight choice between having a Liberal Democrat or a Labour MP&amp;rsquo;.
The real alternative has been distilled to four key points:
end student tuition and top-up fees prevent older people having to selltheir homes to pay for long term personal care provide 10,000 more police and cut their paperwork scrap the unfair council tax A little something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>Yasmin used her what will probably be the final electoral communication delivered by Royal Mail before the election to remind us that &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s the economy, stupid!&amp;rsquo; Short of saying &amp;ldquo;if you value it, vote for it&amp;rdquo;, Yasmin talked about the low mortgage rates under Gorden Brown and the fall in unemployment from New Labour&amp;rsquo;s New Deal. The National Minimum Wage and other &amp;lsquo;redistributive&amp;rsquo; policies are mentioned. A few figures&amp;hellip; A dig at the Lib Dems&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Charles Kennedy in Brent East</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/charles-kennedy-in-brent-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/charles-kennedy-in-brent-east/</guid><description>If you received a copy of Brent People from the Liberal Democrats over the weekend you&amp;rsquo;ll have seen this pic already.
More over at Brent East Campaigning</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Greens</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>I was speaking to Shahrar Ali last night about the Green campaign in Brent East and Brent South.
Something about a solar powered public address system playing a campaign song being cycled by tandem around the constituency. Anyone got any snaps?
I hope to be able to post an MP3 of the song here soon.
After speaking with Costas who owns the Olive Tree organic food store on Willesden Lane I&amp;rsquo;m becoming more convinced of the Green proposition.</description></item><item><title>Counting down... .. .</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/counting-down/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/counting-down/</guid><description>Today is May 3rd. It is 12:00. There are 47 hours of campaigning remaining until the polls open at 7am.
If you see any more campaign materials or meet any of the candidates out and about please let me know - blogger@robdyke.com.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats-3/</guid><description>A departure from the tabloid red top of Brent News, the latest campaign freesheet from the Lib Dems, Brent News, leads with the headline of &amp;lsquo;Sarah Set To Win&amp;rsquo; - naturally&amp;hellip;
It features a photo of the Liberal Democrat leader Charles Kennedy with Sarah Teather on Kilburn High Road. Good to see that when top &amp;lsquo;names&amp;rsquo; (to borrow the description Yasmin gave to the &amp;lsquo;top labour&amp;rsquo; people who have given her support) from the Lib Dems come to support their candidate it is their Leader and prospective Prime Minister that visits.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-labour-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-labour-2/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a scan of the Brent East Labour News &amp;lsquo;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Backing Yasmin&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; I picked up at Kilburn Station last week.
Front page - PDF file
Back page - PDF file</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Rainbow George</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-rainbow-george/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-rainbow-george/</guid><description>So, did you get your Preferendum from George &amp;lsquo;Rainbow&amp;rsquo; Weiss last week? You can&amp;rsquo;t have missed it: it was an A3 sheet of paper folded to A4 and covered with text. What was curious about the materials was the lack of photographs - no pic of Rainbow George, no pic of Tony Bush and George Blair.
A preferendum is an experiment in participatory democracy. The Vote for Yourself Rainbow Dream Ticket party is encouraging the electorate to vote not only for their candidate but also for the policies of the party should it be elected to form a government.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour - Quoting Andrew Gilligan!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/30/campaign-materials-labour-quoting-andrew-gilligan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2005 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/30/campaign-materials-labour-quoting-andrew-gilligan/</guid><description>The man who claimed that New Labour had &amp;lsquo;sexed up&amp;rsquo; the dossier on the threat possed to the United Kingdom by Sadam Hussain&amp;rsquo;s Iraq is being quoted by Yasmin Qureshi on her most recent campaign material.
Andrew Gilligan was writing in Friday 29th Evening Standard. I picked up the most recent flyer - literally, there were some floating around the platform at Kilburn, Jubilee Line - in the early evening on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/29/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2005 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/29/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>I commented that there would be more on the Labour Party Brent East News &amp;lsquo;Delivering For You&amp;rsquo;.
One thing I noticed was that Tony (Blair not Benn) doesn&amp;rsquo;t feature on the campaign material. There are three photos of Ken &amp;lsquo;Red&amp;rsquo; Livingstone - Labours prodigal son - and a photo of Tony Benn (Old &amp;lsquo;Old Labour&amp;rsquo; - sorry Tony) in that upright but slightly reclined pose that he does so well. Another Old Labour party member, Diane Abbot, is quoted in support of Yasmin.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Many!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/campaign-materials-many/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/campaign-materials-many/</guid><description>More campaign materials from Sarah Teather.
And George &amp;lsquo;Rainbow&amp;rsquo; Weiss&amp;rsquo;s Vote For Yourself Rainbow Dream Ticket Preferendum.
More photo analysis of Brent East News.
And a rumor of Team:Yasmin in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Café this lunch time&amp;hellip;
later&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>What else is there to notice about Brent East News &amp;lsquo;Delivering for YOU&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip;
I read the whole of the Ken Livingstone interview on the London Labour Party website. Campaigning in Brent East with Yasmin Qureshi Ken said:&amp;ldquo;I am delighted that my first election visit is in my old seat of Brent East, where human rights campaigner Yasmin Qureshi is in pole position to become Britain&amp;rsquo;s first ever Asian woman.&amp;rdquo;
The &amp;lsquo;round robin&amp;rsquo; makes four mentions of Yasmin&amp;rsquo;s ethnicity and gender.</description></item><item><title>Fifty extra police officers in Brent</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/fifty-extra-police-officers-in-brent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/27/fifty-extra-police-officers-in-brent/</guid><description>I picked up a copy of Brent East News published by Yasmin and the BE Labour Party when in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park on Monday. Under the headline &amp;lsquo;Delivering for You&amp;rsquo; there is a photo of three police officers with a caption &amp;lsquo;Brent now has more than fifty extra police officers&amp;rsquo;.
Fifty Extra Police on Brent streetsYasmin Qureshi&amp;rsquo;s police, beating round the bush.
Fifty extra police officers! Shame that three of the fifty extra police officers in Brent East are on walkabout in Shepherds Bush.</description></item><item><title>Hustings TONIGHT</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/hustings-tonight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/hustings-tonight/</guid><description>Brent Stop The War are holding a General Election Candidate Hustings&amp;hellip;
&amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;to answer your questions about where they stand on the invasion and occupation of Iraq, the withdrawal of troops and associated issues of Palestine, the “war on terror” and the attack on civil liberties.&amp;rsquo;
Here is the flyer.
It&amp;rsquo;ll be held at Dudden Hill Community Centre, TONIGHT 7.00 pm</description></item><item><title>Postal Voting Application Deadline Today</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/postal-voting-application-deadline-today/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/postal-voting-application-deadline-today/</guid><description>From Brent Council&amp;rsquo;s email alert service:
Postal Vote Application Deadline:
The deadline to apply for a new postal vote is Tuesday 26th April at 5pm.
Please make sure all applications have arrived at the Town Hall by that time.
You can deliver them in person should you wish.
Telephone 020 8937 1372 or e-mail using the link below if you need any assitance.
E-mail Electoral Services mailto:electoral.services@brent.gov.uk
Brent&amp;rsquo;s General Election Pages http://www.</description></item><item><title>Brondesbury Residents &amp;amp; Tennants Association Meeting</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/brondesbury-residents-tennants-association-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/26/brondesbury-residents-tennants-association-meeting/</guid><description>Chris, a reader of this blog, writes:
Hi Rob,
Maybe you were there tonight. If so, I&amp;rsquo;m wasting your time. If not, highlights included: Kwasi (who, incidentally, and I appreciate this is always the luck of the draw, is the only candidate I have seen campaigning in the streets) being compared to Boris Johnson; a nice Irish chap pointing out that some Candidate for Kilburn&amp;rsquo;s Beleaguered Motorists (really?</description></item><item><title>Crime</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2005 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/crime/</guid><description>The candidates from Labour, the Conservatives and the Liberal Democrats are all highlighting crime in their campaigns.
But do we need &amp;lsquo;more police on patrol to make our area safer for all&amp;rsquo;? (Sarah Teather - Standing Up For You) Has the fear of crime &amp;lsquo;increased&amp;rsquo; in Brent? (Kwasi Kwarteng - In Touch) Is &amp;lsquo;crime and the fear of crime and issue for every neighbourhood in London&amp;rsquo;? (Yasmin Qureshi - Mapesbury Labour News) If you&amp;rsquo;d like to see the crime statistics for Brent, the Met have great interactive map, but data looks better as text only.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Where do they all come from?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/campaign-materials-where-do-they-all-come-from/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2005 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/campaign-materials-where-do-they-all-come-from/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading up on the entitlement of a prospective parliamentary candidate to the use of Royal Mail delivery services.
In Brent East, a candidate is entitled to use Royal Mail to deliver 40907 items of campaign literature. What I&amp;rsquo;m not sure about is if that is in total (i.e. to all the households) or per &amp;lsquo;drop&amp;rsquo;.
There is further information on the Roayl Mail service to candidiate here. Or you could check out the Department of Consitiutional Affairs &amp;lsquo;guidance for electoral administrators and information on electoral legislation'.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2005 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/24/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>After yesterdays mammouth posting session I went out for a while. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had chance to even leave the building before my mind was drawn back to this blog. More campaign materials from Sarah Teather, local Liberal Democrat. This one an official &amp;lsquo;Election Communication&amp;rsquo; delivered by Royal Mail.
&amp;lsquo;Standing Up For You&amp;rsquo; highlights Sarah&amp;rsquo;s work during her term as MP for Brent East on local &amp;lsquo;quality of life&amp;rsquo; issues and links the Lib Dem policies to local &amp;lsquo;real people&amp;rsquo; through a varity of in-action photos.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Many postings to this blog today. It&amp;rsquo;s all I&amp;rsquo;ve done this morning!
I&amp;rsquo;ve received a letter from Sarah Teather for her campaign to be re-elected by the people of Brent East to serve a second term.
Her message: &amp;lsquo;I believe that people in Brent East deserve a local MP who will stand up to Tony Blair. I am proud to fight this election on my record of local action from fighting for fairer funding for our local schools to welcoming more police for Dudden Hill, Kilburn and Willesden Green.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Conservatives</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-conservatives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-conservatives/</guid><description>When I met Kwasi on Thursday at the MapRA AGM I mentioned to him that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen any campaign materials from him over the last couple of weeks. Yesterday an Election Communiation from Brent East Conservatives was delivered by Royal Mail.
His message: &amp;lsquo;The Conservatives are the alternative. I promise to give you, the electorate, my boss, more for your money. This isn&amp;rsquo;t some form of magic. Our policies are based on common sense.</description></item><item><title>Lack of campaign materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/lack-of-campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/lack-of-campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>On the back of the Mapesbury Labour News distributed by Yasmin at the MapRA Annual General Meeting there is a list of ways to contact Yasmin: By phone: 020 8969 4550, By email: info@yasminqureshi.co.uk, By writting to: 102 Liddell Gardens, Kensal Rise, NW10 3QE.
I checked out the domain www.yasminqureshi.co.uk to see if there was a website. I had hoped that there would be a vibrant source of information about Yasmin and the Labour Party but alas there was nothing but a holding page - &amp;quot; This website is currently under construction and will be available soon&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>At the Mapesbury Residents Association Annnual General Meeting on Thursday night I was hoping to speak to the assembled residents about the Community Wireless Network I am involved in running in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. Having been very impressed by the collective action that MapRA have motived in their community around the Mapesbury Dell project and the purchase of old-fashioned, sorry, &amp;lsquo;heritage&amp;rsquo; street lights for some of the streets, I thought that a Community Wireless Broadband Network would have been something that the residents of Mapesbury may have been interested in working to acheive.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Green Party</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>I received the Green Party Election Communication for Brent East earlier this week. I&amp;rsquo;ve scanned the 100% RECYCLED PAPER leaflet for you to download from here (front cover, inside, back cover).
If you have not received the Green Party Election Communication, please let me know and I will pass it on to Shahrar. I spoke to him yesterday and apparently there has been a problem with the delivery of the leaflets by Royal Mail.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury Residents Association AGM</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/mapesbury-residents-association-agm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/mapesbury-residents-association-agm/</guid><description>Those active in local civil society and engaged in their neighbourhood were out at St. Gabriel&amp;rsquo;s Church on Walm Lane on Thursday night for the Mapesbury Residents Association Annual General Meeting. MapRA is a large and active group of neighbours all commited to woking for the benefit of the Mapesbury community. Attendance from the membership of MapRA is good and the nave of church was full.
I had expected to see Sarah Teather there: She was there last year, speaking on some of the activities that she, as the local MP, had beeen working on with MapRA and other people from the neighbouorhood.</description></item><item><title>C4.com on Brent East</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/21/c4com-on-brent-east/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2005 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/21/c4com-on-brent-east/</guid><description>From Channel 4.com Election 2005 site.
&amp;lsquo;Labour has placed its hopes on lawyer Yasmin Qureishi, who is openly anti-war in her selection process. But like many Labour candidates in what was Labour&amp;rsquo;s urban core support she is going even further to regain disgruntled voters by opposing the policies of the prime minister.
She told Channel 4 news: “I’m one of those people who has their own mind, their own independent mind, and I make my own decisions.</description></item><item><title>Linkup for George 'Rainbow' Weiss</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/21/linkup-for-george-rainbow-weiss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2005 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/21/linkup-for-george-rainbow-weiss/</guid><description>Thanks to a reader, here are some links for the Vote For Yourself Dream Ticket Party and George &amp;lsquo;Rainbox&amp;rsquo; Weiss.
This website details the background to the V4YDTP.
While this page has DTP info.
Links from a reader collecting campaign leaflets from this election. Send them some of the paper the Brent East Candidates send you.
The Guardian website also lists George &amp;lsquo;Rainbow&amp;rsquo; Weiss, but not as a candidate in this election (they need to get that page of their site updated).</description></item><item><title>How will you convince Brent voters to give you another term as MP?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/20/how-will-you-convince-brent-voters-to-give-you-another-term-as-mp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2005 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/20/how-will-you-convince-brent-voters-to-give-you-another-term-as-mp/</guid><description>In December 2003, Simon Ellis interviewed Sarah for myBrent.co.uk.
You can read the full interview here. What interested me was Sarah&amp;rsquo;s answer to this final question: How will you convince Brent voters to give you another term as MP?
&amp;ldquo;I am going to have to work extremely hard over the next two years because many people voted for me partly on a protest. Some people voted for me because our policies but some people also voted against Tony Blair and I am going to need to persuade those people that there are positive reasons for voting for me.</description></item><item><title>Candidate List Announced</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/20/candidate-list-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2005 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/20/candidate-list-announced/</guid><description>The candidates in the Brent East constituency have been announced. They are:
ALI, Shahrar - Green Party KWARTENG, Kwasi Alfred Addo - The Conservative Party Candidate QURESHI, Yasmin - The Labour Party Candidate TEATHER, Sarah Louise - Liberal Democrats WEININGER, Michele Anna - Independent WEISS, &amp;lsquo;Rainbow&amp;rsquo; George - Vote for Yourself Rainbow Dream Ticket I&amp;rsquo;m going to try and get hold of web links for George &amp;lsquo;Rainbow&amp;rsquo; Weiss and Michele Anna Weininger today.</description></item><item><title>Hustings this evening.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/19/hustings-this-evening/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2005 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/19/hustings-this-evening/</guid><description>Sarah Teather - and others? who knows? - will be at a hustings event this evening at Willesden Library organised by BRAVA - Brent Association for Voluntary Action.
If anyone who reads this blog goes to the hustings this evening, please write-up about it here.</description></item><item><title>Where are the Conservatives?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/19/where-are-the-conservatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2005 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/19/where-are-the-conservatives/</guid><description>Since starting this blog I have met the candidiates from Labour, Greens and Liberal Democrats &amp;lsquo;out and about&amp;rsquo; in Brent East. I&amp;rsquo;m still waiting to see Kwasi out and about&amp;hellip; Strange not to have seen the Conservatives. During the by-election of &amp;lsquo;03 they were very visible in this constituency - I remember vividly meeting three party workers on Exeter Road who, after I had asked them for some of their campaign materials, cornered me to drill in their message.</description></item><item><title>While on the subject of voting records....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/while-on-the-subject-of-voting-records/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2005 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/while-on-the-subject-of-voting-records/</guid><description>You can view the voting record of Sarah Teather as complied by The Guardian and Public Whip.</description></item><item><title>Postal voting in Brent East</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/postal-voting-in-brent-east/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2005 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/postal-voting-in-brent-east/</guid><description>Applications for postal voting in Brent East are up 511% on the 2001 General Election. Around 2500 votes in Brent East will be made by post this year.
You can read more on postal voting in London in this story from thisislondon.co.uk</description></item><item><title>Don't mention the war?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/dont-mention-the-war/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2005 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/18/dont-mention-the-war/</guid><description>The Guardian comment on the &amp;lsquo;sssshhhh&amp;rsquo; today. You know, that little exercise in Middle East. They say that &amp;lsquo;Many in Tony Blair&amp;rsquo;s party who opposed the US-led invasion are keeping quiet about the issue now&amp;rsquo;.
&amp;lsquo;However, candidates are mentioning their anti-war positions in constituencies where there has been strong opposition to the conflict, for example, in constituencies with large Muslim communities or student populations.
Yasmin Qureshi, the Labour candidate for Brent East, has not hidden her opposition.</description></item><item><title>Calling all candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/17/calling-all-candidates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2005 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/17/calling-all-candidates/</guid><description>An open letter, to be emailed to each of the candidates standing in Brent East at the forthcoming general election.
Dear Candidate,
I am writing to all the candidates standing in Brent East at the general election with a question. Each party has unveiled their manifesto. National commitments have been made for the program of the next government, which ever colour it ends up being.
Assume you and your party are elected at the next election and you are able to carry out your commitments to the nation.</description></item><item><title>Meeting Shahrar Ali</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/meeting-shahrar-ali/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2005 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/meeting-shahrar-ali/</guid><description>&amp;hellip; coming soon&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Strategic Voter - Info for London</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/strategic-voter-info-for-london/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2005 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/strategic-voter-info-for-london/</guid><description>Strategic Voter has a PDF detailing their recommendations for voting accross London. For Brent East their recommendation is Vote Lib Dem.</description></item><item><title>There’s an election on...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/theres-an-election-on/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2005 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/theres-an-election-on/</guid><description>&amp;hellip;or had you&amp;rsquo;d missed that?
I want to share the Brent East campaign experience from the point of view of the electorate. And I want to distribute information about the candidates and the parties standing in Brent East to my neighbours in this constituency. So until the 6th of May, when the hangover is gone and the lost sleep caught up on, I&amp;rsquo;ll put most of my posting efforts into &amp;lsquo;Brent East Campaigning&amp;rsquo;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Green Party</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2005 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Front Page - JPG
Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Back Page - JPG</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Greens</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2005 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Front Page - JPG
Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Back Page - JPG</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Labour</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-labour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2005 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-labour/</guid><description>Here are some campaign materials from the Labour Party for their candidate Yasmin Qureshi. I won&amp;rsquo;t display them all here, but you can click on the links to see full size scans of the unsolicited mail that has popped through my letter box in support of their candidate.
Elect Yasmin Qureshi - A5 flyer - front - JPG
Elect Yasmin Qureshi - A5 flyer - back - JPG
Brent East News - Labour Party - front page - JPG</description></item><item><title>Meeting Yasmin Qureshi</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/09/meeting-yasmin-qureshi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2005 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/09/meeting-yasmin-qureshi/</guid><description>On Thursday I bumped into Yasmin Qureshi, the Labour candidate for Brent East, on Salusbury Road just outside the friendly and well stocked Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Books (yes, I do work there, how did you guess?). She was out on the campaign trail, meeting and greeting, probably kissing babies, seeking places to display her posters. Yasmin was accompanied by the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward local Councillor Neil Nerva.
I&amp;rsquo;ve met Neil Nerva before.</description></item><item><title>Fear and Loathing on the Brent East Campaign Trail</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/fear-and-loathing-on-the-brent-east-campaign-trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/fear-and-loathing-on-the-brent-east-campaign-trail/</guid><description>05.05.05 said the Indy.
General erection said The Sun.
and they are off.
I&amp;rsquo;ve already met the candidates for the Greens and for Labour out on the streets of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. I&amp;rsquo;ll share these two encounters with you over this weekend.
Campaign materials from the Lib Dems and Labour to come - just as soon as i&amp;rsquo;ve got my image hosting problem sorted.</description></item><item><title>Brent East Campaign Trail</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/brent-east-campaign-trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/brent-east-campaign-trail/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started to blog the Brent East constituency election campaign. I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing all the paper propaganda distributed by candidates over the coming four weeks. Wide open for all the see. Informed choice facilitated.
I&amp;rsquo;ve met two of the candidates already, well three, as I&amp;rsquo;ve met Sarah Teather too. More to share on that score soon.</description></item><item><title>Showing the paper trail...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/showing-the-paper-trail/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/showing-the-paper-trail/</guid><description>Election 2005. You know its coming. I know its coming. It has been trailed more heavily than a Lord of the Rings movie. You probably think its all happened already given the amount of comment and analysis in the media. Slow news year?
Because of my own interest in seeing increased participation from citizens in the upcoming election, I&amp;rsquo;m running another blog between now and &amp;lsquo;the day&amp;rsquo; focusing on the Brent East campaign.</description></item></channel></rss>