<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Green Party on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/green-party/</link><description>Recent content in Green Party on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:48:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/green-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brent Council - Labour Gain from NOC</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</guid><description>Over on the Brent Greens Blog, Shahrar Ali has posted a write up the results for the candidates at the Local Elections. The Greens stood the maximum number of candiates in each of the 20 wards in Brent and many of the candidates clocked up, several hundred votes, even reaching 840 votes in Kilburn.
The Local Election results 08/05/2010 from Brent Council.
Lab - 40 (21 seats gained)
Lib - 17 (10 seats lost)</description></item><item><title>Start the countdown...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/24/start-the-countdown/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/24/start-the-countdown/</guid><description>&lt;p>News that &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/americas/7261670.stm" title="BBC News item">Ralph Nader has announced plans to run again for the US presidency&lt;/a> got me googling like crazy this afternoon&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Just to share with you the &lt;a href="http://gnn.tv/videos/4/Countdown" title="GNN website">&amp;ldquo;Beastie Boy Ad Rock’s remix of Green Party Presidential candidate Ralph Nader&lt;/a>’s blistering critique of the news media and the current state of American politics.&amp;rdquo; Posted to the Guerrilla News Network (GNN).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Turn it up.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solar Panels in a conservation area</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/28/solar-panels-in-a-conservation-area/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 02:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/28/solar-panels-in-a-conservation-area/</guid><description>You may have read a letter in the Kilburn Times from a residents in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park questioning the sanity of planning regulations that prevent people from moving towards renewable energy. I bumped into Rupet Degas from the Brent and Harrow Green Party in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park yesterday and he nearly split our sides laughing at the lack of joined up thinking. This morning he forwarded me a reply he wrote that has, as yet, not been published by the paper.</description></item><item><title>Brent Green Party in Queen&amp;#039;s Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/brent-green-party-in-queens-park/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 17:50:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/brent-green-party-in-queens-park/</guid><description>The local Greens have been distributing their literature in the wards. They have also made the literature available online so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to scan it I can link to it from here.
here you go.
Note that Shahrar Ali, candidate in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park, will appear in the the Green Party Election Broadcast on BBC 1 tomorrow (APR24) at 1845.</description></item><item><title>Queen's Park Tower Plan</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</guid><description>The proposal for the tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park is a lead topic for each of the parties contesting the electoral ward of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. For Labour it is getting like the Monty Python topic not to be mentioned in front of our hosts for the World Cup. The Lib Dems have made great gains from this thread - well, a sitting (yet not restanding) Councillor defected to Team Yellow with the tower plan as a key issue.</description></item><item><title>QP Green&amp;#039;s letters on tower block development</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 14:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</guid><description>I noticed these letters written by Dr Shahrar Ali, Green Party candidate for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park along with Rupert Degas, to Brent area newspapers recently.
On Brent Labour Council tower block imperatives:&amp;quot;Whilst this may not come as a revelation to seasoned campaigners, the public admission is a sign of desperation: a local government that denies responsibility for actions that it is going to take on our behalf but against our will.&amp;ldquo;On the timing of the planning process:</description></item><item><title>Will Brent Vote Blue and Go Green?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/will-brent-vote-blue-and-go-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 14:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/will-brent-vote-blue-and-go-green/</guid><description>Are you serious?
Each day I walk from Mapesbury to Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park via Brondesbury/Kilburn wards - sounds like a round about route but I&amp;rsquo;m just walking cross the boundry corners. In contrast to the General Election last year there are not many posters out on display in gardens and in the shop windows in support of ANY political party up for election in May. However I have noticed that of the posters that are on display the Green&amp;rsquo;s and the Liberal Democrats have strong support.</description></item><item><title>Green Party Candidates in Queen&amp;#039;s Park ward.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/green-party-candidates-in-queens-park-ward/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 06:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/green-party-candidates-in-queens-park-ward/</guid><description>Everyone, meet Shahrar Ali and Rupert Degas.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Greens</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/03/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>I was speaking to Shahrar Ali last night about the Green campaign in Brent East and Brent South.
Something about a solar powered public address system playing a campaign song being cycled by tandem around the constituency. Anyone got any snaps?
I hope to be able to post an MP3 of the song here soon.
After speaking with Costas who owns the Olive Tree organic food store on Willesden Lane I&amp;rsquo;m becoming more convinced of the Green proposition.</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Green Party</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2005 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/23/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>I received the Green Party Election Communication for Brent East earlier this week. I&amp;rsquo;ve scanned the 100% RECYCLED PAPER leaflet for you to download from here (front cover, inside, back cover).
If you have not received the Green Party Election Communication, please let me know and I will pass it on to Shahrar. I spoke to him yesterday and apparently there has been a problem with the delivery of the leaflets by Royal Mail.</description></item><item><title>Meeting Shahrar Ali</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/meeting-shahrar-ali/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2005 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/13/meeting-shahrar-ali/</guid><description>&amp;hellip; coming soon&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Green Party</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2005 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Front Page - JPG
Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Back Page - JPG</description></item></channel></rss>