<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brent Council on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-council/</link><description>Recent content in Brent Council on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 17:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-council/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brent Council Tax : £15m to increase collection rates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/24/brent-council-tax/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 17:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/24/brent-council-tax/</guid><description>Brent Council recently signed a deal with Crapita Business Services for council tax and business rates administration and IT support systems. Reported to be worth £15m over 5 years, the function of the contract is to increase the council tax collection rate, with Crapita giving a guaranteed a collection rate for council tax and an anticipated £4.6 million in savings for the Council over the initial term of the contract.</description></item><item><title>Licensing Committee - part two.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/12/licensing-committee-part-two/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/12/licensing-committee-part-two/</guid><description>Brent Council must be expecting numbers as the hearing. The Licensing Committee has got the main chamber for tonight&amp;rsquo;s session.</description></item><item><title>Brent council to allow residents to manage their personal data.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/03/24/brent-council-to-allow-residents-to-manage-their-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 11:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/03/24/brent-council-to-allow-residents-to-manage-their-personal-data/</guid><description>Brent council says use of Mydex&amp;rsquo;s online personal data service will improve the quality of information it holds on us residents, allowing us to see if the information Brent holds on them is up to date and accurate.
Mydex’s mission is to help individuals realise the value of their personal data. They do this by providing individuals with Personal Data Stores and related services. Personal Data Stores help individuals gather, store, manage, use and share the information they need to manage their lives better.</description></item><item><title>Attendance at Council Committees.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/02/08/attendance-at-council-committees/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/02/08/attendance-at-council-committees/</guid><description>A new record set at Brent Town Hall for a sub-committee meeting. 70 or more local residents present for Licensing Committee hearing on the extension of the License of the Herritage Inn.
Just a quick post while the Councillors get legal advice on the adjournment request from the applicant.</description></item><item><title>Out with the old, in with new.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/06/17/out-with-the-old-in-with-new/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/06/17/out-with-the-old-in-with-new/</guid><description>New signing at Cricklewood library now that Brent Archive has moved out.
Any chance of new planting too?</description></item><item><title>Brent Council - Labour Gain from NOC</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</guid><description>Over on the Brent Greens Blog, Shahrar Ali has posted a write up the results for the candidates at the Local Elections. The Greens stood the maximum number of candiates in each of the 20 wards in Brent and many of the candidates clocked up, several hundred votes, even reaching 840 votes in Kilburn.
The Local Election results 08/05/2010 from Brent Council.
Lab - 40 (21 seats gained)
Lib - 17 (10 seats lost)</description></item><item><title>Local elections in the shadow?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/03/local-elections-in-the-shadow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 10:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/03/local-elections-in-the-shadow/</guid><description>﻿﻿&amp;quot;The local elections are in the shadow of the general election,&amp;quot; said Andrew Stunell, chair of the Liberal Democrats' local election campaign team, reports the Beeb. Locally, the Labour team are focused the parliamentary campaign. What little local material they have published and distributed has been discredited and retracted. The Lib Dems are emphasizing the local campaign, highlighting the work of Lib Dem councillors in the wards.
Mapesbury - Brent Lib Dems The local election promises to be more exciting than the race for Brent Central.</description></item><item><title>List of candidates for Brent Council wards.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/09/list-of-candidates-for-brent-council-wards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 06:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/09/list-of-candidates-for-brent-council-wards/</guid><description>The deadline for nominations closed at midday on 8 April 2010 and details of the candidates for the local elections are available in this PDF, published on 9 April. A PDF? Have Brent Council learned nothing about publishing information online? I&amp;rsquo;ll rework the list and make it nice and human-readable without having to download a PDF!</description></item><item><title>Fix My Street</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/11/fix-my-street/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 14:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/11/fix-my-street/</guid><description>Local residents group North West Two are now using Fix My Street to file reports with Brent Council. I&amp;rsquo;ll be working with the other residents groups in my area to get links to FMS on all the community websites I can.
Fix My Street (FMS) is A LOT faster and easier than using the Brent Council reporting system. All I need to do to report via FMS is enter the street name, choose the right street and then write up the problem.</description></item><item><title>Dollis Hill House renewal project in jeopardy</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/10/dollis-hill-house-renewal-project-in-jeopardy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 09:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/10/dollis-hill-house-renewal-project-in-jeopardy/</guid><description>News earlier this year was that the Heritage Lottery Fund announced stage 1 funding towards a grant of £1.2 million to help restore Dollis Hill House. This would have enabled Dollis Hill House Trust (DHHT) to work with Training For Life and Brent Council to annex a section of a public park for pseudo-social-enterprise, or, in the words of the DHH, to bring about the &amp;ldquo;commercial exploitation of the house’s prime and dramatic location, balanced with a positive vision of the house’s future as a cohesive focus for the growing and increasingly diverse population of the surrounding area.</description></item><item><title>More booze on the Broadway - respond now!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/more-booze-on-the-broadway-respond-now/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 14:50:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/more-booze-on-the-broadway-respond-now/</guid><description>The NW2 residents association is alerting local residents to an application for a 24h license for the sale of alcohol by a new business opening on the broadway. The former New Heights Furniture Shop in Cricklewood Broadway has been taken over by a supermarket called Way–2–Save. They have a branch in Neasden which has very good range of food, fresh fruit and veg and a halal butchers which would add to the choices for supermarket shopping in the area in a positive way.</description></item><item><title>Stonebridge candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 14:05:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</guid><description>With the candidates nominated for the Stonebridge by-election, here&amp;rsquo;s a little summary of them for you:
ALADESHE, Funmi The Conservative Party COX, Sarah Respect ORR, Brian Green Party VAN KALWALA, Zaffar The Labour Party WILTSHIRE, Sandra Elina Liberal Democrats If you receive any literature from the campaign teams out and about in Stonebridge ward, please scan it and email it to me and I'll put it online here for all to see.</description></item><item><title>"Happy voting" ???</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 08:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</guid><description>Is &amp;ldquo;Happy voting!&amp;rdquo; really the proper way to close an email announcing a Council By-election? Anyway&amp;hellip;
A seat has become vacant in the Stonebridge Ward following the death of Councillor Dorman Long. A by-election will be held on Thursday, 13 September 2007 to elect a new representative.
The by-election gives the Lib Dems another opportunity to win a seat - but will they win it? I doubt it. Stonebridge ward is a Labour heartland - you only have to look at the votes cast in the 2006 Local Election to see that&amp;hellip; Winning this single seat will not change the overall political balance of Brent Council: The Lib Dems would need to win a few more by-elections or benefit from defections (not for the first time in Brent&amp;rsquo;s recent political history) in order to be in a position to leave the alliance with the Conservatives and lead a majority administration.</description></item><item><title>Electoral Canvassing 2007</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/03/electoral-canvassing-2007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/03/electoral-canvassing-2007/</guid><description>The 2007 Electoral Canvass is about to start. Once again we must all update our details on the Electoral Register. Failure to do so can lead to a fine of up to £1,000. Now that is what I call an incentive!
Electoral Canvassing - Your Questions Answered.
Posted after receiving a notification from Brent Council Electoral Services department.</description></item><item><title>Freedom of Information</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/21/freedom-of-information/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 05:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/21/freedom-of-information/</guid><description>After reading (and posting) Shahrar&amp;rsquo;s email I got thinking about what other information about parking and PCNs issued I could request from Brent Council under FoI.
How many of us have been issued a ticket because of a simple honest mistake, like, say, scratching off the wrong day on a parking voucher in error, or perhaps forgetting to note your registration on a temporary residents permit? Well that&amp;rsquo;s me on both counts.</description></item><item><title>Parking tickets in Brent and the FoI Act</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/21/parking-tickets-in-brent-and-the-foi-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 05:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/21/parking-tickets-in-brent-and-the-foi-act/</guid><description>&lt;p>Shahrar Ali, a Green Party candidate at both this years local and last years national elections, sent me an email yesterday on a topic important to car-owners - Penalty Charge Notices, or, rather, f&amp;rsquo;ing-tickets, as I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of us refer to them. Shahrar told me about meeting Brent residents while campaigning during the local elections and a common gripe that came up - being issued with a ticket on a public holiday.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He writes:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Trouble is, &amp;ldquo;Restrictions apply on Bank Holidays&amp;rdquo; signage is to be found only on some of the posts as one enters the zone. But most people, reasonably in my view, take their cue from the signage in the bays - which without any explicit indication to the contrary they will assume does not apply on public holidays.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Brent can&amp;rsquo;t have it both ways. Had the assumption not been justified there would hardly be a need for the additional signage. The trouble is these signs are not fit for purpose, ie. noticeable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What&amp;rsquo;s at issue? Nobody likes to get a fine at the best of times, but the suspicion is that signage has been erected to maximise the chances of catching people out and making a quick buck. That&amp;rsquo;s dishonest and only fuels resentment towards local government - increasing cynicsm and eroding trust in public or democratic institutions, moreover.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SKNDC community network ideas</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/skndc-community-network-ideas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 08:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/skndc-community-network-ideas/</guid><description>Last year SKNDC advertised for interested parties to propose solutions for a wireless network project in South Kilburn. Comwifinet responded and we won the work. Yet the project was shelved as the budget for ICT in the Home ran out.
SKFM, the community radio station broadcasting from the NDC area, is currently streaming to listeners over the internet. Listening to the stream reminded me of the community network project and I&amp;rsquo;ve begun to make contact with SKNDC again.</description></item><item><title>civic reporter developments</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-developments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 07:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-developments/</guid><description>early last week I met with two people from Brent Council Environment &amp;amp; Culture Department to discuss the Civic Reporter ideas and application framework that Comwifinet have been working on. A great opportunity to discuss how open accessible data could further develop participation in the up keep of the Borough. Brent Council considering working with a Made In Brent technology organisation and mobile technologies. Brent Council entertaining the public publishing daily status and performance information online.</description></item><item><title>civic reporter - background</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-background/</guid><description>The background to all this. Comwifinet had prototyped the Civic Reporter framework which is inspired by other innovative mobile technology projects, such as that implemented by Lewisham and the mySociety &amp;lsquo;Broken Civic Infrastructure&amp;rsquo; idea. These similar initiatives all start from the question &amp;lsquo;Would putting pictures of abandoned cars on a map on the internet help people to think again about their role in maintaining a tidy Borough?
[The background to all this.</description></item><item><title>FUD review for July</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/08/fud-review-for-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2006 07:35:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/08/fud-review-for-july/</guid><description>FUD? Check wikipedia&amp;hellip;
Received the first campaign materials from Team Yellow Gold and Team Red since the elections for local government in May. Sorry for the blue tint on the scans, I think my scanner is broken.
The BELD are thanking people for voting for them in Mapesbury and give people the contact numbers of their new local councillors. I won&amp;rsquo;t reprint them here though - surely you can get them from Brent Council (after 6 or 7 clicks) or from the BELD website (well actually you can&amp;rsquo;t find any info about your local councillors or FOCUS TEAM on the BELD website).</description></item><item><title>cat robdyke | grep ‘recent activity’</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/04/cat-robdyke-grep-recent-activity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 13:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/08/04/cat-robdyke-grep-recent-activity/</guid><description>Civic reporter has received an initial &amp;lsquo;thanks but no thanks&amp;rsquo; from Brent Council. I&amp;rsquo;m going to post their analysis of the application and my reponse here. this morning I was at home with the baby. I love being at home in the day, it gives me the chance to stand and watch my neighbourhood go by. I counted five Brent Council branded vehicles go past my house, collecting my green box, then my green bin and later my household wheelie bin.</description></item><item><title>in The Eye this fortnight</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/06/25/in-the-eye-this-fortnight/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2006 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/06/25/in-the-eye-this-fortnight/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;- IT upgraded in Brent – so council staff can discuss the world cup online&amp;rdquo; - maybe the Council and BRAVA will find the resources to support The Bonnet Project so residents associations and community groups can communicate with each other online.</description></item><item><title>civic reporter</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/06/21/civic-reporter-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2006 21:19:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/06/21/civic-reporter-2/</guid><description>hush! here&amp;rsquo;s a sneek on something I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on at comwifinet recently&amp;hellip;
Spot it? Text it! - report things to Brent Council via SMS and MMS. What things? a faulty parking meter, fly-tipping, broken things in the environment that you see out and about. Here is the opportunity to report them as you see them&amp;hellip; using your mobile phone.</description></item><item><title>The Teather Factor</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/13/the-teather-factor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2006 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/13/the-teather-factor/</guid><description>Speaking on the &amp;lsquo;carnage&amp;rsquo; following the local elections in Brent, Labour Cllr Mary Arnold acknowledges that Team Yellow worked hard for the victories they knotched up:
&amp;ldquo;There is also the Teather factor - there&amp;rsquo;s a machinery that the Lib Dems have got for producing leaflets and campaigning, for bringing people in to canvass.&amp;rdquo;
The Lib Dems did manage to distribute a lot of paper in Mapesbury and Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park - significantly more than teams Red and Blue.</description></item><item><title>Updates at brent.gov</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/updates-at-brentgov/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 05:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/updates-at-brentgov/</guid><description>I wanted to post this when I got home from the count early this morning but the brent.gov webserver had broken and was not serving the Election Pages. 404errr. That and they were still counting when I got home. And recounting no doubt. You can get the full results for all the candidates in each ward direct from brent.gov.uk as they are uploaded.</description></item><item><title>Big Brother Brent</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/big-brother-brent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 07:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/big-brother-brent/</guid><description> Big Brother Election Poster</description></item><item><title>is the veil intact?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/is-the-veil-intact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/is-the-veil-intact/</guid><description>Electoral law prevents a council from promoting candidates standing in local elections. Has the spirit of the &amp;lsquo;purdah&amp;rsquo; period been broken by Brent Council? The Brent Lib Dems seem to think so. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve not yet seen the article in question, my copy of the Brent Magazine has been sitting unread since it arrived and usually only gets a slight glance before being recycled. I&amp;rsquo;ll get a scan and post it.</description></item><item><title>Mapesbury is All Action!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/mapesbury-is-all-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/25/mapesbury-is-all-action/</guid><description>&lt;p>Noticed more people in yellow safety jackets walking around the streets recently? On Friday last week I saw a member of the Brent Council Street Care team out ward walking in Mapesbury. He was monitoring the recycling collection from both the kerb side boxes and the green wheelie bins - check we residents were using the service and using it correctly? checking up on the contractors? don&amp;rsquo;t know - either way his purpose was to be highly visible in the ward. Suit, yellow jacket, Brent Council Street Care printed on the back in big letters? A visibility exercise in the ward prior to the ward hustings tomorrow and the Mapesbury Residents Associations (MAPRA) Annual General Meeting?That&amp;rsquo;s probably just the skeptic in me&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;but then this afternoon&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>in development</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/in-development/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 12:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/in-development/</guid><description>currently working on some mapping extensions to the Brent East Campaigning website. I plan to show a map of the Borough of Brent and to overlay various political informations such as the elected representatives for the wards both at local and national level. I&amp;rsquo;ll begin with a map and just mash in some datasources that I will build myself. I need to build them by hand as Brent Council supply only a limited amount of information in machine readable format and what is made available in not geo-coded so it is unknown where the information refers to.</description></item><item><title>QP Greens letters on tower block development</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 14:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</guid><description>I noticed these letters written by Dr Shahrar Ali, Green Party candidate for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park along with Rupert Degas, to Brent area newspapers recently.
On Brent Labour Council tower block imperatives:
&amp;ldquo;Whilst this may not come as a revelation to seasoned campaigners, the public admission is a sign of desperation: a local government that denies responsibility for actions that it is going to take on our behalf but against our will.</description></item><item><title>opening up brent council</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/11/opening-up-brent-council/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/11/opening-up-brent-council/</guid><description>brent council collect and publish lots and lots of information. i&amp;rsquo;m not talking about informtion that is about a person, like say census or tax information. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in the information that Brent Council spend a lot of time and money on collecting and verifying and organisaing and publishing about local organisations and projects, events and activities. and I&amp;rsquo;d like to get at it !
Brent Council publish the Brent Magazine and also the Brent Brain website.</description></item><item><title>oh, and there is an election on</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/oh-and-there-is-an-election-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 20:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/oh-and-there-is-an-election-on/</guid><description>4th May. Elections for all seats on Brent Council.</description></item></channel></rss>