<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Council Tax on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/council-tax/</link><description>Recent content in Council Tax on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 17:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/council-tax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brent Council Tax : £15m to increase collection rates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/24/brent-council-tax/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 17:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/04/24/brent-council-tax/</guid><description>Brent Council recently signed a deal with Crapita Business Services for council tax and business rates administration and IT support systems. Reported to be worth £15m over 5 years, the function of the contract is to increase the council tax collection rate, with Crapita giving a guaranteed a collection rate for council tax and an anticipated £4.6 million in savings for the Council over the initial term of the contract.</description></item><item><title>Brent News from the Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 17:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</guid><description>This local red top was delivered in late February. It leads with the news of the Liberal Democrats delivering a &amp;ldquo;hammer blow&amp;rdquo; to Labour&amp;rdquo; in Dunfermline by-election.
The national political story was the continued opposition to the ID card legislation by Sarah Teather and the Liberal Democrats. The newsletter also covered the story of the comments made by Labour Cllr Jonathan Davies on the &amp;lsquo;consultation&amp;rsquo; over the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Tower plans.</description></item><item><title>the lib dems stand up for us</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/the-lib-dems-stand-up-for-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/the-lib-dems-stand-up-for-us/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;the lib dems stand up for us&amp;rdquo; ? well it is a Brent Lib Dem flyer&amp;hellip; this flyer arrived in either late Feb or early March - the trail started early for the BELD team.
The update lacks focus - there are a lot of different things crammed ontoa doublesided sheet of A4. Quality of life/local environment make the agenda again - also mentioned is that the lib dems want to focus council tax receipts on public services, sports facilities and public toliets - with disabled access?</description></item></channel></rss>