<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Elections on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/elections/</link><description>Recent content in Elections on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:48:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/elections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brent Council - Labour Gain from NOC</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/10/brent-council-labour-gain-from-noc/</guid><description>Over on the Brent Greens Blog, Shahrar Ali has posted a write up the results for the candidates at the Local Elections. The Greens stood the maximum number of candiates in each of the 20 wards in Brent and many of the candidates clocked up, several hundred votes, even reaching 840 votes in Kilburn.
The Local Election results 08/05/2010 from Brent Council.
Lab - 40 (21 seats gained)
Lib - 17 (10 seats lost)</description></item><item><title>ULU Elects!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/27/ulu-elects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 11:25:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/27/ulu-elects/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to suffer election fatigue what with GCSU, America, shortly London and ULU as well. Well damm representative governance, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say.
ULU do get several points awarded for a sensible and secure electronic voting mechanism. You can vote from this page, online and confidentialy, assuming that you have got a username and password that have been emailed to your ULU College Email account.
How did they do such a thing you may ask&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Some colleges in the UoL will provide ULU with a database of the students who are eligible to vote in the elections from that college.</description></item><item><title>How I would have rigged the Goldsmiths College Student Elections...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/26/how-i-would-have-rigged-the-goldsmiths-college-student-elections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 10:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/26/how-i-would-have-rigged-the-goldsmiths-college-student-elections/</guid><description>&lt;p>How I would have rigged the Goldsmiths College Student Elections and some recommendations for the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are many ways of rigging an election and, with increased abstraction and dispersal of the act of voting, influencing the outcome of ballots gets easier and easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s just think for a moment what takes place when a student votes. First of all, the student needs to be co-present with the ballot! This is a given and the only part of the process that can not be virtualised. The student presents some ID before being given a ballot paper. The ballot is privately completed and cast into the ballot box.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Goldsmiths College Students Election e-Voting was extremely vulnerable to exploitation by someone with malicious intent. The e-voting mechanism virtualised the ballot paper instead of virtualising the whole process. Anyone visiting the goldsmithsstudents.com website was able to download a Microsoft Word file. This file used a macro to capture the input of the user; in this case the ranking of the preference of candidates. A student was expected to complete the form, save it, then send the file as an attachment from their college email account to &lt;span class="Object" id="OBJ_PREFIX_DWT713">&lt;a href="mailto:su@gold.ac.uk">su@gold.ac.uk&lt;/a>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The most vulnerable part of the whole process is that &lt;strong>single file&lt;/strong> made available for public download.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Start the countdown...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/24/start-the-countdown/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/24/start-the-countdown/</guid><description>&lt;p>News that &lt;a href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/americas/7261670.stm" title="BBC News item">Ralph Nader has announced plans to run again for the US presidency&lt;/a> got me googling like crazy this afternoon&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Just to share with you the &lt;a href="http://gnn.tv/videos/4/Countdown" title="GNN website">&amp;ldquo;Beastie Boy Ad Rock’s remix of Green Party Presidential candidate Ralph Nader&lt;/a>’s blistering critique of the news media and the current state of American politics.&amp;rdquo; Posted to the Guerrilla News Network (GNN).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Turn it up.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Stonebridge candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 14:05:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</guid><description>With the candidates nominated for the Stonebridge by-election, here&amp;rsquo;s a little summary of them for you:
ALADESHE, Funmi The Conservative Party COX, Sarah Respect ORR, Brian Green Party VAN KALWALA, Zaffar The Labour Party WILTSHIRE, Sandra Elina Liberal Democrats If you receive any literature from the campaign teams out and about in Stonebridge ward, please scan it and email it to me and I'll put it online here for all to see.</description></item><item><title>"Happy voting" ???</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 08:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</guid><description>Is &amp;ldquo;Happy voting!&amp;rdquo; really the proper way to close an email announcing a Council By-election? Anyway&amp;hellip;
A seat has become vacant in the Stonebridge Ward following the death of Councillor Dorman Long. A by-election will be held on Thursday, 13 September 2007 to elect a new representative.
The by-election gives the Lib Dems another opportunity to win a seat - but will they win it? I doubt it. Stonebridge ward is a Labour heartland - you only have to look at the votes cast in the 2006 Local Election to see that&amp;hellip; Winning this single seat will not change the overall political balance of Brent Council: The Lib Dems would need to win a few more by-elections or benefit from defections (not for the first time in Brent&amp;rsquo;s recent political history) in order to be in a position to leave the alliance with the Conservatives and lead a majority administration.</description></item><item><title>Electoral Canvassing 2007</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/03/electoral-canvassing-2007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/03/electoral-canvassing-2007/</guid><description>The 2007 Electoral Canvass is about to start. Once again we must all update our details on the Electoral Register. Failure to do so can lead to a fine of up to £1,000. Now that is what I call an incentive!
Electoral Canvassing - Your Questions Answered.
Posted after receiving a notification from Brent Council Electoral Services department.</description></item><item><title>legal challenges to the results</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/31/legal-challenges-to-the-results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 07:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/31/legal-challenges-to-the-results/</guid><description>Last weeks' (24th May) KTimes carried two stories about potential legal challenges to the results of the Brent Council elections. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what is happening with the query about the election of Cllr Pawan Gupta in Dudden Hill but I do have some news on the challenge to the count in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park.
I understand that Brent Council have written to all the candidates in the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward acknowledging the concern and the reasoning behind the querry raised by Shahrar Ali.</description></item><item><title>Next steps in Queen's Park ward</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/21/next-steps-in-queens-park-ward/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/21/next-steps-in-queens-park-ward/</guid><description>What news have I on the &amp;lsquo;missing votes&amp;rsquo; in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park? Well, I know that all the candidates have been written to by Shahrar Ali who has appraised them of his calculations and his investigations with Brent Council. I imagine that the next steps will be to petition the Returning Officer through the High Court as the Officer does not have the power to choose to recount the ballot. More info as and when I&amp;rsquo;ve digested the papers from the Law Courts&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Witnessing the count</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/19/witnessing-the-count/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/19/witnessing-the-count/</guid><description>The suggestion that a number of votes went uncounted at the local election is based on what was witnessed by Shahrar Ali on the night. There is no way that Shahrar could have seen all the ballot papers in for the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward, but he did witness the first sort and count of the block votes and also the count of the &amp;lsquo;splits&amp;rsquo; and the paper with unallocated votes.</description></item><item><title>How are votes counted?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/19/how-are-votes-counted/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 06:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/19/how-are-votes-counted/</guid><description>&lt;p>While researching &lt;a href="http://www.robdyke.com/bec/wp-trackback.php?p=125">the possibility of votes going uncounted in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward&lt;/a> I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered many interesting pieces of information. Well, I fiund them interesting anyway. Want to know how your votes are processed after you have mailing them of pushed them into those little black boxes at the polling station? Read more&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Missing votes in Queen's Park ward?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/12/missing-votes-in-queens-park/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/12/missing-votes-in-queens-park/</guid><description>Did those of you who stood up to be counted on May 4th get counted?
I&amp;rsquo;ve spent today researching the process for the counting of ballots and gathering information on the election result in Brent as I believe that there is cause for concern over the result returned in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward. My concern centres on the counting of ballot papers with unallocated votes. let me explain&amp;hellip;
You each had three votes on your ballot paper.</description></item><item><title>Photos from the count.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/07/photos-from-the-count/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2006 15:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/07/photos-from-the-count/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded all the snaps I took at the count to my gallery.</description></item><item><title>Updates at brent.gov</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/updates-at-brentgov/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 05:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/updates-at-brentgov/</guid><description>I wanted to post this when I got home from the count early this morning but the brent.gov webserver had broken and was not serving the Election Pages. 404errr. That and they were still counting when I got home. And recounting no doubt. You can get the full results for all the candidates in each ward direct from brent.gov.uk as they are uploaded.</description></item><item><title>And our winners are....</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/and-our-winners-are/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 05:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/05/and-our-winners-are/</guid><description>Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park, Mapesbury and Brondesbury have all turned Yellow - congratulations to the Cllrs in these wards. You&amp;rsquo;ve been trusted with them - look after them. Make sure that you continue with the effort that it took to win the ward as you work the ward.</description></item><item><title>Live! from Brent Town Hall it'...............?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/live-from-brent-town-hall-its/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/live-from-brent-town-hall-its/</guid><description>Well what a difference a year makes. Last year there was smoking in the Town Hall and a late (unlicensed?) bar. This year after two major pieces of legislation (smoking ban and 24h licensing) the Town Hall is not the den it was. Shame about the bar&amp;hellip; Now, where would I find out if the Council was licensed for the late bar last year&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. 😉</description></item><item><title>Going to the count...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/going-to-the-count/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 15:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/going-to-the-count/</guid><description>Last year I was the guest of Team Green. This year Team Yellow have invited me to join the best lockin in Brent. Once again I&amp;rsquo;ll bring you the result and a pretty graphic from the floor of the town hall as the result is announced&amp;hellip;.assuming I don&amp;rsquo;t fall asleep! I&amp;rsquo;m tired now. Not from any intensive campaigning like the Teams&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m a 6-week-new-dad! We&amp;rsquo;ll see if I make it through to the small hours again!</description></item><item><title>Big Brother Brent</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/big-brother-brent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 07:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/big-brother-brent/</guid><description> Big Brother Election Poster</description></item><item><title>Brent, are you voting?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/brent-are-you-voting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 07:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/04/brent-are-you-voting/</guid><description>I can see people reading this blog. There have been 216 of you this last week and 48 readers so far today! Are you voting, Brent people? Who are you voting for? Why? Why vote at all? Got any comments? After all, it&amp;rsquo;s Your Council for Your Street and Your Services - Are you having your say?
Me? Of course I&amp;rsquo;ve voted! I&amp;rsquo;ve supported Team Yellow in my ward, Mapesbury (Look for the Bird!</description></item><item><title>my thoughts on the results</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/my-thoughts-on-the-results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 17:50:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/my-thoughts-on-the-results/</guid><description>what do I think? I think the Green&amp;rsquo;s have won it really. I expect them to gain two seats, well, at least one in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. Also, I think that Cameron may have spoken to a lot of people at a local level and Team Blue will make a few gains. Team Yellow (Look for the Bird!) will also make gains, probably bringing them level with the Blues&amp;hellip; These gains will be to someones loss: Team Read.</description></item><item><title>been busy - is this the last post?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/been-busy-is-this-the-last-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/been-busy-is-this-the-last-post/</guid><description>well tomorrow is the day when Brent will select its councillors. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard many a rumour (and started a few) and seen many a bun thrown. Could I call Mapesbury, Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park or Brondesbury now? And the others in Brent East? Could I tell you have the council will look by Friday?
If you are into political betting then you&amp;rsquo;ll have seen the odds offered by one bookmaker. Here&amp;rsquo;s the Lib Dems story, bouyed as odds on them winning the council are slashed.</description></item><item><title>Past Election Results</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/past-election-results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/past-election-results/</guid><description>One sure-fire way of demonstrating that you have some skill with a computer is to generate a barchart from some data in a spreadsheet program like Calc (in openoffice) or a program from Microsoft. Both the Lib Dems and the Conservatives have got someone on their team that would pass a European Computer Driving License test no problem.
Both parties have proved that you can prove anything with stats.
Brent last elected its Councillors in 2002: long before the Iraq war, two (three?</description></item><item><title>5 reasons to vote - one is a tower!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/5-reasons-to-vote-one-is-a-tower/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 08:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/5-reasons-to-vote-one-is-a-tower/</guid><description>did anyone else see this? the electoral commission have been running advertising campaigns to encourage us out to a polling station next month. here&amp;rsquo;s one that i think makes the link between local service delivery and decision making nice and simply.
Electoral Commission - 5 reasons to vote
Reason number one (to vote) is the large tower block looming in the back ground over the lush green open space.</description></item><item><title>oh, and there is an election on</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/oh-and-there-is-an-election-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 20:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/oh-and-there-is-an-election-on/</guid><description>4th May. Elections for all seats on Brent Council.</description></item><item><title>did you know there was an election on?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/did-you-know-there-was-an-election-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 08:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/08/did-you-know-there-was-an-election-on/</guid><description>Elections are due to be held on 4th May 2006 to elect Councillors for all the seats on Brent Council.</description></item><item><title>Local Democracy: Election for Councillors in Preston and Fryent wards.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/24/local-democracy-election-for-councillors-in-preston-and-fryent-wards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/05/24/local-democracy-election-for-councillors-in-preston-and-fryent-wards/</guid><description>While technically in Brent North the elections for local councillors for the Preston and Fryent wards of Brent still need reporting - and where better then here?
Brent Councils Local Democracy pages have lots of information on the elections which will take place on the 16th June 2005.
Shahrar Ali will be standing in the Preston Ward as the Green Party Candidate. The Greens didn&amp;rsquo;t have a candidate in Brent North at the last election so it will be interesting to see how Shahrar and the Greens do in Preston - a gague of Green support in Brent North if you will.</description></item><item><title>Brent East by-election, 2003</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/brent-east-by-election-2003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/03/24/brent-east-by-election-2003/</guid><description>The by-election of 2003 was caused by the death of the member of Parliament for Brent East, Paul Daisley of the Labour Party. The by-election to fill his seat was held on September 13, and was won by the Liberal Democrat candidate Sarah Teather.
The turnout by electors at this election was 36.42%
More information on the 2003 Brent East by-election from wikipedia.</description></item></channel></rss>