<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tower block on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/tower-block/</link><description>Recent content in Tower block on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:25:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/tower-block/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Focus on...Queen's Park</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/focus-onqueens-park/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/focus-onqueens-park/</guid><description>A recent Focus On&amp;hellip;Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park from the Liberal Democrats with the candidates for Councillors showing their opposition to the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park tower development.
Lib Dems Focus on Queen&amp;#39;s Park Also highlighted are the traffic problems that are percieved will blight an already congested Salusbury Road. Well, the development is supposed to address this issue by changing the flow of traffic in the area - but with no tower to route traffic around&amp;hellip;?</description></item><item><title>Queen's Park Tower Plan</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/23/queens-park-tower-plan/</guid><description>The proposal for the tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park is a lead topic for each of the parties contesting the electoral ward of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park. For Labour it is getting like the Monty Python topic not to be mentioned in front of our hosts for the World Cup. The Lib Dems have made great gains from this thread - well, a sitting (yet not restanding) Councillor defected to Team Yellow with the tower plan as a key issue.</description></item><item><title>QP Greens letters on tower block development</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 14:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/qp-greens-letters-on-tower-block-development/</guid><description>I noticed these letters written by Dr Shahrar Ali, Green Party candidate for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park along with Rupert Degas, to Brent area newspapers recently.
On Brent Labour Council tower block imperatives:&amp;ldquo;Whilst this may not come as a revelation to seasoned campaigners, the public admission is a sign of desperation: a local government that denies responsibility for actions that it is going to take on our behalf but against our will.&amp;quot;On the timing of the planning process:</description></item><item><title>Tower Politics</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/tower-politics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 03:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/19/tower-politics/</guid><description>Over at stopthetower a recent email news update has been posted by Barney Cokeliss. Go read it for the stopthetower campaign group&amp;rsquo;s update on the proposed tower block development in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park.
Barney, Will and the gang have not yet got the hang of the idea that as the web is always on, 24hrs a day they can update their website with information as it happens, without having to wait for lots of things to report and then produce a newsletter.</description></item><item><title>JONATHAN DAVIES BRENT COUNCILLOR QUEENS PARK WARD</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/jonathan-davies-brent-councillor-queens-park-ward/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 06:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/13/jonathan-davies-brent-councillor-queens-park-ward/</guid><description>&lt;p>JONATHAN DAVIES BRENT COUNCILLOR QUEENS PARK WARD&lt;/p>
&lt;p>6 April 2006&lt;/p>
&lt;p>QUEEN&amp;rsquo;S PARK TOWERBLOCK&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Many people have been asking me about the Council&amp;rsquo;s plan to put a 26-storey towerblock on the car park next to Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Station. The Council is not prepared to have an open public consultation about the proposal. My view is that the people who elected me as their councillor deserve to be informed about the proposal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Council was in extensive pre-application talks with the proposed developer, Genesis, from at least the middle of 2004. In April 2005, the Council amended the planning guidance relating to the site to allow for a building of up to 20 storeys paving the way for Genesis&amp;rsquo;s planning application for a set of twin 26-storey towerblocks. The Council persuaded them to withdraw it in September 2005 due to the unexpected level of public opposition to the proposal.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Brent Labour Councillor Jonathan Davies has joined the Liberal Democrats</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/12/brent-labour-councillor-jonathan-davies-has-joined-the-liberal-democrats/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 07:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/12/brent-labour-councillor-jonathan-davies-has-joined-the-liberal-democrats/</guid><description>Brent Labour Councillor Jonathan Davies has joined the Liberal Democrats reports the BELD website.
&amp;ldquo;I have realised that the beliefs I stand for such as the safeguarding of our civil liberties, international justice and a free and fair society are best represented within the Liberal Democrats.&amp;rdquo;
Also connected to Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s feelings over the proposed development of a tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ? : &amp;ldquo;The issue of Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Tower is a classic example of Brent Labour in action.</description></item><item><title>Brent News from the Lib Dems</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 17:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/10/brent-news-from-the-lib-dems/</guid><description>This local red top was delivered in late February. It leads with the news of the Liberal Democrats delivering a &amp;ldquo;hammer blow&amp;rdquo; to Labour&amp;quot; in Dunfermline by-election.
brent news lib dems feb 06
The national political story was the continued opposition to the ID card legislation by Sarah Teather and the Liberal Democrats. The newsletter also covered the story of the comments made by Labour Cllr Jonathan Davies on the &amp;lsquo;consultation&amp;rsquo; over the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Tower plans.</description></item><item><title>calling it as you see it</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/calling-it-as-you-see-it/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 12:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/calling-it-as-you-see-it/</guid><description>Brent Lib Dems have been redistributing the comments made by Labour Cllr for Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Jonathan Davies on the governance and effectiveness of Brents' Labour Council.
Outer of BELD &amp;lsquo;the verdict&amp;rsquo; flyer
I&amp;rsquo;m glad to see that Cllr Davies has the ability to speak his own mind and to make judgements based on his observations. His views on the consultation around the proposed development consisting of a tower block in Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park will chime with many in the local area.</description></item><item><title>5 reasons to vote - one is a tower!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/5-reasons-to-vote-one-is-a-tower/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 08:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/09/5-reasons-to-vote-one-is-a-tower/</guid><description>did anyone else see this? the electoral commission have been running advertising campaigns to encourage us out to a polling station next month. here&amp;rsquo;s one that i think makes the link between local service delivery and decision making nice and simply.
Electoral Commission - 5 reasons to vote
Reason number one (to vote) is the large tower block looming in the back ground over the lush green open space.</description></item></channel></rss>