<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cricklewood on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/cricklewood/</link><description>Recent content in Cricklewood on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 06:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/cricklewood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Heritage Inn Community Event</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/05/31/heritage-inn-community-event/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 06:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/05/31/heritage-inn-community-event/</guid><description>I spent Bank Holiday Monday at the Heritage Inn Community Event. It was good to meet with my neighbors and to build bridges, so we can work together for the benefit of our locality. Viva Cricklewood!
Lovely chicken too.</description></item><item><title>More booze on the Broadway - respond now!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/more-booze-on-the-broadway-respond-now/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 14:50:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/11/04/more-booze-on-the-broadway-respond-now/</guid><description>The NW2 residents association is alerting local residents to an application for a 24h license for the sale of alcohol by a new business opening on the broadway. The former New Heights Furniture Shop in Cricklewood Broadway has been taken over by a supermarket called Way–2–Save. They have a branch in Neasden which has very good range of food, fresh fruit and veg and a halal butchers which would add to the choices for supermarket shopping in the area in a positive way.</description></item><item><title>North West Two</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/07/24/north-west-two/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 08:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/07/24/north-west-two/</guid><description>The website of my neighbourhood&amp;rsquo;s residents association, North West Two, is now up and running. Do drop by and visit them at www.northwesttwo.co.uk
Take a moment to register and then you can post comments on the news and information posted to the site. There will also be two mailing lists for the community, one distributing information from the association and a second one of local freecycle, skill swap and other announcements.</description></item><item><title>Five Brent Post Offices to close?</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/03/five-brent-post-offices-to-close/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 21:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/03/03/five-brent-post-offices-to-close/</guid><description>The Government and The Post Office last year announced plans to close around 2,500 Post Offices in the UK, of which up to 169 offices in London are shortlisted. All this was announced in October last year. Now the Post Office has begun a six-week consultation on plans for the capital's post offices... not that they are making a big thing about it on the website... you'll find it in small text on the right hand side under 'network changes'.</description></item><item><title>friends of cricklewood library...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/friends-of-cricklewood-library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2008/02/04/friends-of-cricklewood-library/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m now a Friend of Cricklewood Library. I join the group last month and attended a meeting. Going to be making a few Freedom of Information requests to Brent Council in search of data on public consultation exercises and service use.
More&amp;hellip; when I&amp;rsquo;ve got my degree work finished?</description></item></channel></rss>