<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brent East on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-east/</link><description>Recent content in Brent East on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:27:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/brent-east/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Local election leaflets online</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/04/23/local-election-leaflets-online/</guid><description>The Straight Choice election leaflet project is an archive of election leaflets distributed throughout the campaign. This is a helpful thing to be doing as &amp;hellip;..
Promises that candidates make in their leaflets can be compared to what they promise to do elsewhere. In the future we can also compare the voting record of MPs with what they promised on the campaign trail.
It helps catch parties or candidates who are breaking electoral law - 2 parties have been reported to the authorities based on leaflets uploaded to TheStraightChoice.</description></item><item><title>Boundary changes: Winners and losers</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/02/05/boundary-changes-winners-and-losers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2007 15:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/02/05/boundary-changes-winners-and-losers/</guid><description>The BBC have an article on the electoral ward boundary changes. London looses Brent East. The BBCs prediction for the larger seats that gain territory from Brent East are &amp;lsquo;labour marginal&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Local elections - Look for the BIRD!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/local-elections-look-for-the-bird/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2006 22:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/05/03/local-elections-look-for-the-bird/</guid><description>In Brent, we don&amp;rsquo;t do anything by halves. So today we elect all of our Councillors. Over at Brent East Campaigning there are a few last posts and a really great graph&amp;hellip; when I post again we&amp;rsquo;ll know what we&amp;rsquo;ve got for the next four years&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Past Election Results</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/past-election-results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/26/past-election-results/</guid><description>One sure-fire way of demonstrating that you have some skill with a computer is to generate a barchart from some data in a spreadsheet program like Calc (in openoffice) or a program from Microsoft. Both the Lib Dems and the Conservatives have got someone on their team that would pass a European Computer Driving License test no problem.
Both parties have proved that you can prove anything with stats.
Brent last elected its Councillors in 2002: long before the Iraq war, two (three?</description></item><item><title>More on Brent East Campaigning</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/11/more-on-brent-east-campaigning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 17:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/04/11/more-on-brent-east-campaigning/</guid><description>The b.e.c weblog fears without loathing the Brent East Campaign trail, posting articles and images that catalogue the activism of the political parties and some independent candidates in this area.
I blogged the 2005 General Election, now I’m back for more during the four weeks prior to the local elections in May.</description></item><item><title>There’s an election on...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/theres-an-election-on.../</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2005 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/12/theres-an-election-on.../</guid><description>&amp;hellip;or had you&amp;rsquo;d missed that?
I want to share the Brent East campaign experience from the point of view of the electorate. And I want to distribute information about the candidates and the parties standing in Brent East to my neighbours in this constituency. So until the 6th of May, when the hangover is gone and the lost sleep caught up on, I&amp;rsquo;ll put most of my posting efforts into &amp;lsquo;Brent East Campaigning&amp;rsquo;</description></item><item><title>Campaign Materials - Greens</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-greens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2005 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/11/campaign-materials-greens/</guid><description>Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Front Page - JPG
Brent East Green News - A4 newsletter - Back Page - JPG</description></item><item><title>Meeting Yasmin Qureshi</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/09/meeting-yasmin-qureshi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2005 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/09/meeting-yasmin-qureshi/</guid><description>On Thursday I bumped into Yasmin Qureshi, the Labour candidate for Brent East, on Salusbury Road just outside the friendly and well stocked Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park Books (yes, I do work there, how did you guess?). She was out on the campaign trail, meeting and greeting, probably kissing babies, seeking places to display her posters. Yasmin was accompanied by the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Park ward local Councillor Neil Nerva.
I&amp;rsquo;ve met Neil Nerva before.</description></item><item><title>Brent East Campaign Trail</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/brent-east-campaign-trail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 09:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/04/08/brent-east-campaign-trail/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started to blog the Brent East constituency election campaign. I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing all the paper propaganda distributed by candidates over the coming four weeks. Wide open for all the see. Informed choice facilitated.
I&amp;rsquo;ve met two of the candidates already, well three, as I&amp;rsquo;ve met Sarah Teather too. More to share on that score soon.</description></item><item><title>Congratulations Brent East.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/congratulations-brent-east./</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2005/02/15/congratulations-brent-east./</guid><description>Sarah has been unanimously re-selected by Brent Liberal Democrats to fight the next General Election. You can read the news story on this over at the BELD website.
Sarah said she would be campaigning for a renewed mandate from the electorate of Brent East on local issues such as civic neglect, neighbourhood policing, housing problems and post office closures. Her efforts would continue in the House of Commons tackling ID cards, detention without trail and student tuition fees.</description></item><item><title>Happy anniversary Sarah!</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/14/happy-anniversary-sarah/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2004/10/14/happy-anniversary-sarah/</guid><description>Today Sarah celebrates the first anniversary of being elected to serve Brent East. 365 Days in office. Happy anniversary Sarah.
In today&amp;rsquo;s Guardian Sarah is interviewed by Matt Barnard where she talks about the highlights of the last 12 months.
Top thing you probably didn&amp;rsquo;t know about Sarah that you&amp;rsquo;ll discover from the interview - she&amp;rsquo;s learning Gujarati.</description></item></channel></rss>