<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community Network on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/community-network/</link><description>Recent content in Community Network on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 08:44:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/community-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SKNDC community network ideas</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/skndc-community-network-ideas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 08:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/skndc-community-network-ideas/</guid><description>Last year SKNDC advertised for interested parties to propose solutions for a wireless network project in South Kilburn. Comwifinet responded and we won the work. Yet the project was shelved as the budget for ICT in the Home ran out.
SKFM, the community radio station broadcasting from the NDC area, is currently streaming to listeners over the internet. Listening to the stream reminded me of the community network project and I&amp;rsquo;ve begun to make contact with SKNDC again.</description></item><item><title>community network presentation - Tower Hamlets</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/community-network-presentation-tower-hamlets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2006 08:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/19/community-network-presentation-tower-hamlets/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the presentation for viewing in a web browser. You can also download a PDF of the presentation if you need (and I stress NEED) to print it.</description></item><item><title>Tower Hamlets - community wireless</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/tower-hamlets-community-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 07:44:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/tower-hamlets-community-wireless/</guid><description>Visiting Tower Hamlets today to talk about seeding a sustainable community enterprise while increasing participation and technology access using wireless technologies. More to post on this later.</description></item><item><title>civic reporter developments</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-developments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 07:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-developments/</guid><description>early last week I met with two people from Brent Council Environment &amp;amp; Culture Department to discuss the Civic Reporter ideas and application framework that Comwifinet have been working on. A great opportunity to discuss how open accessible data could further develop participation in the up keep of the Borough. Brent Council considering working with a Made In Brent technology organisation and mobile technologies. Brent Council entertaining the public publishing daily status and performance information online.</description></item><item><title>civic reporter - background</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2006/09/18/civic-reporter-background/</guid><description>The background to all this. Comwifinet had prototyped the Civic Reporter framework which is inspired by other innovative mobile technology projects, such as that implemented by Lewisham and the mySociety &amp;lsquo;Broken Civic Infrastructure&amp;rsquo; idea. These similar initiatives all start from the question &amp;lsquo;Would putting pictures of abandoned cars on a map on the internet help people to think again about their role in maintaining a tidy Borough?
[The background to all this.</description></item></channel></rss>