<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stonebridge on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/stonebridge/</link><description>Recent content in Stonebridge on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/stonebridge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Photos from Stonebridge - Hillside &amp; Fawood Children's Centre</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/photos-from-stonebridge-hillside-fawood-childrens-centre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/photos-from-stonebridge-hillside-fawood-childrens-centre/</guid><description>From wikipedia: Stonebridge is the largest electoral ward in Brent and includes Stonebridge Estate, and parts of Park Royal and Brent Park, St. Raphael&amp;rsquo;s Estate, Mitchellbrook and the Hillside district. The area has strong links with the Afro-Caribbean community which forms the ward&amp;rsquo;s ethnic majority.
Here are a few photos of the last remaining block on the Stonebridge Estate off Hillside, Brent. You can see the cleared land from recent demolition work in the foreground.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Butler's hoarding at Unisys, Brentfield</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/dawn-butlers-hoarding-at-unisys-brentfield/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 13:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/05/dawn-butlers-hoarding-at-unisys-brentfield/</guid><description>Is back on its legs.
Whatever you do, don&amp;rsquo;t visit the web address stencilled on the windows of the building, unless you want to book an escort&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Butler hording advertising at Unisys, Brentfield.</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/butler-advertising-at-unisys-brentfield/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2010/05/04/butler-advertising-at-unisys-brentfield/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Consider a building with a few broken windows. If the windows are not repaired, the tendency is for vandals to break a few more windows. Eventually, they may even break into the building, and if it&amp;rsquo;s unoccupied, perhaps become squatters or light fires inside.&amp;rdquo; Wilson and Kelling, 1982.
A building like this?
The ex-Unisys building on Brentfield has been empty for well over a decade. In 1997 the owners were granted planning consent to convert the office blocks to a 330-bedroom hotel, add a new penthouse storey on front block facing North Circular Road, a new single-deck car park and new boundary wall.</description></item><item><title>Stonebridge candidates</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 14:05:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/23/stonebridge-candidates/</guid><description>With the candidates nominated for the Stonebridge by-election, here&amp;rsquo;s a little summary of them for you:
ALADESHE, Funmi The Conservative Party COX, Sarah Respect ORR, Brian Green Party VAN KALWALA, Zaffar The Labour Party WILTSHIRE, Sandra Elina Liberal Democrats</description></item><item><title>"Happy voting" ???</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 08:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2007/08/09/happy-voting/</guid><description>Is &amp;ldquo;Happy voting!&amp;rdquo; really the proper way to close an email announcing a Council By-election? Anyway&amp;hellip;
A seat has become vacant in the Stonebridge Ward following the death of Councillor Dorman Long. A by-election will be held on Thursday, 13 September 2007 to elect a new representative.
The by-election gives the Lib Dems another opportunity to win a seat - but will they win it? I doubt it. Stonebridge ward is a Labour heartland - you only have to look at the votes cast in the 2006 Local Election to see that&amp;hellip; Winning this single seat will not change the overall political balance of Brent Council: The Lib Dems would need to win a few more by-elections or benefit from defections (not for the first time in Brent&amp;rsquo;s recent political history) in order to be in a position to leave the alliance with the Conservatives and lead a majority administration.</description></item></channel></rss>