<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EHI on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/ehi/</link><description>Recent content in EHI on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 15:49:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/ehi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the special category of the awards that is, of course, chosen by the readers of EHI</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2013/10/13/the-special-category-of-the-awards-that-is-of-course-chosen-by-the-readers-of-ehi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 22:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2013/10/13/the-special-category-of-the-awards-that-is-of-course-chosen-by-the-readers-of-ehi/</guid><description>So, this years Healthcare IT Champion of the Year, the special category of the awards that is chosen by the readers of EHI, was announced as Kemi Adenubi, the GPSoC programme director for the Health and Social Care Information Centre.
Adenubi described winning the award as &amp;ldquo;absolutely fabulous&amp;rdquo;; &amp;ldquo;It was wonderful to be nominated, it was great fun to have people say ‘I voted for you’,This will be really good for the project and the team as it shows there’s some recognition for the project we have done together, because it’s an individual nomination, but I have a great team.</description></item><item><title>EHI Healthcare IT Champion 2013</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2013/06/27/ehi-healthcare-it-champion-2013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2013/06/27/ehi-healthcare-it-champion-2013/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been nominated for EHI Healthcare IT Champion 2013.
Vote for me and give your support to &amp;ldquo;playing nicely together&amp;rdquo;!
Its a great honour to be nominated by my peers for an award which seeks to recognise commitment and achievement above and beyond someone&amp;rsquo;s day job. Sure, I run Tactix4 which provides services and support for opensource solutions to the NHS but I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in plenty more these past 24 months which have shaped policy, practice and procurement of technology for healthcare IT in the UK.</description></item></channel></rss>