<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tactix4 on this is rob dyke dot com</title><link>https://robdyke.com/tags/tactix4/</link><description>Recent content in Tactix4 on this is rob dyke dot com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 23:44:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robdyke.com/tags/tactix4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>So far in 2014...</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2014/05/20/so-far-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2014/05/20/so-far-in-2014/</guid><description>Really? 6 months since my last update? Bonkers.
By way of an update, here are a few slideshares from recent conferences I&amp;rsquo;ve been presenting at.
At Healthcare Innovation Expo Tactix4 were participants in the NHS England Open Source Programme and I shared these slides as part of my discussion
Back in Manchester a week later for BCS Health 2014 I participated in the stream &amp;lsquo;Fit for practice – exploring the nursing experience of the usability of clinical systems&amp;rsquo; facilitated by the Royal College of Nurses and Chaired by Dr Susan Hamer of The National Institute for Health Research.</description></item><item><title>Tactix4 with ITK ISCF award with Luton and Dunstable NHS Trust</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2012/12/16/tactix4-with-itk-iscf-award-with-luton-and-dunstable-nhs-trust/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 18:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2012/12/16/tactix4-with-itk-iscf-award-with-luton-and-dunstable-nhs-trust/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m pleased that my company &lt;a href="http://www.tactix4.com/">Tactix4&lt;/a> has won two awards from The &lt;a href="http://www.dh.gov.uk/health/2012/12/sharing-challenge-funding/">Information Sharing Challenge Fund&lt;/a>, a Department of Health initiative funding ideas that change the way information is used and shared between different organisations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Two NHS Trusts bid with Tactix4 demonstrating that our ideas showed value for money that could easily be adopted by other NHS organisations as part of the NHS Interoperability Toolkit (ITK).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tactix4 win ITK ISCF award with Kings College Hospital</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2012/12/16/tactix4-win-two-itk-iscf-awards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 18:07:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2012/12/16/tactix4-win-two-itk-iscf-awards/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m pleased that my company &lt;a href="http://www.tactix4.com/">Tactix4&lt;/a> has won two awards from The &lt;a href="http://www.dh.gov.uk/health/2012/12/sharing-challenge-funding/">Information Sharing Challenge Fund&lt;/a>, a Department of Health initiative funding ideas that change the way information is used and shared between different organisations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Two NHS Trusts bid with Tactix4 demonstrating that our ideas showed value for money that could easily be adopted by other NHS organisations as part of the NHS Interoperability Toolkit (ITK).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A few notes on the enthusiasm around healthcare IT</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2012/07/06/a-few-notes-on-the-enthusiasm-around-healthcare-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 12:55:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2012/07/06/a-few-notes-on-the-enthusiasm-around-healthcare-it/</guid><description>&lt;p>There is a renewed vigor in healthcare IT. Lots of great projects curated by enthusiastic people, encouraging new thinking around the definition, development design and delivery of technology for healthcare. Here I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about &lt;a href="http://digihealthcon.wordpress.com/">DigiHealthCon&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="http://www.handihealth.net/">HANDI&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="http://nhshackday.com/">NHS Hack Day&lt;/a> and the &lt;a href="http://ehealthopensource.org/">eHealthOpenSource&lt;/a> competition and Pipe and Hat Club. I&amp;rsquo;m involved in three organisations: eHealth OpenSource as Secretary, HANDI as a co-founder and NHS Hack Day as a participant and advocate. When I&amp;rsquo;m not doing things relating to those three, I&amp;rsquo;m a Director of &lt;a href="http://www.tactix4.com/">Tactix4 Limited&lt;/a>, an opensource healthcare IT company. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share some of my thinking about these projects and how I see them fitting together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cough up the hairball and make NHS technology open</title><link>https://robdyke.com/2011/08/05/573/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 16:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robdyke.com/2011/08/05/573/</guid><description>Here is a piece co-authored by me published in the Guardian Healthcare Network on open source in the NHS.
In my view the NHS would benefit greatly from greater use of open source, standards and data, according to the creators of the award-winning Open Me project:
&amp;ldquo;The NHS technology environment could be described as a giant hairball – a Gordian knot of past policies, established practices, new initiatives and government objectives and an ever changing landscape of opportunity from new technology.</description></item></channel></rss>